W is Korea's best webtoon series.
Kang Chul is the protagonist.
It looks good on you.
He meets the girl from reality, Oh Yeon Joo,
and dreams of starting a happy life.
The killer who killed Chul's entire family 10 years ago appears.
I will put a hole on her forehead.
He threatens Chul to kill Yeon Joo.
As the purpose of W's characters disappear,
the characters themselves start to disappear too.
Chul join hands with W's writer, Seong Moo,
and tries to protect the W world as well as Yeon Joo.
They catch the man who killed Chul's entire family 10 years ago,
and the plan was just about to be accomplished.
The killer with Seong Moo's face appears and...
makes all the plans go down the drain.
He kills Mr Son Hyeon Seok who was almost like Chul's father...
and falsely accuses Chul as the killer.
Stop the car. I will drive.
Chul gets shot by the police on the run and struggles to live.
He gets saved by Yeon Joo who went back to the reality for Chul.
Grocery shopping.
Cake.
Give me one bite.
Go for shopping.
How is this? It's five dollars.
It's cheap.
(Episode 12)
Did we do four things now?
Today's task is done if we do two more.
Do you like it with a lot of bacon?
- What did you just say?
-  What?
You said something about task.
The task to do 10 sweet things a day.
You said your husband disappeared after doing only four of them.
I wanted to do them on behalf of your husband...
because you saved my life.
You said your husband looked like me.
Isn't that why...
you're following me?
How did you know?
I never mentioned anything about the task.
I read it.
From where?
Here.
Do you know this webtoon?
Your face tells me you know it well.
I read it here.
Your husband disappeared after doing four sweet things.
He was so cheap.
How could he do that to his wife?
You didn't appear, and I couldn't do anything here,
so I read this over and over.
The story was fun and interesting.
I felt bad for Kang Chul, but he also seemed foolish...
like me.
That's why I didn't turn myself in...
so that I could meet you.
I was going to ask you what happens next.
I couldn't go to prison without finding that out.
Have you read the book after this one?
After this one,
what happens to Chul and Yeon Joo?
Does Chul...
forget Yeon Joo for good?
Answer me.
Is your husband who suddenly disappeared...
me?
Is it hard for you to answer?
Then let's find out together.
This is your father's studio, right?
I...
didn't know I took the book with me.
I wasn't planning to tell you.
I was going to keep it a secret.
I just...
wanted it to be a happen ending, that's all.
Hey, Seok Beom.
Seok Beom, please don't go.
Let me go.
I'm so scared.
I'm more scared of you. You laugh by yourself.
I have to get to the hospital.
Please wait with me just until Yeon Joo's back.
When is Yeon Joo coming back?
You don't even know where she went.
Where is your father?
Why?
I want to meet him.
Don't worry, I won't shoot him.
I'd be an idiot to make the same mistake twice.
Where is he?
He didn't draw it.
He never framed you.
Please don't mistake him.
Why is the door locked?
You'll see.
Mr Oh?
This is Oh Seong Moo?
Yes.
What happened to him?
I don't know either.
It's only been a few hours, although it's months in your time.
I'm dizzy.
I'm...
Come on, Dr Kang. Brother. Brother.
It'll only be a little while.
It won't be long. No.
Have a bowl of ramyeon. I'll make it for you.
Stop offering me ramyeon. Why do you keep touching me?
Wasn't that door closed before?
What? What?
Who... Who is he?
Kang... Kang...
Kang what?
Can you help me? She fainted.
Yeon Joo.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
It's just exhaustion.
Exhaustion?
I skipped a month of time.
It was like this last time, too.
Does this mean all you have to do is rest?
Yes, rest will do.
I'm glad.
Are you going to Myungsei University Medical Centre?
Of course.
Nurse Kim. We're coming over now. Can you book a room for us?
We'll do the basic tests and a chest x-ray.
Where are you going?
Don't go.
I have something I have to take care of. I'll join you soon.
Do you remember?
Do you...
remember me?
Do you remember everything now?
No.
I'm just assuming...
how the Kang Chul in the comic would have felt.
Since you didn't change, I'm sure I'll find out soon...
what your strange charm is about.
I'll come in a bit. Please take care of her.
That's Kang Chul.
It's Kang Chul for sure. It's definitely him. Why is he here?
Kang Chul... Why is Kang Chul...
I...
May I come in?
Yes... Yes. Come in.
What is your name?
It's Park Soo Bong.
I'm sorry, but can I borrow your shoes?
I came here without shoes.
Yes, sure.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I've met you once before.
We have?
In the garden.
- I'm sorry.
-  I don't think sorry will cut it.
I'm sorry. I don't know any scenes that wasn't in the book.
I see.
Do you have a screwdriver?
A screwdriver? Do you mean a slot or a double-slot?
Do you want both?
(A loud noise)
Pardon me.
Here you go.
I brought a slot and double-slot screwdrivers...
just in case.
What are you going to do?
It's because it's dangerous. The same thing shouldn't happen again.
He won't come out if I destroy it completely.
I see.
If you disassemble it, you won't be able to assemble it back.
What if you need it again?
That's right. You majored in computer science.
- What happened to Oh Seong Moo?
-  Well,
while I was gone to get some snacks,
his face had disappeared like that.
He was drawing like the killer told him to.
He had a gun and the voice file.
It wasn't just over there.
It was such a mess here, too.
Yeon Joo suddenly disappeared,
and Mr Oh's face also disappeared.
I was so scared that I was shuddering,
and then you appeared suddenly.
By the way, Chul,
may I ask for a handshake?
I've been your fan for a long time.
I couldn't talk to you back then because of the situation,
so I...
Goodness.
It was me who drew the penthouse and the broadcasting station.
I'm the one who draws those.
I've been drawing the background for three years.
Is that so?
This is amazing.
Do you want some beer? You like beer. I have beers of all types.
Water will do.
I'll bring you some water. Of course I will.
Goodness, this is incredible.
Oh, my goodness.
He even smells good.
(Oh, no.)
Here's your water.
Thank you. Where can I find what happens after episode 34?
- Episode 34?
-  I need to see the next one...
to find out what's been happening.
Here you go.
Is this the letter I sent?
Yes, you sent it to Mr Oh.
(Where is Kang Chul?)
(Please give it to your father.)
Mr Oh and I were creating a story...
to catch the killer.
Then that's how that happened to Mr Oh.
What's the story you created?
This is the storyboard.
(You can't shoot me because you're just a set-up.)
You're just an illusion.
You're nothing but a character I created.
Why did you appear in front of me...
and pretending to be human?
You're just a character, do you understand?
You're just a set-up I created.
How can you be a creator?
Why did I think you were a creator?
Why was I so upset...
that I shot you?
You're nothing, either.
Who is it?
Take a guess.
Guess who I am.
How do you feel being alone in an empty world?
You love killing people by shooting them,
but you have no one to kill now.
You probably can't shoot, either.
How are you surviving?
You can't leave again like last time...
because I got rid of the exit.
Isn't it better to just die?
Are you telling me...
- to die?
-  What's the point of living alone?
The time would be stopped forever.
Why would I die?
You'll disappear first.
You're no longer the main character. You're a murderer and a fugitive.
You'll disappear soon.
Once the main character disappears,
the world keeps going again.
All I have to do is wait for you to disappear,
so why would I die?
Mum?
Was that a dream?
Was that all a dream?
- Hello?
-  Are you awake?
How do you feel?
Hello? Can't you hear me?
I can hear you.
I asked how you are. Are you all right?
I think I am all right.
But where are you right now?
I'm near your father's studio.
You're here right now?
Are you really calling me from here?
How can I call you from the comic?
I just got a cellphone under Park Soo Bong's name.
Save the number. It's mine.
Will you continue to sleep?
If you're feeling okay, let's go on a date.
A date?
While you were down for two days, I adjusted to this world.
I also figured out what's happening. I did everything.
Except for my marriage problem.
What?
It says that I am your husband,
and I think it's certainly true. I've only read it in the comic,
so I can't feel it.
So I waited for you to wake up.
Let's go on a date.
You know me too well, and I don't know much about you.
So you need to give me chances to catch up.
Do you not want to?
I have to go to Dad. I just woke up.
Let's talk about your dad when we meet. I got things to say.
You're going on a date with me, right?
Start getting ready. I'll call you when I'm near.
- Hello?
-  I was...
I was just checking if it's really your number.
It is.
But where did you get the money to buy the phone?
I took it from Soo Bong.
Can you pay him back for me? I borrowed a lot.
Am I your bank or something?
You want me to go separate ways?
You're mean.
Even when I was broke, I bought you clothes and ice cream.
I didn't say anything. I was just asking.
- Why?
-  When are you coming again?
Will 30 minutes be enough?
No. Give me an hour.
Okay.
Yes. He borrowed money.
- 1,000 dollars.
-  1,000 dollars?
- That's a lot.
-  Well,
he had to buy shoes, clothes, and a mobile phone.
He needs money to go on a date with you too.
I'll pay you back later.
Don't worry about it. I guess he will pay me.
You can't handle it. He spends as if he's super rich.
I know. I'm going to go bankrupt.
By the way, what's going to happen now?
Will he continue to live here?
Is that possible? Can I get my money back?
Well, it's been all right so far.
I wonder if it's possible from now on.
I'm normal when I'm there.
So isn't it the same?
By the way, do you know that?
His hand is strange.
Don't you have more?
How much more?
The more the better. I need a lot of things.
Is that all?
I have more in my bank account.
What? Your hand...
What? Your...
It's happening because I'm not acting like the protagonist.
Don't tell Yeon Joo.
Remember? Remember when So Hee was about to disappear?
His hand turned translucent.
Gosh. He told me not to tell you.
I said it.
Don't tell him that I told you about what he said.
Let's talk later. Someone's at the door.
Gosh, I might not get my money back.
Mum?
Yeon Joo.
- Can I come in?
-  Wait.
How... How did you come here?
You said you were going to call me when you're near.
I wanted to see how you live.
What?
I heard from Soo Bong that your mum went to work.
I'm going in.
The book lacks a lot of information.
I have the right to know about you, you know?
Well.
So this is where you live.
Yes.
This is where I live. It's nothing like a penthouse.
It's nice and cosy in here.
It's similar to my old house.
Why did you come barging in? I'm not ready yet.
Get ready and come out. I'll wait.
There are beverages in the fridge. Feel free to drink them.
Okay.
Wait.
Can you take off your gown?
What did you just say?
Nothing.
You're sad that I don't remember it,
and I'm frustrated too.
Shouldn't we do everything we did in this comic?
We should see each other in nude and kiss five times.
There is a big gap in our relationships.
I'm curious.
I want to feel how Chul felt in this comic.
You're joking, right?
I am very serious right now.
No way.
Take your time. I will wait for you here.
(- Did we complete four?
-  Is it time to do the task?)
What are you doing?
Thank you.
For what?
For not forgetting me and missing me.
We don't have a picture.
Let's take a picture together. I regretted it a lot.
Okay.
Is she your mother? She's beautiful.
Yes.
Your husband had never been in your room, right?
What?
If he knew you were such a dirty person,
he would've thought about marriage one more time.
He's a neat-freak.
He would've been shocked.
It's all your fault!
I was going mad because I thought you might be dead.
When did I have any time to clean my room?
And originally I am a very neat person.
I saw everything, so I'll go down and wait.
Come down when you are ready.
Where are we going?
What do you feel like eating?
Are you going to treat me?
You don't know any place.
You have neither money nor friends.
So I have to buy.
I'll tell you what I think about the comic.
Chul and Yeon Joo got married too early.
But of course there was a situation.
So let's go on a date,
like other couples.
It's funny that we're on a date when we're married.
Let's take time to do the sweet things you like.
Let's go with the flow.
What do you think?
I like it.
Where should we go? You can choose.
Maybe we came too late. It's just us here.
Right.
When do I get to have those five kisses?
What?
How about now? No one is around.
That's enough joking around.
I'm serious.
I was joking about seeing you in nude earlier, but I'm serious now.
Do you not want to? Is it too awkward?
- Then we'll take it slow.
-  No...
Why would it be awkward?
Then can I do it?
Yes.
You can...
Is this how it feels?
I see.
- I get it.
-  Get what?
How does it feel?
No comments.
No comments?
It's delicious. I'm glad you picked this place.
Are you mad? Why aren't you talking?
Your hand.
What should we do?
I know you've been hiding it from me since earlier.
I was going to tell you after we finished.
I can't...
eat.
It's been like this for about a month...
ever since Mr Son died.
- What are we going to do?
-  Take care of it.
How are we going to take care of it?
I've talked to your father a lot since then.
With my father?
I didn't know which one was Oh Seong Moo, so I met both.
That's how I knew why our plan failed.
No. No, no...
Please don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
Who are you?
I'm supposed to kill Kang Chul.
Why did you kill him?
(Why did you kill him?)
How are you alive when you've been stabbed?
What are you?
Who are you?
Don't be so conceited.
I found out before you did.
Oh Seong Moo promised me then...
to make me a face.
One more thing.
Please...
You'll be the protagonist. I'll turn you into the protagonist.
No, it's not hard to do.
I can make it happen. Please...
He told me I'd become the protagonist if I get rid of you.
He promised me,
but he betrayed me as soon as he returned.
That jerk.
That's why I ate him.
For breaking his promise.
What does...
There's something your father failed to tell me.
He had already met the killer that day.
They also had made a promise.
That's why it didn't work when we tried to turn it into a dream.
He was aware of his identity, and my memories were erased.
It's my mistake.
I chose the wrong point in time to turn into a dream.
That's why things got messy.
Then...
I thought about it.
Let's make a promise.
About what?
When you go to the studio,
draw me a picture.
What do you mean? What now?
Are you telling me to turn this into a dream all over again?
Then you'll disappear from here.
It's easy for you since you'll forget about me and live on,
but I have to stay here by myself and repeat the memories again.
If you were going to be like this,
why did you ask me to date?
Why did you kiss me just now?
- I never mentioned dreams.
-  That's what you're trying to say.
You want to turn back time to before the killer knew...
about his identity so that everyone is safe.
That's what the cartoon's Kang Chul said.
That's not my plan.
We were in a bind. We didn't have a choice then.
Now, we have time to think.
I don't want to live the same life over again either.
Nor do I want you to have these repeating memories.
Then...
what do you want me to draw?
Draw this for me.
What is this?
I think the killer has to die for your dad to return.
Since I'm no longer the protagonist,
I might disappear again.
There is only one solution.
It's the story your father and I had planned from the beginning.
Hello?
It's me.
How are the kids?
We have to catch the killer and make Han Cheol Ho kill him.
That's the best way. We must make it happen.
It's the only way for your father and I to live.
Although,
I want to change the ending your father wrote.
In the end,
Kang Chul and Oh Yeon Joo should get married and live happily.
That would be the best ending for W.
Don't you think so?
I don't care what the readers think.
I realised after I saw your father.
Oh Seong Moo is not a creator.
He thought he was and that's why this happened to him.
It's impossible for him to have created everything in that world.
How can a writer make up billions of characters?
It doesn't make sense.
What he could control was the few he designed himself.
That's why I came to this conclusion.
The comic book is only a pathway to connect the two worlds.
This world and that world are each independent.
Two different worlds.
- Where does the killer live?
-  Pardon me?
There must be a place. Is there any photo you used as a reference?
There are photos of an apartment I used.
Where is it?
Was the killer's address mentioned in the webtoon?
No, because things happened before I drew anything.
That's why the police couldn't find him.
These are the photos of the apartment I used.
(Sungha Apartment in Mungye-dong, Dobong-gu, Seoul)
What the two worlds share in common are things in the webtoon...
including me, a few other characters...
and certain locations and things that are set up.
Two worlds came together via Oh Seong Moo's tablet.
I left via the tablet,
but there were variables.
- What's going on?
-  The characters became aware.
Yeon Joo.
Depending on which characters became aware,
people in real life were called upon.
They were kicked out when one episode ended.
Variables continued to appear,
and because of that, you've been used so far.
You've been used enough.
It's time that we use the variables to our advantage.
What do you want to eat?
- A hamburger.
-  A hamburger?
Let's go get some hamburgers.
I chose apartment number 815. There's no particular reason.
10 minutes will be enough.
After 10 minutes, turn it on.
I'm in reality.
At the same time, I'm one of the characters.
If a character can call someone in reality,
my first hypothesis is...
that I can pull myself back into the world of the webtoon.
From now on, I'll summon myself.
Here,
the world of the webtoon.
Hello, this is 112.
I'd like to report a suspect for murder.
I'm listening. Which murder case are you referring to?
I caught the killer of the shooting at Channel W.
Please arrest him.
Okay, please wait one moment.
The address is Sungha Apartment 2-815, 216-13...
Mungye-dong, Dobong-gu, Seoul.
His name is Han Sang Hoon.
We'll leave now and check.
Could you identify yourself?
I'm just a citizen.
Hello? Hello?
Sir, we received an important report.
Which one of us will die first?
I think it'll be you.
Since I caught the killer, it will take some time for me to disappear.
I completed one of the main character's tasks.
You scum.
Rot in the detention centre for a while.
I'll think about how to kill you.
Is this...
Once you leave here, go to the office and draw this.
I assembled the tablet.
No. You already know.
If I turn it on, the killer...
That's why we must catch the killer so he won't be free.
I'll stop him from getting his hands...
on the tablet.
First, draw the car I'll ride.
Check his identity.
He looks like him.
We caught the killer of the shooting.
Please send us the support.
All right, that's enough. Let's stop the interview now.
I'm a little tired.
Sir, the killer of the shooting got arrested.
Wait a moment.
What do you mean? Where?
He was arrested in his apartment in Dobong-gu.
- How?
-  Someone reported to the police.
Who are you talking about?
- What?
-  Isn't it President Kang?
The one who reported him.
The police said his voice was similar to his.
What if he's alive?
I think he's alive.
It's definitely President Kang.
Perhaps. We should find out more about it.
Okay.
No way.
How does it make sense? He was certainly there.
At around 10:30pm,
the suspect who killed 10 people at a shooting at Channel W office...
was arrested at his home.
The suspect hasn't been identified yet.
He was reported by a courageous citizen.
The anonymous citizen went into the suspect's house,
and after a fight, he reported...
The second you must draw is...
my dead body in decay.
Where are you?
- What do you mean?
-  Did you see the news?
So Hee thinks it's you who caught the killer.
Yes, I caught him.
What? Is it true?
- How did you do it?
-  Do Yoon, listen carefully.
Go to my house where I was 15 days ago.
Then you'll find my body.
What? What are you talking about?
Report it to the police and let everyone know.
The body's DNA will match mine.
Do Yoon, I'm dead.
I got shot and died unjustly with a false charge.
However, I'm still alive, so don't worry.
I thought you should know.
- Hey.
-  It's better that...
So Hee thinks I'm dead.
It's for her own good.
I'll call you later.
Then,
what about So Hee?
If it's a happy ending for us,
she'll disappear again.
- I'll create a variable for her.
-  A variable?
I can't accept the fact that there's only one reason...
for our existence.
When there's a variable, the direction of one's life changes...
like how I met you.
If her fate is determined only because she's one of the characters,
we'll free her.
Hey, I'm going to the police station now.
I heard the voice, and I think it's him,
so right now, I...
What?
He died?
I'm going to get rid of...
the set-up for So Hee.
On 23rd, the police announced...
that a dead body found in Yangpyeong-gun, Gyeonggi Provice...
was identified as Kang Chul.
On 22nd of last month,
Kang was on a flee under the charge of killing the director of WBN.
After 33 days of fleeing, he was found dead.
Kang was shot by the police while fleeing...
How can you come back?
Once you leave now, it's over.
You can't come back here.
I think I can.
It was only possible when you became aware.
That means you have to come back after losing all of your memories.
- Then, it'll only be a dream.
-  I don't want dreams any more.
What are you going to do?
I think it'll be possible. Wait here for me.
You also said that last time.
You told me to wait until the operation is over,
but you disappeared.
That's Kang Chul in the comic.
There's one more thing I'd like you to draw.
It's too expensive here, and I couldn't afford it.
Draw me the ring I lost.
My second hypothesis is...
that I've been called into reality.
Therefore, when the mission in one episode is accomplished,
I...
go back.
(To be continued)
(Kang Chul)
Hello?
I came back.
Where are you?
I'm coming to you now.
Get ready so that we finish our date.
Let's finish our fifth kiss.
What?
I can't stand losing.
I can't let your ex-husband defeat me.
That's a strange competition.
Are you competing with someone?
You'll find out soon that I'm much better.
(W)
Oh Yeon Joo, the character I'm tired of...
appears again.
W is no longer a webtoon. I abandoned it.
Hope makes me imagine again.
As Chul came back to me,
W ended with a happy ending.
I heard Han Sang Hoon escaped from prison.
You're Chul's family. The purpose of my existence is to get rid of you.
No one asked you to be the female lead in this comic.
Did you think it'd be a happy ending?
What happened to the woman who was here?
This is the last episode of W.