Timing and Subtitles by the Cassiopeia Team @ Viki
Over 10 millions copies sold.Republic of Korea's best webtoon, W.
The protagonist, Kang Cheol, finds out that he is a main character of a webtoon through Oh Yeon Joo.
Kang Cheol, after becoming a murderer and a fugitive, loses the qualification of a main character and is about to cease to exist.
Kang Cheol goes back to W's world and catches the true culprit.
The moment that happy ending is about to come true,
If I think of a webtoon character then could I also summon the comic character backwards into reality?
Aish! Call Han Cheol Ho!
Yeon Joo.
Where is Kang Cheol?
He went back to that place.
Then you're saying that Kang Cheol is not here now.
The true culprit crossed over to the real world and kidnapped Oh Yeon Joo.
Should we go together? To go and find your husband.
In order to catch Kang Cheol, he shoots Oh Yeon Joo.
Episode 14
Hand me the defibrillator.
Yes. How much should I charge it to?
Charge it at 150 joules.
- Is it charged? - Yes, it's charged.
Move away. One, two, shock!
One more time.
It's charged.
Move away! One, two, shock!
It's PEA. (Pulseless electrical activity) Massage more. _____________ Hurry!
Yes.
Gwangmyung-si, Eunha-gu, Chilsan-dong, 63-2, Yoojin Factory
Damn it.
What is that blood stain over there?
Some woman... he shot her.
What do you mean woman? I don't see a woman.
She collapsed though.
Soo Bong!
Yeon Joo.
Please save me.
Park Soo Bong
Please answer the phone. Ah, seriously!
Hello? Hello! Noona! Where are you? Are you alright?
Are you alright? What happened? Noona? Hello?
Is this Soo Bong?
T...Teacher?
What about Yeon Joo?
Teacher, where are you? Where are you?
That... Teacher, where are you going?
Where is Yeon Joo? I have to find Yeon Joo.
Teacher! Teacher! Let's ride in my car.
Teacher, here. Here.
That, Teacher you should ride here.
Teacher, right now, we are going to the real culprit's hideout, right?
Is it alright? Teacher, it will be alright, huh?
Excuse me. Excuse me. I would like to ask something.
Who is it?
Well... perhaps... is there an injured woman?
Ah, that lady? The ambulance took her earlier.
I think everything is alright, Teacher, since they brought her to the hospital right away.
These days the 119 system is very good.
No.
No. It can't be.
They said Kang Cheol went to get her.
Then it will be okay. Kang Cheol... Kang Cheol went...
No. No. It can't...
Emergency
E-excuse me.
Yes?
Perhaps, is a female patient here who has been shot...
Are you Oh Yeon Joo's guardian?
Yes. That's right.
Oh Yeon Joo, where is she?
That...
Intensive Care Unit
Park Soo Bong
Oh Yeon Joo's husband?
Yes.
The surgery went well.
But... prior to the surgery, there was a temporary cardiac arrest caused by excessive hemorrhage while she was in ER.
We've performed CPR for over 30 minutes.
She isn't conscious as of yet.
She is not conscious, her pupils are dilated a bit, and there is no reflex.
Then?
It's... going to be a bit difficult.
Difficult?
- Brain dead?- It's still not a sure state,
but if she continues to be unconscious then...
- Teacher!- Are you alright?
Teacher!
My Yeon Joo. Where is our Yeon Joo?
That... but...
- She is not regaining consciousness?- No.
Oh, no.
What about her husband? I need to investigate him since it's a gunshot.
He's inside.
This way.
Oh my.
Where did they go?
- What?- They suddenly disappeared within a few minutes.
Along with her husband.
We still can't find them.
I also find it so strange.
Ah, look at them.
Why isn't she coming home?
This girl hasn't coming home early lately.
Isn't she dating?
Um... it's her mother.
Teacher, what should I tell her?
Tell her you don't know.
Yes, Mother.
Oh, Soo Bong?
Yes, I'm Soo Bong.
Noona left her cell phone at her dad's workshop.
Why did she leave her phone there?
S...she was hanging out here, and then
she got called into work and went to the hospital.
When she contacts me, I'll tell her to call home.
Ah, I'm not feeling that well. Yes.
Goodbye.
Yeon Joo.
Noona Yeon Joo! Noona Yeon Joo! Noona Yeon Joo...
Hyung Kang.
Please open the door.
Ah, yes.
- Is the writer inside?- Yes.
But, Hyung Kang, what happened to Noona Yeon Joo?
Hyung Kang. Hyung Kang!
Hyung Kang, what about Noona? Noona...
I see you returned.
What about Yeon Joo?
What about Noona?
I took her there.
Why?
What for?
Since they said there was no hope.
If something goes wrong here, there is no turning back.
She stayed at the hospital for 3 days. Even there, they said there was no hope, so I moved her to a hotel.
Because I couldn't explain about the gunshot.
She spent another week there.
She opened her eyes just once.
Yeon Joo.
Can you see me?
Very briefly.
And so?
What about now?
She's dead.
Teacher. Teacher!
Teacher, are you okay?
Ah, Teacher!
Teacher!
You came?
I heard Writer Oh got hospitalized.
- Yes, early in the morning.- Why?
I heard he was under a lot of stress.
Ah, also, I heard he took medication along with alcohol, but he is alright now.
Ah! I feel so uneasy and am going nuts!
- Why?- I...
I submitted some negative comments online, stating that he shouldn't write the webtoon so shabby like that.
I mixed in some cuss words...
Could he have drank after reading those comments and getting stressed?
- That's possible.- Aish!
What's the room number?
Kang Cheol
Yes, Hyung. Yes, he woke up just a while ago.
Ah, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hyung, one moment.
Sir, this is Park Min Soo. I operated on you before. You remember me, right?
Sir, I asked you to stop drinking alcohol at that time, but why did you?
No matter how hard your work is, you really shouldn't do this.
Shouldn't Oh Yeon Joo...
Where did she go? Why isn't she looking after you?
Oh, right, sir. There is something I'm curious about.
Why did Oh Yeon Joo suddenly die?
I mean, she was kind of a useless character, but still...
Her dying that way left me feeling bad.
Of course, a tragically sad ending isn't bad, either.
What's wrong? What's wrong? What are you doing? Sir!
Sir! Ex... Excuse me...
Let go! Let go!
Why are you doing this?
I did it. I was the one who shot.
I shot Yeon Joo. It was me who shot her.
- You did not shoot her.- No.
I did shoot her.
I remember it all.
I shot my daughter.
No. That's not you.
I... can no longer live.
I can not live anymore.
Get yourself together and listen to me!
Do you know why I sought for you? It's because you have something to do.
Don't blame yourself. You did not shoot your daughter but the real culprit did.
But the only one who could save her is only you.
That's why you should get yourself together. You can't break down.
You need to save your daughter!
How could I save her? She's dead.
She did die, but you can save her.
Yeon Joo became a half-way comic character like me when she got married to me.
So she gets hurt and bleeds in the manhwa (comic), and that is why she died after being shot.
But instead, because she became a manhwa character
you can save her by drawing. Just like how I was brought to life after being dead.
Do you understand?
With your drawing, you can make her alive.
That is why, before she died I brought her inside the manhwa world.
It's not the end yet.
I will never give up. I will, with no fail
save her.
How could I draw? It's all crushed.
I broke it with a hammer because that bastard told me to.
That bastard told me so I crushed it all.
There isn't a tablet anymore.
There is.
There is one for sure. Somewhere.
Where did he go?
That... but why did he suddenly go out? What did you say?
Well, I didn't say anything much.
I just asked something about the manhwa
and when I asked why Oh Yeon Joo died, and he just suddenly...
Why? What's wrong?
Sheesh! Why would you ask that? Why!
There are other things to ask! Why did you ask that to a patient! Are you in your right mind?
As a doctor, you have no mannerism, and can't even get a hint about the situation!
Why did you ask that kind of thing! Why!
Do you have any thoughts or not! Oh, Teacher.
- Call a nurse. - Please call a nurse.
Teacher. Teacher. Teacher, are you alright? Teacher!
What is this? Did I do something so wrong?
Can't I ask why a manhwa character died?
What should I do? I think I'm hurt.
I will be going back now.
Please take care of him.
You probably don't know what Oh Yeon Joo means to me.
Yeon Joo is my only family.
Not the fake family that you made but a true family that has substance.
Not with those fabricated memories but actual memories that we shared together.
Not a predetermined fate but a fate that I chose myself.
For the first time, only with my own will.
That's why, I can't give up.
Yeon Joo... is the proof that I'm human, just like you and her
That I am a human being.
That's why I will surely save your daughter and be happy together.
This time I won't back up.
Nobody can make me despair.
I will come from behind and win for sure. And the ending will be...
a happy ending no matter what.
Oh right, now your life is important to me too.
Not as the god who made me but as the father of my wife.
You are already my family.
You might not acknowledge it, but that's how it is to me.
That's why, don't do things like what you did earlier, please! Okay?
Arrogant punk.
Hyung.
Please be careful.
Honestly, I'm going crazy.
Don't cry and wait. I might call for help.
To me? What?
I don't know yet, either.
Be careful, okay?
How could there be another one?
Until now, I only used one tablet.
There must be a replacement.
If not, there's no way the real culprit would have broken it.
That is the most important thing to him
Hey, draw that first.
Your tablet.
He just had it crushed so that we could never use it.
There must be a copy drawn somewhere in the manhwa.
If not, he wouldn't have recklessly disposed of it.
Don't you remember?
I put it in the trunk.
Trunk of the car?
When the police looked for evidence, there was no tablet.
- Han Cheol Ho.- Han Cheol Ho.
This is used by illustrators.
It's used for drawing.
Drawing?
Yes. If it's this kind, it's one that a professional would use.
How do you do it?
With this, you can just draw like with a pencil.
This is the electronic pen.
Why would he have something like this in his trunk? It's not even a weapon.
- Pardon?- Nothing.
Assemblyman, Assemblymen Park is calling and asking when you are coming.
- Tell him I will be there soon.- Yes.
Hello? Yes.
Turn it off for now.
But the copy will have the same functionality?
We won't know. We need to use it to know what's different.
But still, we have to find it.
First, we must.
It's not the same one. It's a trap!
Hey, Kang Cheol.
Is this what you are looking for?
Wow! It's been a really long time for us to be meeting like this again, isn't it?
Ever since Kang Cheol became CEO Kang Cheol, I couldn't touch you at all.
But now,
you are dead. You've put up a show on your own that you are dead.
So even if you die here again,
no one will say anything. You're already dead.
Even if I kill you here right now,
I won't be found guilty of anything.
Huh?! You dug your grave, jerk! Do you get it?!
Does it still feel foggy? Are you still out of it?
Hey.
Aren't you curious where I got that injection?
It's fascinating, right?
How can there be something like that?
For now, turn it off.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Tell him to put the car back in. I'm going to take a look at this first before leaving.
Yes.
What is this, eh?
This jerk. He really is a nut job!
As he draws, he is having fantasies.
Were you trying to make a terrorist group or something, Kang Cheol?
What is this?
Revolver
What the-
Not just revolvers. There are all kinds of medications!
Natrium Amytal. Scopolamine, Sodium Pentothal.
Amphetamin, Mescaline. There!
Which injection should I give you? What do you want?
Sodium?
Sodium Pentothal
Timing and Subtitles by the Cassiopeia Team @ Viki
My CEO Kang Cheol.
In case you die of drug overdose,
I let you live.
You were appearing and disappearing suddenly, acting like Hong Gil Dong (Legendary fictional hero).
Now that you are drugged up, even that must be hard, too.
Isn't it a type of story that would come out in a manhwa or something?
If you press "Enter," it appears; if you press 'Delete," it disappears again.
Why you were in a gun fight against Han Sang Hoon,
now I understand.
But,
what I'm really curious about is,
what on earth is this? This!
From now, these are the questions you have to answer.
Where did Han Sang Hoon get that and what is your relationship with him?
How did you know I have that?
Who is the original owner of that thing?
Who is the woman who disappears after getting shot at the scene?
How can you come into my office so easily?
Let's start.
This is the price for tormenting me for the past 10 years.
Ah, this bastard.
Hey. Hey, you won't talk? Huh?
Hey! Huh?
Hey!
- Yes.- Why aren't you coming?
Ah, I have something to take care of.
Yes, I'll be right there.
That's right. Since you were young,
you were pretty good at keeping your mouth shut, weren't you?
But it will be a bit different this time. You should know,
what is in here, too.
You'd better be prepared.
Hospital.
What?
Say that again. What did you say?
I have to take it to the hospital.
What about the hospital? Say it louder.
Why isn't he contacting me again?
Aish, I should have quit.
It's uploaded! It's uploaded again!
Please. Please, please, please.
W Oh Seung Moo
Secret of the Tablet
Please.
Aish! I told him to be careful! Ah!
So you are telling me
to believe what you said.
It's true.
- Go inside and watch over him.- Yes.
Oh, he is a dead guy already.
It doesn't matter if he dies, so don't even give him a sip of water.
I understand.
It's me.
Tell him that I have and urgent matter to take care of so I have to stop by somewhere.
What time is it right now?
What?
Just tell me what time it is. What time is it?
It's 2:30.
2:30?
Then, thirty minutes have passed.
It's about time for it to arrive.
What?
Park Soo Bong, material is going there.
Please take good care of it.
What are you saying now?
To be continued
Park Soo Bong, material is going there.
What is this? My name?
Is he calling out to me?
Don't cry and wait. I might send out an SOS.
Is this it? Is this it?
You are going to carry that? It's heavy. Let me carry it.
That's fine. Lead the way.
Yes.
Teacher! Teacher!
Teacher!
W..webtoon has been uploaded.
What?
Did something go wrong? To him, too?
I'm not sure whether it went wrong or not.
Hyung is almost dying.
Teacher, look at this.
He sent me a message.
He put this message for me to see, right? He said the material is coming here.
What could the material be? What is the material?
Could it be the tablet? Right?
Which floor is the hospital room on?
8th floor. Internal Medicine department. #810.
Hospital.
Say that again. What did you say?
I have to take that there.
Take what?
That? Why?
There's someone I need to save.
Who?
So this is what you are saying now.
The woman who disappeared after Han Sang Hoon shot her,
is Oh Yeon Joo, your wife.
So that's why you killed Han Sang Hoon.
Your wife, who was brain-dead,
stayed at your penthouse,
and died not long ago.
That's right.
She's dead.
But?
If I have that, I can save her.
You saw what that thing can do.
That's why I came to get it.
You can revive her again?
If you just press "Enter," a dead person will come back to be living again?
You have to draw it.
You have to draw it?
The owner of the tablet has to draw it.
That's why I was going to take it to the hospital.
The owner is in the hospital.
Crazy bastard! What kind of Manhwa-like fabrication are you saying?
You can resurrect a person by drawing?
What you saw is not Manhwa-like,
And then?
Continue.
Bring some more guys. There is something I need to double check.
I understand.
What are you guys? Without permission!
We got Mr. Kang Cheol's permission. Let us go in for a little.
What are you talking about? What do you mean Kang Cheol?
How dare you selling deceased CEO Kang?
We have rented this for our company VIP's use. With whose permission are you coming in?
Ah, hello? Seo Do Yeon keeps blocking us.
Yes.
Please talk to Mr. Kang Cheol.
Hello?
Hyung. Let them in.
Are you crazy? What are you trying to do?
Let them check.
- Is he really dead?- Yes.
I am certain that he just died. And gunshot is correct, too.
I got it. Withdraw for now.
How should I accept this situation now?
You can confirm.
How?
If he draws and my wife resurrects, is there any clearer proof than that?
It has the answers to all your questions.
Sungjin Hospital Internal Medicine Ward #810
His name is Oh Seong Moo.
2:30.
Then, thirty minutes have passed.
It's about time for it to arrive.
What?
Mr. Park Soo Bong, the thing is going that way. Take good care of it.
To be continued
What was that!
What is this?
It's here. #810.
#810. Patient: Yoon Sun Ae
What? This isn't Oh Seong Moo.
Excuse me.
Assemblyman, Han Cheol Ho!
You've been working hard.
By any chance, is there another patient in this room, by the name of Oh Seong Moo?
Ah, this is a 1 person room.
- Should I help you?- No, no, no.
I must have gotten the wrong room. Go ahead and work.
Why would he lie like this, when it will be caught so quickly?
Third hypothesis.
Since I am in the real world, I can summon webtoon characters, according to my will.
At this time,
I am summoning Han Cheol Ho to the real world.
It must be the tablet, right?
The material... But how will it come here?
What is this?
Teacher, it's Han Cheol...
Perhaps, are you Oh Seong Moo?
Yes, that's me.
You're saying you're Oh Seong Moo?
But you weren't here just a minute ago.
Wait a minute.
But why do you look exactly like Han Sang Ho?
You...
Perhaps, you are Han Sang Ho, right?!
How did you...?
What are you, bastard? What are you?
What kind of bastard are you?!
What are you, bastard!
- Teacher!- What are you?
Teacher... How could Han Cheol Ho bring it personally? He isn't a delivery person!
This is... a real table, right?
So there was a copy. But do you think it will function again, Teacher?
Teacher. Han Cheol Ho... Han Cheol Ho...
Han Cheol Ho went back.
Damn!
Ah, I'm tired. You have the key, right?
Yeah.
That scared me! What is that?
- Hey, what do we do? What the heck?- What do we do?
Excuse me. Hey, come to your senses.
Are you okay? Let's untie him first.
Yeah.
Gather in the hotel for now. There is something I need to explain to you guys.
CEO Kang is in danger. The truth is that CEO Kang--
Miss Oh Yeon Joo?
Nurse. Nurse!
To be continued
How long has it been?
It's been about twenty minutes.
- Twenty minutes?- Yes.
Oh, yes.
- Hello?- Soo Bong.
Noona?
It's me. What happened?
N-Noona?! Noona, Noona Yeon Joo? Are you really Noona Yeon Joo?
But, this is imposs... Noona, is it really you?
Yeah, I'm alive. I guess I survived.
But, where are you? Where are you right now, Noona?
I...
I'm in the hotel right now. I just came back so suddenly.
Are you okay? You're fine? You can talk?
Oh, you're talking right now. Well, nothing's strange? You can move all your fingers and toes?
And you can remember everything? What about the place you got shot?
I'm not hurt.
I'm totally fine.
Ah, you really make people worry!
How did I survive?
Ah, really! Teacher! Teacher's drawings!
Dad came back?
Of course!
- But, he's not answering my calls.- Huh?
Ah, he should be in the hotel right now. He kept waiting for the webtoon to appear.
W
If he saw the webtoon, he'll come to find you soon. I'm looking for Hyung Cheol right now.
Where?
Well, the place Hyung Cheol was tortured.
What do you mean tortured?
I came here to find him but he's not here right now.
- Hey.- Hey, hey, wait, wait.
Aigoo.
Hey, we should call the ambulance, right? Go tell the boss.
I got it.
What?
- Taxi...- Huh?
Please call a taxi for me. I need to go to the hotel.
But, I think you should go to the hospital.
I mean...
They said that they were worried so they called an ambulance, but he was gone by the time they arrived.
But, he would've went back to you, right?
Is he really hurt?
I understand. What about Dad? Is Dad okay?
A dead person was the worry! Why are yo--
Who is worrying about who right now?
I got it.
No, I'll look at the comic to see what happened.
That'll be faster.
Oh, okay.
I used the phone well.
Yes.
By any chance, can I use the internet for a moment?
There's someone I need to save.
Timing and Subtitles by the Cassiopeia Team @ Viki
♫ Whether you will continue to love me  ♫
♫ and I will live with you ♫
♫ We will hold on to the belief that
Why isn't he coming?
♫ love is destiny ♫
♫ Day after day while longing for you, I cry ♫
♫ I wander around searching for you  ♫
♫ Today, too, I'm waiting for you ♫
♫ Actually, without you  ♫
♫ I can't do anything except cry again ♫
Final Episode
♫ Now without you, each day is a day without meaning ♫
♫ I won't let go of you again ♫
♫ Let's not break up again ♫
♫  Is the person whom I have fallen for really you? Am I, who is wanting you, the real me? ♫
♫  In this moment, when we are holding hands together, there is no sense of comfort that can embrace us warmly  ♫
[W Preview]We are only free after the end.
Why are you appearing now?
Before the final episode ends, we cannot escape this world.
Hurry up, you bastards! Let me go!
I got a hostage, so I can live, too. Come here.
Why are you alive? I clearly shot you! Why are you alive?!
The police are coming right now. They will find the house soon.
Now we must decide. On the ending.