(W by Oh Seong Moo)
Kang Chul gets attacked at a hotel rooftop.
A strange woman saves him after appearing shortly after.
Wake up! Hey!
She leaves a business card with a name Oh Yeon Joo and disappears.
Yeon Joo, where are you right now?
Because of a nurse instigated by an unidentified person,
Kang Chul is put in danger once again.
- Please let me in.
-  No, you are not allowed.
Oh, no. Please.
- Yeon Joo suddenly appears to help.
-  Are you okay?
We finally meet each other.
He avoids death once again.
Yeon Joo keeps appearing in his life.
Why don't you...
- Oh, my.
-  Gosh.
Kang Chul senses that...
she holds the key to his life.
I drew it.
It's my artwork.
He's a monster.
I created a monster.
So I decided to judge him.
I should've finished his life a long time ago.
Who...
are you?
(Episode 3)
- Yeon Joo.
-  Hey.
- Dad is in his room, right?
-  He went out.
Where did he go again?
I don't know. He packed his things and went out. Even his computer.
He even kicked us out. He told us to go home.
I sent Seon Mi and Yoon Hee home.
I can't stop thinking that it's strange.
I told you that Chul is going to die.
I think that's why Mr Oh kicked us out.
That means that woman...
is you. It should be you.
I told you that Chul was going to die,
so you went into the webtoon, saved his life and got out.
Yes. But it just doesn't make any sense.
It doesn't make sense, but it actually does.
It doesn't make any sense, but it actually does.
It's...
Yeon Joo, your dress...
Soo Bong. Listen to me carefully.
Do you know how much this dress is?
It's over 3,000 dollars.
What about these shoes?
Do you think I would buy all these with my own money?
That's right.
Who among my friends would buy...
this expensive dress to me with no problem?
Is it...
Seok Beom?
Professor Park?
Your father?
Are you saying it's Chul?
Do you believe me now?
Do you?
- Gosh, Soo Bong.
-  Don't come any closer.
What's wrong?
- Get up now.
-  Don't come closer!
Still, it doesn't make sense.
- How can this be happening?
-  Stop talking.
I will. How did you go into the webtoon?
Can you go in whenever you like? Can I go in, too?
I don't know why I keep going inside it.
I suddenly found myself in the webtoon.
Anyhow, a few things became clear.
Everything in that world revolves around Chul.
I don't appear on the cartoon unless I get involved with Chul.
The time I do my own things and my thoughts...
don't count. It all gets edited out.
Chul is the main character and I'm just a supporting role.
Also, time centres around Chul, too.
It skips the time when Chul isn't doing anything.
That's why two months passed in an instant.
Less than five minutes in this world...
can be as long as two months over there.
It can even be 2 years or 20 years.
How is it possible?
Think about it.
This webtoon has been published serially for seven years.
During those 7 years, 15 years have passed in Chul's life.
It makes sense that time passes faster in it.
It only shows important incidents.
Also, whether I can come back or not depends on Chul.
An ending scene must include a change in Chul's mind.
That's how an episode ends.
I can only come back when the episode ends. That's why...
- I did it.
-  Did what?
You mean the kiss?
Did you really kiss Chul?
I didn't have a choice. I had to surprise him or something.
I needed an ending scene.
No way. You did it on purpose.
Everyone knows you're a fan of Chul.
I didn't do it on purpose!
Was it good?
What?
I mean...
he's a cartoon character. He's not real person.
How was the touch of his lips?
How did you feel when you kissed him?
I was in a hurry. I didn't feel anything.
He's not a cartoon character.
He is a human.
He's not different from us.
I see. You were in a hurry.
Tell me this. Is he handsome?
He is.
How about So Hee? Did you see her, too?
Sure, I did.
- Is she really glamorous?
-  Goodness.
Why are all men so crazy about women's chest?
I'm not crazy about it.
Gosh, you're driving me crazy. Now, it sounds so real.
It is real.
You'll see the reason why I tried to save him soon.
He's an actual human just like us.
How can I watch him die?
Besides, I'm a doctor.
Right. Mr Oh said he will end it today.
End what?
He said today's episode will be the last one.
He said he will start over today's episode. He'll probably kill Chul.
He must've left because he didn't want to be disturbed.
Is he going to kill Chul again?
I should've finished his life a long time ago.
Right there at the Han River Bridge.
He'll come back when he's finished. Even if you find him...
Soo Bong, do you remember how Chul almost threw himself from a bridge?
In what year was that story published?
It was in the 5th book. So it must be 2009.
In 2009?
(2012 Reference Documents for W)
(2011 Reference Documents for W)
(2009 Reference Documents for W)
(Jeon Seung Min, the star of Athens Olympics)
(Suicides on Han River Bridge)
(Yeon Joo left me. I'm all alone now.)
Yeon Joo left me.
I'm all alone now.
Let's go.
I'm left alone in this house.
I no longer have any family.
I lost my will to do anything.
I can't even draw a single cut.
How will I continue my work?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
(The real reason why people die if they fall off a bridge)
(I'm sorry, but I need to end it here.)
But I need to end it here.
Was Chul supposed to die here?
What?
Goodbye.
Hello? Gosh.
It's all right.
I'll send it soon.
It's all done,
but I fell asleep.
Actually,
I should stop here for now.
It's due to a personal reason.
I already have the ending.
It's strange.
I ended it last night with him in the water.
However, Kang Chul is still alive.
He was holding on with one hand...
all night long.
Was I drunk?
Did I think the character was dead without actually drawing it?
However,
this may be a start...
to find strength again.
That's why...
I decided to save Chul.
(2010 Reference Documents for W)
The fact that a joint representative of JN Global...
is an Olympics athlete Kang Chul has become an issue.
After his court judgement in 2007, it was his first time...
appearing in public.
JN Global, an electronic commerce company,
went public last year and is maintaining its market price...
- Hey, did you wait a long time?
-  Yes.
What if I buy this broadcasting station?
What did you say?
Now that I've earned money, I should catch him.
You said money and labour force were the issues.
Using a private agency is illegal. I can't use national institutions.
I thought I could buy this broadcasting station.
I can find the culprit by making a crime-solving programme.
The staff should only be composed of Korea's best professionals.
I'll hire only the best state attorneys and prosecutors.
I'll provide all the money.
You can be the supervisor.
I already decided the name of the channel to be W.
W stands for who and why.
The purpose is to find out who committed the crime and why.
Who killed my family...
and why did they do it?
I should find that out now.
I seem to be possessed.
I respect you, Sir.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you so much.
-  Thank you!
Hello. I'm a huge fan of W!
Thank you.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
My gosh!
Mr Oh, I respect you very much.
- Please accept me as your student.
-  Please stand up.
- Thank you.
-  Things are working out so well...
- that I can't even believe it.
-  Oh my gosh!
Do you enjoy reading webtoon?
There's a webtoon that's lauded...
to have changed the dynamics of Korean media contents.
He's become popular recently.
A webtoon artist of W,
Oh Seong Moo is with us today. Hello.
Hello.
I've wanted to meet you. I finally get to meet you today.
- It's nice to meet you.
-  Me, too.
I'm a big fan of yours.
Thank you.
How do you feel these days? Does the popularity of W...
feel real to you?
I'm not sure.
As I only work at my desk,
I'm very busy to meet the deadline.
Now that I'm sitting here,
- it seems more real.
-  I see.
There's "Sherlock Holmes" in London...
I definitely succeeded.
Soo Seon must regret that she left me.
(Gosh, I lost him.)
Strange things keep happening these days.
My drawing doesn't turn out the way I want.
It feels as if Kang Chul is rejecting...
the story that I'm coming up with.
(Where are you going?)
Is it because of the alcohol?
It happened again.
I woke up in the morning and saw a scene I didn't draw.
Have I lost my mind?
He's alive.
I can definitely feel it, but how...
How is he alive?
(2015 Reference Documents for W)
(Monster)
(I'd rather slaughter than be slaughtered.)
Monster.
He's a monster.
He'll kill me one day.
I'd rather slaughter than be slaughtered.
No.
I should have killed him a long time ago.
Everything went wrong...
from Han River.
- Which medicine is that?
-  I have a headache.
You probably caught a cold...
by wearing only a dress on a rainy day.
- I know.
-  Why did you go out so late?
No one cares.
I'm leaving.
Goodness, what on earth is this?
Gosh.
Why with Yeon Joo? Gosh.
What kind of rubbish is this?
The door is closing.
I felt some negative energy just now.
Goodness.
- What on earth?
-  Kang Chul kissed her.
Goodness.
What's with this woman? I hate her.
Everyone in the country is watching it.
Soo Bong, I just got off work. How's Dad?
He's not home yet.
No matter how much I think about it,
it's still hard to believe.
How could this happen?
This is what I don't understand.
Let's say that you went inside because of Kang Chul at first,
but why did it happen again?
I don't know, either.
You said you need an ending scene to get out.
It means there is a rule for entering it as well.
Then why is it only you?
Isn't that the biggest problem?
What if you are dragged into the webtoon suddenly?
What will you do then?
How do you know what would happen if you get involved with Chul?
Yeon Joo.
Hello? Yeon Joo, are you listening to me?
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Yeon Joo.
Hello?
Who are you?
I found this mobile phone at a bus station.
Where is the owner?
I only found this mobile phone and a bag.
Oh, no.
I am sorry, but can you wait for me there? I'll be right there.
Yes. Okay.
My mouth always causes problem.
Oh, gosh.
You're here. This way, please.
I didn't hear the details on the phone.
What exactly happened?
Mr Kang told me to make sure nobody speaks about it.
Anyone who talks about it will get fired,
so you don't have to worry about it.
But we have no right to stop our customers.
We got the contact number of the person who recorded the video.
You should meet the customer and settle things yourself.
What is the video about?
It's...
It seems like he had an argument...
with a lady he came with.
An argument?
I don't know what exactly happened.
Why don't you...
That lady suddenly got upset and slapped his face.
And they somehow became fine again...
and started to kiss.
Kiss?
And they went inside the fitting room together.
They locked the door, too.
Mr Kang came out alone after a long time.
But that's not what he wanted to hide.
He wanted to hide the fact that she disappeared.
She disappeared?
Yes. They went in together,
but only Mr Kang came out. She disappeared.
I don't understand what you're talking right now.
I don't understand it, either.
But everyone says the same thing.
Where is the fitting room?
It's over there.
No, it was the other door.
There's nowhere to leave. How did she manage to disappear?
- Well...
-  Excuse me?
Oh, my!
Hello?
I'm at the store right now.
Did you meet the manager?
Yeon Joo is here.
- What?
-  She's here.
Inside the fitting room.
What happened?
That's what I want to ask. What happened?
She was in there. Why did you say she disappeared?
Yeon Joo.
She won't wake up.
Is it the rescue centre?
- We have a patient here.
-  Don't call an ambulance.
- What?
-  Hang up the phone.
What are you trying to do?
Where are you going?
She can't go to a hospital. I'm taking her to a hotel.
How will you take the responsibility?
Please send over Doctor Yoon.
I'll go there first. Wrap up and come to the hotel.
What?
Why am I here again?
I'm curious, too. Why did you come back?
I don't know, either.
Sir.
What's going on?
Who is she?
You're here.
- Where's Doctor Yoon?
-  He's not here yet.
Mr Kang!
Detective Park is here.
Hello.
Hello. What brings you here?
I came because of the witness, Oh Yeon Joo.
I see. You haven't found her yet?
She's really strange.
How did she manage to avoid all the surveillance cameras?
You don't have to try too hard.
She's not a criminal. It's okay if you can't find her.
What are you talking about? We are going to find her.
By the way...
Something happened.
I will go put her in bed.
You don't have to see us out.
We will get going then.
What? Isn't she Yeon Joo?
What happened?
Finally, she's in my arms.
What?
She's the key to my life.
By the way, is she really pretty?
Is she pretty?
What?
Why does everyone say that she's beautiful?
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
I feel dizzy.
You're probably still drunk from the medicine.
You're not dying, so don't worry.
Where am I?
It's my room. It's where I stay.
The penthouse?
How do you know that?
You live at the hotel penthouse. It's on the 33th, the top floor.
You really know everything about me.
I know everything.
What else do you know?
I know that your family...
suddenly got killed in your house and it traumatised you.
That's why you live in hotels without having your own house.
That's interesting.
What else do you know?
You keep a gun underneath your pillow.
You always keep it there even though it's illegal.
You can't sleep without it.
How do you know that?
I saw it.
Where did you see it?
That was the saddest scene.
The Han River Bridge.
I cried as well at the time.
I was afraid...
Chul would really kill himself.
Die!
Die! Die!
You were supposed to guard the door.
- We were told to come downstairs.
-  By whom?
The message was from Do Yoon's phone,
but he said he didn't send it.
I will...
find you soon.
Wait for it.
Where am I?
Is this Chul's room?
It is his room. This is his bed and that is... Oh my gosh.
Did I get dragged in here again? Why?
Why? How?
You're here.
- Yes.
-  How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
A nurse checked on you. She said you're all fine.
- You'll be just fine.
-  Why did she say I fainted?
- She said it's from overwork.
-  Overwork?
A severe exhaustion put a lot of strain on your body.
A severe exhaustion?
You were in bed for two days.
Maybe you overstrained yourself.
What?
Well... Maybe I did.
Why don't you eat lunch with President Kang? He'll be back soon.
- Will he come back here?
-  Yes.
I prepared some clothes you can change into in the bathroom.
- I see.
-  Excuse me.
What should I do?
What am I supposed to do now? My goodness.
It's huge.
It's see-through.
Gosh.
Isn't that the biggest problem?
How do you know what would happen if you get involved with Chul?
What if you are dragged into the webtoon suddenly?
Gosh. Wait a minute.
I found it.
- Did you say she's alone?
-  She's in the shower.
I told you not to leave her alone when she wakes up.
- I can't go in there with her.
-  My gosh.
What should I do?
Which one should I pick?
She can't run away from here. This is on the 33rd floor.
Goodness.
I heard she's awake.
- Yes. You can see her later.
-  Why? What is she doing now?
She's having an honest talk with Chul.
In the bathroom?
Here you go again, Yeon Joo.
What is this now?
It's 11am and you just woke up. What are you trying to do here?
It's nothing.
- Excuse me?
-  It's nothing.
You always do things and say it's nothing.
Don't come near me.
Stop. I'll shoot you if you don't.
Gosh. You're such an unpredictable woman.
You suddenly showed up,
slapped me in the face, kissed me,
disappeared and showed up again.
Now, you suddenly take your clothes off...
and point a gun at me.
I know you don't understand me. I'd do the same if I were you.
There is a reason why I'm doing this.
- What reason?
-  Don't move.
I'm really going to shoot you. I'm not kidding.
- Go ahead then.
-  I'm serious.
It's dangerous!
Why do you worry when you're going to kill me?
I said I will shoot you!
You have to have bullets. Don't you know that?
I wanted to see...
what you'd do when you know that I keep a gun under my pillow.
Why are you doing this?
I don't like doing this, so let's compromise by talking.
I have about 100 questions,
but I'll let you live if you answer the first question.
How did you disappear that day?
I have to report you to the police if you don't answer.
How cruel!
You said that I saved your life.
Certainly, you did. That's why I let you go before.
Aren't you the one who broke the promise?
You disappeared without answering any of my questions.
You must keep the promise now.
I waited for two months like a gentleman.
Do you agree?
How did you disappear?
There must have been a way.
I'll have to report you to the police if you don't answer.
If you can't answer it, here's my next question.
Why did you kiss me after hitting me that day?
I'll wait since we still have a lot of time.
I did that so I could disappear.
What did you say?
Do what?
I kissed you.
Kiss.
Yes.
You kissed me so you could disappear.
I didn't imagine such an answer.
Did you disappear because you kissed me that day?
Is it the way?
It's true,
so please stop it and let me go.
- Is that so?
-  Yes.
Why are you still here?
You're still here.
Just kissing won't make me disappear.
There has to be a change in emotions.
I was talking about that kind of kiss.
Emotions?
I didn't like it very much then.
You may not have liked it, but you were surprised.
Yes, I was.
That's what I mean. There was some kind of change in your emotions.
That's the rule.
You seem surprised. You're blushing.
I'm talking about you.
- What do you mean?
-  Your change of emotions counts.
What kind of rule is that?
Why are my emotions important?
It's because you're the main character.
The main character?
For what?
What you just did can be considered sexual assault.
I'm going to sue you.
You're the one who committed sexual assault.
On top of that, you slapped me.
Besides, I was doing a scientific experiment...
to prove the logic of your statement.
What you're saying now...
is that you can only disappear when there's a change of...
emotions in me.
Is that correct?
- Yes.
-  Is that why you slapped me?
Did you fire the gun and took off that gown to surprise me?
That's right.
It's very peculiar.
I thought you'd say it was teleporting.
Still, it doesn't seem like a lie...
since you're still here even when you had a chance to disappear.
I'm not lying.
Just because it's not a lie doesn't mean it's true.
You're only talking about what happened...
without the important context.
There must be something you're hiding.
There must be a context which explains why you can disappear...
only when there's been a change of emotions in me.
You must tell me.
I don't know any more than that.
How could you not know?
Answer in the count of 10.
One.
- Two.
-  I said I don't know.
Three.
- Four.
-  Don't scare me.
You won't even fire.
Five.
What's going on?
Get out.
What are you doing?
I'm investigating instead of the police...
because you talk too much.
However, Yeon Joo keeps teasing me...
instead of telling the truth.
Are you all right?
- Stop it.
-  Get out.
- Stop it. She's still a patient.
-  Get out!
This is how you fire a gun.
This is very important with my life on the line.
It doesn't matter even though you saved my life.
You were a saviour, but you're also very dangerous.
That's why I'm going to shoot if you don't answer.
I counted up to five.
Six.
Seven.
How important is the secret that you can't tell even at gunpoint?
You won't shoot me.
Eight.
How can you be sure?
You...
wouldn't do that.
Nine.
I thought you knew everything about me,
but you're wrong about certain things.
I can do it.
No way.
Will you not answer me?
Ten.
(W)
Were you surprised?
You didn't know the power you had.
What happened?
Did you shoot her?
Did you?
She passed out because she was shocked. Move her to a room.
Have you lost your mind? What have you done?
I was only trying to scare her.
You've completely lost your mind.
Please come now.
The patient became unconscious again.
Something...
shocking happened.
Yes, please come now.
- Could you bring us some water?
-  Okay.
Did he lose his mind after being in the hospital for too long?
He's odd, but she's very odd, too.
They're both odd.
Did you call the nurse?
I said to hand her over to the police.
Did you bring her to act like a hoodlum? Are you a gang or what?
Why would you threaten a woman with a gun?
Isn't an investigation for truth what you wanted?
Report her to the police now.
Not to the police.
I can't bear to watch it.
Report her to the police first. If they can't solve it,
we can investigate then. That's the order of things.
Why do you make things complicated?
You don't know what you're getting yourself into.
I told you not to.
It will never be solved once the police get involved.
I told you. Yeon Joo is the key to my life.
Please change my flight to night schedule. I'm dropping by Busan.
Is she awake?
How is she?
I gave her a tranquilliser, and her blood pressure is normal.
- Please give us some minutes.
-  Sure.
Are you upset?
Did you ask if I'm upset?
That's not the right expression.
You shot me with the gun.
I'm sorry for surprising you.
Actually, I knew that a gunshot wouldn't kill you.
Why don't you know that?
You're invincible, Yeon Joo.
You can never die.
You really didn't know that?
How do you know that?
If you answer my question, I'll tell you.
Since we had already seen it,
let's admit that you are not an ordinary person.
You're perhaps from another world.
From another world that I don't know about.
You work as a cardiothoracic surgery resident there.
Right?
(Cardiothoracic surgery resident, Oh Yeon Joo)
Where is that?
Anyway, I'm relieved.
I checked with my eyes that you can't disappear like last time.
If everything is up to me,
that means there is no way you can escape.
You know me well, don't you?
Once I make my mind, I never get swayed.
That's my talent.
I even won a gold medal with that, too.
So now, you can't go back...
until you answer all my questions.
Stay here with me.
Since you saved my life,
I will protect you from the police and the media.
You can stay here as long as you like.
If you want to go back, you just have to answer my questions.
It seems like you have a lot of surprising things to tell me.
If you say the truth and surprise me, you get to go back.
I'll be able to find the answers I want then.
What do you think? It's a fair deal, isn't it?
Surprise me if you want to go back.
What kind of world is the world you live in?
You said you know and saw everything about me.
Where did you see me?
Is it hard to answer?
It's hard.
Then let's stay here together. I don't mind.
We have plenty of time.
You want me...
- to live here?
-  If not here,
where would you go?
I think you have nowhere to go.
We're ready.
I planned to have lunch together before going on a business trip.
But something came up in Busan. Let's eat when I'm back.
I'll be back on Friday. My secretary will assist you in the meantime.
Right.
It's the mobile phone you threw last time. Call me if anything happens.
I want to reconcile with you. I'm sorry for what I did a while ago.
I sincerely apologise.
Rest well.
I love you.
Never mind.
Right.
You must've thought I'd be really surprised to see you in nude.
You thought my heart would beat fast and my eyes would go blind?
No. I just took a chance.
- Do you know you're unbelievable?
-  I know that.
Take care.
Let's go.
- What is it really?
-  What?
You said she's not beautiful at all,
but you act like you're in love.
She'd been naked.
She kissed you and confessed her love. She even slapped you.
All that looks like a love fight.
And what? Are you going to stay here together?
That's like a couple moving in together.
- That's right.
-  Anyone would think that.
- Right.
-  You're so cool about it.
It's complicated. Think however you want.
Wait.
What is it?
You said you are going somewhere.
I'm stopping by Busan and going to New York. Why?
Be careful.
Am I going to die on the way?
Will the train derail? Or will the aeroplane get hijacked?
I don't know. I was just worried.
You are not sure how I'm going to die this time.
When I'm here, I don't know things, either.
So I can't help you.
You can know from there then?
Yes.
I'm even more curious about you now.
You never answer. Why are you worried that I might die?
I am one of those people...
who want your life to be a happy ending.
I am your fan. Really.
Are you saying I'm going to be unfortunate if I hear the answer?
Perhaps.
That's why I can't answer.
Besides, you are my first patient...
I saved alone.
Is that right? I'm honoured.
- You are my second patient, too.
-  I'm even more honoured.
So...
always be careful.
I will do that.
I guess you will answer this question.
How old are you?
I'm 30.
We're the same age. Are you married?
No.
That's good.
I found out why I kept dragged here...
only after a while.
It was because this man...
had said that I was the key to his life.
At that moment,
the heroine of this webtoon changed.
From Yoon So Hee...
to Oh Yeon Joo.
(W)
I'm sure Yeon Joo is the key to my life.
She's the only one who can open the door to the secrets.
Would you like to go and drink a glass of wine with me?
Excuse me.
You are the doctor from the rooftop.
What do I do? I can't get caught by the police.
Please reveal your identity.
Even if I want to, I have no identity to reveal.
If she's an innocent citizen, why can't she identify herself?
They're convinced that you are the criminal.
You need to answer my question now.
- You're going to regret this.
-  I won't.
What do you mean by the world I live in?
The world inside a webtoon.