That day, at the Ohsung villa, near the location where Food Talk took place,
Jo Ye Ryeong and Yoo Tae Oh had a secret affair, right?
Yes.
And the victim Min Na recorded that.
Yes. Things got out of hand trying to retrieve that video clip.
Bonjour!
Wow, what's this? It's such an interesting combination.
Hey, Yoo Tae Oh, you shouldn't be like that as a man. Huh?
You're going to get it from me.
Cha Geum Joo, leave that here and go home safely.
Having someone order me around, I don't like that particularly.
Cha Geum Joo...
While I was following you around,
I started liking you.
Ah, well... I'm talking as in liking you as a person.
Then, get lost quietly.
Right now, I'm holding onto an important voice recording and need to go to the prosecutor's office.
- Hey, look. You—- What are you so curious about?
I'm a janitor.
Cha Geum Joo, stop right there.
If you don't bring that to me, you'll surely die.
Go ahead and shoot me.
This is my life to me.
Oh, no. I don't have much patience.
One, two.
What's that sound?
Perhaps... Lawyer Cha?
Aish, really.
- It sounded like a gun shot just now.- We heard it too.
Liking someone is liking, but you need to listen.
I'll go alone through the side road. Go and find Attorney Cha.
Lawyer Cha!
We need to quickly call 119.
We have a first-aid patient!
- Attorney Cha...  - We're under the Han River bridge.
That day, at the Ohsung villa, near the location where Food Talk took place,
Jo Ye Ryeong and Yoo Tae Oh had a secret affair, right?
Yes. Things got out of hand
trying to retrieve that video clip.
Save me. I'll do anything!
I can tell my manager to bring a billion dollars right now!
Hey, I have more money than you.
Hey, but have a go at this.
Do you think I'll save you or kill you?
Hm?
Woman With a Suitcase
Episode 14  When losers unite...
Subtitles brought to you by The Feisty Team @ Viki
Lawyer Cha!
What brings you to Busan?
To be honest, I wanted to ask you a few things.
While Busan police were investigating drug dealers,
they arrested someone who said he was the culprit behind the homeless girl incident,
but they just let him go due to lack of evidence.
Ah, that?
I was curious why it had to wrap up that way.
That's
a complicated question.
Did the Head Prosecutor order that? To let him go?
Geum Joo, thank you.
I knew this was going to happen.
Mr. Brave. Isn't she your lover?
- I don't only have one or two lovers. - No, this woman.
Aigoo, that's right. She is.
By this rate, isn't she going to die?
God Tae Oh's concerts are all canceled. Is something going on?
- Isn't Tae Oh Oppa sick?- He's gone missing.
- Let's report this to the police.- Daebak! For real?
- Is he going somewhere?- Something is weird. He's not the type of person to disappear like this.
- Right, he did go dark for a while from time to time, but...  - This is weird. He hasn't been active in his SNS either.
Let's contact them now—the police.
Park Hye Joo, do you know anything about Yoo Tae Oh's disappearance?
I'm not sure. What would I know?
Yoo Tae Oh. Just tell me whether he's alive or not.
Lawyer Cha! Are you regaining consciousness?
I'll help you sit up.
Are you okay?
Seeing as how I'm hurting,
- I didn't die.- There was about to be a big accident.
Lawyer Cha, what happened?
- What about my cell phone? Where is it?- I tried to find it,
but it wasn't at the site.
- It's crucial evidence. - Crucial?
- Can't you tell she's a patient?  - That's why we're interrogating her here.
Cha Geum Joo?
What happened to Yoo Tae Oh?
Where is he?
Shouldn't you first ask me how I got shot?
Isn't that the right order?
Then why did you get shot?
- I got shot while getting Yoo Tae Oh's confession.  - Aigoo, aigoo.
Then it's true you were with him?
- Yes. - Tell me where he is now!
Geez, looks like you'll have to be sitting in an interrogation room to spill anything.
I'll ask you again. Where is Yoo Tae Oh right now?
Prosecutor Choi, as far as Yoo Tae Oh's whereabouts go,
it's something you need to find out.
I'm talking about you guys, the police.
Oh, no. What do we do?
- Something's wrong! - What's wrong with 4087?
- He suddenly collapsed. He's dying. - We have a patient. Send an ambulance.
- What do I do? - Oh!
W-W-Where? Did you get hit here? I'm sorry. Is your bottom half okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I'm deeply reflecting.
Reflecting?
From now on, no matter what happens, I won't let you be by yourself. I'm going to go around with you no matter what.
Because you didn't come to the office for a few days, I thought you quit.
What do you mean 'quit?' Didn't I tell you I'm like a cicada? A cicada! Like a cicada, I stick right on you!
We argued over submitting an appeal.
What do you mean argue? It was a discussion between a defense team members. To see what would be the best way and if not what could make the difference.
But why haven't you come to the office?
- I went to Busan.- Why Busan?
I'll tell you everything, but first, you need to be secure.
Well, because you're reflecting now,
- I'll forgive you.- Thank you.
Lawyer Cha, I realized something this time.
I can't do without you,
but you also can't do without me.
Aigoo, my stomach!
Excuse me. Seoul National Hospital.
My doctor is at that hospital.
Aigoo, my stomach! Hurry! Hurry, hurry!
I was contacted by Yoo Tae Oh.
Then Jo Ye Ryeong tried to stop her scandal from leaking out, so she had someone
attack Min Na. Is that what he confessed?
Yes. I even recorded everything.
But then that man appeared.
"That man?" You're talking about the Fixer, right?
Yes.
Then you told Prosecutor Choi all this, too?
No. Prosecutor Choi is Ohsung's snitch anyhow.
What are you going to now? He's going to be on the move, looking for Yoo Tae Oh.
I need to do an interview.
She seems fine.
Why am I so sad?
Ham Bok Geo!
How did you get here?
What did you do while this happened to Cha Geum Joo?
Did you perhaps escape?
There's also something I'm good at.
I cosplayed as a patient.
But there's no wheelchair. It wouldn't be nice like, bam!
Before you receive aggravated punishment, hurry up and go back.
This is your lawyer's order.
Geez, I came out because you got shot, but you're scolding me.
Is your body okay?
I'm okay.
Attorney, Cha, this just a warning.
Next time, it might not end with a cast.
Even so, I can't get squashed away now.
You won't change your direction, huh?
Then, you two should talk to me over there.
There's something I want to ask you about how this happened to you.
Alright? Follow me.
Client, please continue to cosplay a chairman and get enough rest.
- Where are you going?  - Reporters are waiting for me.
Reporters?
You must be thinking of doing an interview with the reporters.
You know I'm an expert in that arena.
But why are you all covered up? You shouldn't be.
Grab it.
The point of holding an interview is to make an impact.
You have to emphasize that you even got shot.
But it's cold—
Man, this is much better than covering her.
I'll listen to the expert this time.
Right.
Fighting!
Please tell us! Please find him!
What do we do about our oppa!
Who shot you, Cha Geum Joo?
- It's Alan Baston. - Who's Alan Baston?
During Seo Ji Ah's murder case trial,
he's the witness who committed perjury, saying Ham Bok Geo is the murderer.
Were you with Yoo Tae Oh at the time of the shooting?
- What happened to Yoo Tae Oh? - Do you know where Yoo Tae Oh is?
- Please tell us!  - What happened?
Did you not meet Yoo Tae Oh? Do you know something?
I will not take any more questions.
What the heck? What's going on?
This is not a courtroom.
I'll reveal everything in the courtroom.
Courtroom? What type of courtroom are you referring to?
An appeal.  Press conference held by Attorney Cha Geum Joo over her shooting incident
Wow. She doesn't even get nervous.
At that rate, you can say she was born to do that.
- At that appeal...
How much did Yoo Tae Oh confess?
He said that Jo Ye Ryeong was behind the homeless girl, Min Na's incident.
But the Fixer showed up all of a sudden and took her cell phone that had the recording on it.
- How about Yoo Tae Oh? - She didn't tell me anything about him.
Let's just see. I think she's got some ideas.
How is it relevant?
Seo Ji Ah's murder case and Yoo Tae Oh's disappearance,
they're all relevant to the homeless girl incident.
Wow, our Golden Tree is doing great.
I should've married Cha Geum Joo, not that moron.
Then our Golden Tree will become famous, right?
How are they all relevant?
Unless the truth behind the homeless girl incident is revealed,
things of this nature will continue to happen.
- He's alive, right?  - Please find him!
So, I urge the court
to accept the appeal on the homeless girl incident.
- Find Yoo Tae Oh!  - Find him! Find him!
- Retry the homeless girl incident! - Retry! Retry!
Insisting on the relevance of the disappearance of Yoo Tae Oh and the homeless girl incident,
demanding investigation into Yoo Tae Oh's disappearance and appeal, the fans are protesting...
Cha Geum Joo is amazing.
Trying to get an appeal by moving Yoo Tae Oh's fans?
But did CEO Lee Dong Soo overextend himself taking care of Yoo Tae Oh and all?
Yoo Tae Oh met Cha Geum Joo
and aimed at me.
He couldn't be left alone.
Here's what you asked for.
They have grudges against Ohsung.
But why did you want that?
Sam Hon Technology, Kang Young Doo...
Kang Young Doo  (Born 8-2-1943)
Subtitles brought to you by The Feisty Team @ Viki
How did you take care of Yoo Tae Oh?
Why should I tell you that, Park Hye Joo?
Since it's come to this, I'm going to have to turn the table.
When the appeal starts, all of us will be subpoenaed.
Shouldn't we escape that before then?
Park Hye Joo, I'm a professional.
A professional is someone who takes care of business as much as he's been paid and leaves. I'm the Fixer, a janitor.
Don't worry about me, but look for a way for you to escape.
I'm sure money wasn't the driving force behind your involvement in this.
I don't know why you're doing this, but
I'll just let our discussion slide by since you're so pretty.
See you again, okay?
Your real name is Kang Eun Tae. Born in Gyeonggido, Gangjoo.
You're studying overseas in France.
Go on.
Your father, Kang Young Doo, was involved in a ramen machine patent lawsuit for a long time
and lost to Ohsung and then he committed suicide.
Should I go on?
Like Sam Hon Technology, you wanted to see Ohsung get eaten up by a more powerful entity.
I underestimated Park Hye Joo.
Okay.
Let me try drawing a picture.
I take care of all the secrets of CEO Lee Dong Soo and give them to you,
and you'll become the best in this industry, right?   Ohsung
Then what do I not have?
Are you going to revive my late father who committed suicide?
I have something like this.
You know what this is, right?
That revenge... I'll help you.
Park Hye Joo, do you know why a human gives up on revenge?
Revenge takes all the energy out of you.
This was as much energy as I was going to use for this case,
but you're provoking me unnecessarily.
What are you going to do about it? How are you going to take responsibility? Huh?
I will take responsibility.
Just as Lee Dong Soo killed your father so brilliantly through law,
we can screw over that Lee Dong Soo legally.
Don't you think the color of your revenge will change a bit that way?
That's not a bad idea.
By chance, did you come to visit with me?
Yes.
Is something going on with you?
There's many things.
What is this?
I came to give you back your phone.
I'm sure you wouldn't give up at the retrial.
So... I stole this from Lee Dong Soo.
Subtitles brought to you by The Feisty Team @ Viki
Hye Joo...
That should help you at the retrial, right?
I'm sorry for all that time, Eonni.
You'll understand me, right? I had no choice because I was the weak one.
Even if others didn't, I always thought that you would always understand me.
You must protect the source of your video clip.
But... are you going to be okay?
Doing this, what if it puts you in danger too?
Then I'll be sure to take care of myself.
Who's the source?
I'm not the one saying this but... could it be Lawyer Park Hye Joo?
I'm worried if it's a trap.
But wouldn't revealing this help with the retrial?
Heol... This coming into our hands is amazing.
Attorney Cha is asking me to reveal it at an appropriate time.
Does Representative Ham know?
CEO Ham says he'll tell us when the appropriate timing is.
She's running all over the place asking for a retrial. Will you leave her alone like that?
It's not a case involving city and state. The court won't accept the retrial that easily.
But that was the case I stopped investigating while I was head prosecutor in Busan.
I can't even sleep these days.
What happened to the guy who confessed to be the real culprit to the homeless girl incident?
There is this drug dealer named Lee Byun Dae.
010-7552-2679
Yes, hello?
Lawyer Oh has arrived in Busan.
In Busan?
Okay, I understand. I'm right on my way.
You look so much older than your age.
You have the money? Show me it again.
I don't... have it right now. I'll send it to you right away.
Pay first and get the goods after. Pay up first.
Really. I said I'll send it to you right away.
You think I've never fell for this before?
Hey. You know Lee Byun Dae, right?
What about Byun Dae?
If you find him, I will give you this for free.
How does that sound?
Byun Dae!
What's up?
You here? You came here rather fast.
Damn it!
Hey, hey!
- What, what?  - Here...
- Thank you!  - Bye!
Hey!
Get him!
Wait for me!
No, go ahead!
Hey!
It's fake!!
It's a dead end. Hey, hey, that's dangerous.
Don't come near, you stupid cop!
Put that down. I'm not a cop. I'm a lawyer. Min Na's lawyer.
What are you talking about? She died a long time ago.
You confessed you were the culprit, but the Prosecutors Office let you go, huh?
Byun Dae. Min Ah misses you.
Crazy bastard, why do you keep talking about Min Na?
Because Min Ah is alive.
Don't talk about her.
I told you don't talk about her!
Relax. Byung Dae, relax.
Let go of me!
Hi, Min Ah.
Yes, Lawyer Mister. Is there something going on?
I have someone I want to show you.
- Yes? Who is it?- Just a minute.
You were alive. You were alive...
Even that punk Byun Dae was so happy that you were alive.
Tell him I'm so happy that he told the truth. Be sure to. You have to!
Okay.
I think it's really strange.
I put my life on the line to catch the murderer. Yet the true perpetrator tells me that he feels so much better.
And the victim is even being forgiving.
Attorney, the ones who don't like to retry are not the true perpetrator or the victim.
It's so ironic that it's the people who don't want to accept their wrongdoings.
Accepting that you're wrong is much harder than you think.
I really felt it this time. Judges and prosecutors make things such as mistakes too.
So, there has to be a system that can prove them wrong.
But I don't think that would be easy.
People who believe that they're smart would have a hard time accepting that.
This woman has changed many people's lives.
It's not right only trying to protect your own career.
What will you do about Gyeong Hwan?
That is the hardest thing for me.
The fact that Gyeong Hwan who was falsely accused can't seem to make up his mind.
Gyeong Hwan, what did you want to be when you grew up?
A baseball player. Just like Lee Dae Oh.
But... my dream changed when I was 8 years old.
What is it?
To be a pharmacist.
When I was 8 years old, my mother sent me to buy medicine.
I picked up the medicine with a prescription and gave it to mom.
That night... my mother died.
In my arms...
I didn't even what that medicine was going to be used for.
And I didn't even know she was trying to kill herself and I bought it for her...
My dad beat me up all the time for it. So, I left home.
Only if the pharmacist had said to bring my mom with me...
If my mother was just okay...
I took one on purpose and each of them...
I'm going to eat this.
To be honest, I'm scared.
I'm worried you and Min Ah will be put in danger.
That's what I'm afraid of...
That's why...
So? So that's why you couldn't decide.
Don't worry!
I have a hidden plan too.
You must've thought that I'm such a devoted person to call for this retrial, huh?
It's not like that!
I'm doing it just because I want to become famous.
You want to become famous?
That's right! I have my personal greed...
I'm telling you don't worry.
You and Min Na... If I am to protect my people, I need to become famous.
I don't have money and...
I'm the most dense person in this field.
So the only thing I can do is become famous, right?
Gosh, seriously...
Relax. Everything will be okay.
Oppa! You have to be really really well!
Okay.
How well will you be?
The successful people...
You have to be very well.
How do we win against them? I don't have much power.
To be honest, I have no confidence.
At times like these, I have no choice to but to get strong.
If losers were to unite, you never know.
It's me. Ham Bok Geo.
I thought you would be worried.
That video is going to be released today.
Today, K-fact announced that they have a video clip of missing Hallyu star Yoo Tae Oh and...  K-fact releases a sex video clip between Yoo Tae Oh and daughter-in-law of conglomerate
and Ohsung Group's second daughter-in-law A
The controversial video clip was filmed in Ohsung vacation home and the person who filmed this is...
the victim of homeless girl incident, Kim Min Na.
Whether this case will be retried or now is on everyone's focus.
What happened there? How did K-fact get a hold of that?
I don't know. I haven't had it for a few years.
There's no way Yoo Tae Oh's agency would've revealed it...
Is CEO Lee Dong Soo trying to control Jo Ye Ryeong by releasing this and throwing the first punch?
That's weird though.
You don't know where Yoo Tae Oh is do you?
I'm curious too. Whether he's dead or alive.
Ah... starting to get at me more and more.
I'm sorry but I can't tell you as of right now.
I'll personally contact you at a later time. Okay.
I can't give out personal information.
Hello, K-fact. Yes, we can't reveal our source.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Let me know who the source is for the video clip.
We believe in protecting our source.
We can never... never tell you who our source is.
Go ahead.
Okay. Take everything please.
I had so much to sort through for trash, but it's nice to have government official to do that for me.
What is this... Ah...
Are you coming in to work? Are you okay?
Yes. I was getting antsy.
You plan to wear that at the court?
Someone told me this makes an impact.
Lawyer Cha. Talk with me for a bit.
Lawyer Cha. Let's look at the reality. It won't work this time.
Min Na is alive and Gyeong Hwan has done his time.
Lawyer Goo.
I now think that... this will all be over soon.
So...
So I thought about it and I realized that if we retrial, I won't make any money.
But if I take another case while working on this retrial, I won't be as effective.
I'm not confident enough to make you a living.
- What? Are you telling me to get out?- Yes.
How can you be so disloyal?
I looked into it...
Harvard Law School?
I sent them your trial resume and they offered to give you a one year scholarship.
Lawyer Cha. You really...
I got an interview for next week.
So, go ahead and leave.
There's no need for you to be so thankful. I mean... Lawyer Goo.
You are the best lawyer in all of Korea.
But when you come back, you have to come back to Golden Tree.
You can't play elsewhere just because you're so successful.
Our Cha Geum Joo... let me give you a hug.
There's no room. Take the next one.
I can make room.
Oh, my... oh, my... oh, my...
What blew over?
It's today's headline on K-fact.
[Breaking News] The biggest scandal, Yoo Tae Oh and daughter-in-law of conglomerate, sex video revealed
- By chance, didn't you release this, CEO?  - How could...
How could this be in Ham Bok Geo's hands?
What's Jo Ye Ryeong doing?
She's asking for explanation right away.
Do you possibly know who gave them that video?
I'm not sure. How did that get leaked?
For now, we're thinking of denying that you're the woman in the video clip.
How about Prosecutors Office?
I'll talk to Prosecutor Choi and although there will be an investigation...
I've already mentioned that we should drive this as a photo manipulation.
But that's not the problem...
The thing is who released this video clip?
By chance, do you suspect anyone...
Why is Representative Lee not coming?
Ah... he is coming right now. However...
is there a possibility that somebody else who knows Representative Lee Dong Soo could have the video?
I don't know. That would be a bit difficult.
He ordered me to sell Ohsung Art Center shares over that.
It's just that I heard something strange from Prosecutor Choi.
I heard that CEO Lee Dong Soo is working with hedge fund Milliet.
The last I heard, it's special investigative team's top secret information.
Lee Dong Soo...
Then, have a nice chat.
I'm extremely sorry about the leaking of video clip.
I'm looking into it also, but...
What more do you need?
What are you referring to?
I gave everything to Representative Lee.
Did you hold Milliet's hand instead of me?
Why don't you tell me? The thing that special investigative team is looking into...
Lawyer Goo will be back soon, right?
Lawyer. I keep getting greedy.
How should I say it? I want to become a skilled lawyer, even if I could do it in one day. That kind of greed.
So I want to become a trustworthy and confident partner to you.
Did you not know? Even you right now,
you are a proud partner.
- Really?- Of course!
Oh... thank you.
But um.. are you going to keep keeping this a secret from me?
What?
About Yoo Tae Oh's whereabouts.
We have to submit our request for the retrial and...
I think it's about time that you told me about it.
To be honest, I don't really know either.
Wait, what? You don't know?
When I woke up after getting shot, I was in the hospital.
I think it may have been Alan...
I think maybe he took Yoo Tae Oh somewhere but
I don't know what happened.
You did an interview though acting as if you knew everything.
Well, kind of sort of bluffing?
Ah, lie...
Yes.
With my hidden cards...
I couldn't imagine overcoming this crisis.
So, I acted as if I had it all.
- Ah... so its so you can get the retrial and find Yoo Tae Oh?- Yep.
But... I can't believe it.
Why did you bluff with me, too?
Because you're so naive.
You're the type who wears his feelings on his sleeves.
I thought you'd get caught if I told you.
I'm saying you don't have a poker face.
So how do look to you right now?
I made you mad?
Wrong. I'm in a good mood.
I'm sorry.
Did your workplace give you a lot of severance pay?
I think Professional Kang put him away.
Put him away?
- What?- You know that...
Tae Oh?
Yes, the day Paralegal Cha fell is the day he was put away.
I looked into it. Since I chased him down, there was no evidence of him on the phone.
I don't think he left the vacation home.
Then, how about the location where he's been put away?
Well, that...
Was it you by any chance?
What are you talking about?
I suddenly can't get in contact with Pro Kang.
Jo Ye Ryeong's video clip has leaked.
Someone is totally screwing me over, but...
The one I'm suspecting of...
Why do I feel like it's you?
Are you saying I'm playing the snitch?
If so, why would I do such a thing?
I would've revealed the autopsy results.
I don't know.
To cut me out completely?
Report to Jo Ye Ryeong.
You move Ohsung and...
The fact that Milliet is controlling you...
What happens if Ohsung family finds out about that?
Boy, you watched too many videos.
What connection is there between me and Milliet?
CEO Lee Dong Soo is being controlled by the international hedge fund Milliet.
Buy stock shares of Ohsung and...
control Ohsung to his heart content.
Attorney Park, what are you thinking right now? Perhaps...
Are you trying to go back?
As if.
I've come too far to go back.
CEO. Taking me in as a hostage...
Don't you think you miscalculated?
Chan Geum Joo...
She can give up everything for me but...
I can't.
I'm not interested in Cha Geum Joo's life.
So...
rather than becoming a pathetic hostage...
Rather, I'd like this seat.
Please drink it and let's get going.
You have to go to the director's meeting and explain yourself today.
I don't think I can go.
No, I mean... I can't go.
Even so, you have to go out there.
I will stop them so don't worry too much.
If you get an uneasy question, don't answer it.
Just show a puzzled look on your face.
You understand?
Ohsung's reputation has fallen to the ground!
Resign from your director position right away.
Or explain yourself about the video clip.
Whatever you may have seen...
That is not the truth.
It was manipulated.
You call that an explanation?
Are you trying to deceive us, too?
We'll wrap up here.
If you have any objections in the future, please submit it to me in writing.
No matter what it is, you can let me know.
As for my email address...
I'll send it to your secretaries.
Let's go.
Wow... Ms. Golden Tree, you got so famous.
It's thanks to you.
But don't you think you're requesting visitors too often?
I'm disappointed.
The homeless girl case retrial... is that all you're after?
Are you going to let me rot here?
You know everything. Why are you acting this way?
In order to get you out of there...
we have to dig into the homeless girl incident.
You saw it at our last trial.
Even if I argue the possibility of the third party committing the murder,
the judge didn't even budge.
Are you really going to retrial?
Of course!
Why do you ask me this out of the blue?
How could someone like you be so rude in front of the judge?
I believe in the existence of the law but
As for people who practice law...
I decided not to believe them too easily.
If we end up with a retrial,
you'll get to testify as a witness.
So... you need to prepare yourself.
The source of that video clip...
Was it Park Hye Joo?
I can't reveal my source.
Why would Park Hye Joo...
Why she gave you that video...
Did you think of the motive?
I hear that Ohsung Law Firm's Representative...
has changed.
It's no longer Lee Dong Soo.
Representative Lee Dong Soo
You are not Ohsung's lawyer.
You're our dog (servant).
Representative Park Hye Joo
You are curious where Yoo Tae Oh is, aren't you?
Shall I let you know?
The place where the Food Talk took place.
He's nicely buried in your vacation home somewhere.
- Lawyer Park...- What do you mean 'Lawyer Park'?
'Representative Park.' That's what you have to call me now.
I threw you a rope to rescue you when you were on the verge of dying...
Is this how you repay my generosity?
Was that a rope to rescue me?
It was a rope you can cut at any given time.
What have you done to him?
How did you manage to control him?
I used your accomplishments against you.
You and him had a special connection.
As for that... hear it for yourself.
Tell me. Where in my vacation home did you hide him?
Where did you bury Yoo Tae Oh?!
Let loose your dogs and look for him.
The minute they dig up Yoo Tae Oh's body...
You will be caught at that seat as the true criminal.
Even if you left it alone... until the day you die...
you'll be Park Hye Joo's hostage.
Subtitles brought to you by The Feisty Team @ Viki
CEO.
What brings you here?
You wouldn't have come to take some time off...
Ah, you must be here looking for Yoo Tae Oh's body.
I had no idea you'd stick by a rookie like Park Hye Joo.
I hired the wrong Fixer.
You'll pay for all this someday.
Pay for it?
I believe I've already been paid for by you, CEO.
Attorney Park told me there's bad blood between you and I.
What is she talking about?
You'll find out soon.
Thanks... for making up your mind.
Detective, please keep him very safe until the date of the trial.
Don't worry.
Um...
I don't have any money.
I can't pay your fee. Is that okay?
Then you can't buy a lawyer. You'll have to cancel your retrial. Sorry.
What's this? Take it out.
- Here. Oh, no...  - Wow, it's cool. What's that?
This is all I have.
Then you're putting everything you've got for this retrial.
You lost everything you have. So, you have to go for it with all your might from this point on, got it? Okay, fighting!
Fighting!
I like this the most out of all the payment we received.
It's all he has.
Application for a Retrial
I haven't had such an exciting and nervous feeling for long time while submitting document. Such a day has come.
But there are good signs.
When the stamp goes down at one time clearly and nice when I file my paperwork, the trial goes smoothly.
I hope that sign is right this time.
But I wonder what happened to Yoo Tae Oh.
It's been a week since Hallyu Star Yoo Tae Oh was missing.
Meanwhile, Lawyer Cha Geum Joo, the last person who stayed with him before his missing and got attacked
cast a doubt on the connection between the homeless girl case and Yoo Tae Oh's missing.
She applied the retrial of the case.-Will they approve it?-If you don't approve it...
We went over the retrial application but it seems it's hard to accept the grounds.
May I ask you the reason?
According to the record, besides Defendant Oh Gyeong Hwan had confessed his crime at the prosecutors' office,
he admitted his crime at the court as well.
Being taken this into consideration, his sentence was reduced.
That confession was made under coercive investigation.
Please reference evidence #1 I submitted earlier.
After Defendant Oh Gyeong Hwan was released from prison, he wrote an apology letter several times and mailed it to the police.
And even though the victim is alive, the testimony from the person who survived from the brain death.
is fully reliable? That's my doubt.
Please look at the evidence #2 attached to the retrial application.
There's Lee Byung Dae's confession who was arrested for dealing drugs in Busan saying that he was hired by someone to get involved in the homeless girl incident.
That's just the defense argument. The incident was already closed by the Prosecutors Office and the police for lack of evidence.
Defense, I do see your effort, but let's stop here.
I'm sure you know of the legal stability.
The case from the past is exactly that.
People like us can be slightly wrong, but not hugely wrong.
Subtitles brought to you by The Feisty Team @ Viki
Find Yoo Tae Oh oppa for us!
Defense, what are you doing right now?
Your Honor, the homeless girl incident is not just in the past, but it still continues in the present...
It's crime in progress that is relevant to the disappearance of celebrity Yoo Tae Oh.
If the court does not allow for the retrial...
the currently missing Yoo Tae Oh, or perhaps a celebrity who might already be dead...
You will not avoid the media's criticism that you're neglecting them.
Are you pressuring the court with the threat of media coverage?
No. Judge, you should never...
be controlled by the media.
As for me, a judgement that may be in the wrong...
How significant that could mean to the people...
Where the trust in the law comes from...
I want to clearly remind you.
Why law exists... the reason behind that...
Please show it to us, Your Honor.
I'll assist Jo Ye Ryeong from now on and work for a better Grace Group.
Gosh, how could someone so young be so sharp?
CEO Park, I welcome you to our Grace Group.
Thank you. Rather than the madam who doesn't even show her face anywhere...
CEO Park would better serve as a vice chairwoman.
Thank you.
You have a guest.
CEO Lee Dong Soo.
Did you receive a confirmation for your retrial?
This was a difficult visit for you. Please tell me what brought you here.
I thought Ham Bok Geo would stop it, but he's revealing it unexpectedly.
I don't like it when someone forces me to do something.
My circumstance is looking pathetic for me to beat around the bush with you.
After the retrial, your career and other things... they'll all end.
Look after your own career.
I thought you'd have something other to say besides a threat.
I'm busy because I have to prepare for the retrial.
Do you still...
think of her as your sister?
You must still think of Attorney Park as your younger sister, but...
What brings you here?
I'm here to see the CEO. CEO Park Hye Soo.
I'll have to inspect you. This is the CEO's order.
My body is covered with metals. It would be difficult.
I'm the Golden Tree.
Prosecutor Choi
Ah, seriously... Prosecutor Choi
CEO Park Hye Joo
I got out of a meeting since I heard you were coming.
Where's Yoo Tae Oh?
Why do you ask me that? I think I cooperated with you as much as I can.
Now, you're asking me to find out where Yoo Tae Oh's body is now?
It won't be easy.
His body?
You already knew that Yoo Tae Oh was dead from the time you came to visit me, right?
- What makes you think that? - Earlier...
I asked you where Yoo Tae Oh was. Not if he was dead.
Hye Joo... no...
Attorney Park Hye Joo...
You already knew Yoo Tae Oh was dead and used me.
To get rid of CEO Lee Dong Soo.
Then, let me ask you again.
Where is Yoo Tae Oh?
Paralegal Cha, please!
Isn't it about time you behave like an attorney?
- Like an attorney? - There are attorneys everywhere you turn.
In the midst, you're on the bottom of the totem pole.
Ah, your press conference was very honest. Sounds like you passed the bar with a difference of one point.
Do you get it now? You don't have the brain to survive Seochodong now.
Don't be delusional. You were cool when you used to be a paralegal.
The Seoul Central District Court  Criminal Case 11, Decision
I'm sorry to behave like an attorney...
The retrial has been decided.
Retrial?
Fine, work hard on your retrial. But would it change anything?
There's a limit to what you can do.
Of course, it would be like that by myself. Since I don't have the brain to survive that...
the losers have united.
Aren't you curious as to who would be the one to get knocked down?
♫  You were always standing one step behind me  ♫
♫  Won't you look at me forever?  ♫
♫  When you look at me  ♫
Woman with a Suitcase
Either save the kids or me. Just do one thing. So, focus on saving the kids, Cha Geum Joo...
Won't you need to compromise since it's come to this?
Lose the retrial, but let Ham Bok Geo remain a murderer.
- Negotiation is up to the conditions.- You're no longer the Park Hye Joo I used to know.
But does that change anything? There's limit to what you can do.
Since I don't have the brain to survive this, the losers decided to unite.
Aren't you curious who would get knocked out?
- I'm nervous. - It's almost time. Let's go!
Watch carefully how I rescue those kids as an attorney.