CEO Park Hye Joo
Earlier...
I asked you where Yoo Tae Oh was. Not if he was dead.
Hae Joo... No...
Attorney Park Hye Joo...
You already knew Yoo Tae Oh was dead and used me
to get rid of CEO Lee Dong Soo.
Then, let me ask you again.
Where is Yoo Tae Oh?
Paralegal Cha, please!
Isn't it about time you behaved like an attorney?
Like an attorney?
There are attorneys everywhere you turn.
In the midst, you're on the bottom of the pole.
Ah, your press conference was very honest.
Sounds like you passed the bar with a difference of one point.
Do you get it now?
You don't have the brains to survive Seochodong now.
Don't be delusional.
You were only cool when you used to be a paralegal.
The Seoul District Court Criminal Case 11, Decision
I'm sorry to behave like an attorney.
The retrial has been decided.
Retrial?
Fine, work hard on your retrial.
But will it change anything? There's a limit to what you can do.
Of course, it would be like that by myself.
Since I don't have the brains to survive that alone...
the losers have united.
Aren't you curious as to who would be the one
to get knocked down?
How I rescue the kids as a lawyer...
watch very carefully.
Okay.
Let's say you rescue the kids. But how would you go about rescuing Ham Bok Geo?
Wouldn't you have to resolve Seo Ji Ah's murder case to win properly?
We requested Yoo Tae Oh to appear as a witness, but we don't even know where he is...
- What do you think happened?  - I'm wondering if he's already dead.
But you know... the additional report that disappeared...
Where is Yoo Tae Oh?
Hey, if I knew, would I be here like this?
- Then give it to me.  - Give what?
The missing additional document to the autopsy report.
You're the one who hid it, right?
Geez, this rude junior of mine...
Hey, what are you doing in here? Huh?
I was thinking and realized that the report did arrive here whole, but the fact that a page is missing...
I can only conclude that you committed an illegal act, Prosecutor.
Hey, you know I'm a prosecutor of Korean. You think I tainted the evidence?
Yes. Seeing how you perform in court, your character is more than enough to do that sort of thing.
Hey, you... really...
really should be careful. I'm going to one day just...
Prosecutor...
Be careful.
Because I'm going to unravel it one day.
Hey, Park Hae Joo! Why don't you answer your phone?
Hey, at the retrial... Cha Geum Joo and that bastard Ma Seok Woo will try to save Ham Bok Geo all at the same time.
If that happens, I'll be completely humiliated.
That won't happen.
By chance, did you take that additional report?
Yeah.
I would like for you to give it back.
Why? Isn't me stealing it something you should be thankful for?
Well... it's because I'm wondering what you'll do. Like if you suddenly cooperate with Cha Geum Joo.
- Do you have a lighter?  - Yeah.
You were talking about this, right?
The proof that says Alan Baston is the real killer.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Subtitles brought to you by The Feisty Team @ Viki
You're... no longer the Park Hye Joo I used to know.
- Hi, Attorney Min.  - Welcome, Attorney Lee Dong Soo.
I heard you were recruiting. Daeseoyang is a huge company.
Well, nothing compared to your company size. Have a seat.
So, what is it...
I heard you're leaving Ohsung.
I was wondering if you'd like to join us.
Whose idea is this?
Well... it's actually the Princess' suggestion.
I didn't want to take my case to Park Hye Joo, so I picked this law firm.
Yes. If you join us, she says she'll give us her lawsuit.
I'll think about it.
Thank you for your consideration.
But that Park Hye Joo... that shrewd one... are you going to leave her there?
You should teach her a lesson.
Yes?
My vacation home?
I understand. I'll go there right now.
It's a dead badger.
Hey, it's the corpse of a badger! Find something else.
You worked hard.
Search. Hurry and go search.
Geez, seriously...
Geez, what did that punk do here?
Go ahead and shoot me. This is like my life.
Save me!
Do you think I'll save you or kill you?
Before you leave us, God Tae Oh, you have to eat this first.
Last time when I got rid of Seo Ji Ah, that shrewd girl
left the real killer evidence in her stomach.
She drew a picture of a parrot on the candy wrapper.
So, I thought of a really fun idea.
Wait, wait, give it to me. You can't carry this.
I'm okay!
I'm not okay! I'm not okay! It hasn't been long since you took off your cast.
Attorney, next time, don't even lift up a single paper.
I'll take care of my documents.
How did it go? You visiting Prosecutor Choi?
I pointed out everything, but he didn't even budge.
I feel like he may not know anything.
I think all these witness will come, but......Yoo Tae Oh...
What should we do about Yoo Tae Oh? Seeing as he hasn't even been found by the police yet...
It would be really great if he came back in one piece.
These are documents we can't submit since we haven't retrieved them.
Ah, and...
This second evidence...
Are you going to use this in the trial this time?
Why?
It's a bit worrying.
It's an issue of conflict of interest.
If they bring up the fact that we were defending Jo Ye Ryeong in the past...
we can get sued for breaching our contract.
I'm ready for that.
I hope the judge makes a good call.
We have to hope that the judge will have the eyes of God.
Woman With a Suitcase
Episode 15God's Eyes
I don't think a good lawyer is someone who's good in trials.
The big things always happen behind the scenes.
I came by just in case you have a misunderstanding.
What misunderstanding?
Our fault lies in that both of us were loyal to Ohsung.
You and I both... I think it's foolish to screw ourselves up over this.
I don't know how you got your grip on Professional Kang, but...
since it's come to this, isn't negotiation necessary?
Negotiation begins with condition.
Lose the retrial...
but instead let Ham Bok Geo remain a murderer.
Are you asking me to draw the line between those two cases?
Hurry up!
Yes, Editor, we just got in.
Look over here.
What's all this?
Commemorating Ohsung Construction Completion...
Sam Hon Technology Patent Lawsuit...
Over here... take a picture of this.
What's that?
It was displayed like a museum inside CEO Lee Dong Soo's vacation home.
A display?
Yes, as if to show off his own accomplishments he had everything displayed.
But this is weird.
Why is that one empty?
The only one that's empty is the one from Sam Hon Technology's patent lawsuit?
Yes. Do you think it's relevant to this case?
A legal professional's achievement can come back to him as a karma.
Lee Dong Soo's achievements...
Look into Sam Hon Technology case. Find out if there's anything unusual about it.
Okay, I'll do that.
What will you do about your travel ban?
Don't worry about stuff like that. I'm a pro.
I guess the achievement Attorney Lee Dong Soo was so proud of has come back to him as karma.
It looks like... it's been a really long time since they closed down.
Be careful.
Sam Hon Technology at war with Ohsung Technology over patent
Prosecutor on the case Lee Dong Soo arrests Sam Hon Technology's CEO Kang Young Doo?
Is your gunshot wound okay?
I'm perfectly fine.
You must be really happy about your retrial.
That goes without saying.
Is your trial preparation going well?
You have to stand as a witness in this retrial.
I don't know if my testimony would be any help.
You can't be a double timer.
Double timing?
Whether it's this side or that side, be sure to support one side firmly.
Don't worry about this side and that side both.
What do you mean I'm double timing?
I think you are.
By chance, if you're talking about Attorney Ma... I don't think I've been weighing toward one side completely.
Besides, it's not our time to talk about stuff like that.
At times you can be double timing when it comes to a relationship between a man and woman.
It's not like you're having an affair. Who cares?
Weigh everything and double time all you want and come to me in the end.
Then, what do you mean when you say not to double time?
Either save the kids or me.
Just pick one. If you're trying to prove my innocence under these circumstances, the judge will feel a lot of pressure.
He'll be under pressure by the people who are connected to the Food Talk.
Then the trial will tangle up.
Cha Geum Joo, I'll work on saving myself.
I know the Prosecutor's Office well.
If they're embarrassed, they'll end up canceling my arrest.
So, you focus on saving the kids.
What are you thinking?
I'm your lawyer. You can't have an ulterior motive.
If you have a strategy for the trial, you should share it with me.
You're looking into Sam Hon Technology patent lawsuit, right?
So, I'm thinking the same thing you are.
What do you think I'm thinking?
Make Lee Dong Soo dig his own trap in the courtroom?
You know all about Lee Dong Soo's trial experience.
Right...
Have Lee Dong Soo stand witness and pump him up as much as you can.
How great of a prosecutor he was and how great of a lawyer he is. Got it?
Witness subpoena
Must I go to the courtroom? Tell them I'm saying no.
Unfortunately, you can't deny the witness subpoena.
They won't arrest Jo Ye Ryeong by chance, will they?
For now, let's make sure you deny the charges of hiring the culprit in the homeless girl case.
Even the video clip I was in with Yoo Tae Oh?
Yes.
You're the one who gave money to Lee Byung Dae, right, Secretary Jo?
- Yes.  - You should leave the country before the trial begins.
I understand.
Um... I'm nervous.
I'm nervous, too. But everything will be fine. It's okay.
That's right, Oppa! Fighting!
Now, everyone... you can do a good job, right?
Yes.
Should we do a "Fighting" for that reason?
There.
Paralegal.
One, two, three, Fighting!
Your Honor, may I say one more thing?
This is my last testimony.
In short, this courtroom is shitty.
It's almost time.
- Let's go!  - Let's go!
Cha Geum Joo, are you prepared for today's trial?
Today's homeless girl incident's retrial, right? How do you think it will turn out?
It's like hitting a boulder with an egg, but we'll do our best.
Will you be revealing the truth behind Seo Ji Ah's murder case and the missing Yoo Tae Oh case?
I'll just say one thing right now.
You can't lock away truth.
- Please say something about the trial.  - One word, please!
There will be the sixth retrial on a criminal case in our country momentarily. [  Homeless Girl Case becomes the sixth retrial case in Korea ]
Attorneys Cha Geum Joo and Ma Seok Woo believe this case is relevant to Seo Ji Ah's murder case...
and also the missing Hallyu star Yoo Tae Oh case as well.
You'll be attending this today, too, right, CEO?
Is something going to happen to Jo Ye Ryeong?
Just in case, be ready to write up subpoenas.
Okay.
Let's go.
Just a moment, please.
Do you know this?
You're the prettiest when I see you in a courtroom.
I'm not saying this to make you relax. It's the truth.
So, be confident in the courtroom.
The witness stand is over there.
I know.
Everyone, stand.[ Retrial of homeless girl case ]
Retrial of homeless girl case
Everyone, sit down.
At this time, case number 2015
Zero 34 retrial will begin.
Is the defendant side present?
The witness testimony has been set for this trial.
Are all the witnesses present?
- Yes. - Yes.
Everyone, please stand and pledge your oath.
Oath.
I'll speak only the truth without hiding or adding according to my conscience...
If I lie, I pledge to accept the punishment for perjury.
Witness 1. I call victim Kim Min Na to the stand.
Witness, you were called to that vacation home on the day of the incident, correct?
Yes.
The person in this photo invited you to a party called, "Food Talk," at that vacation home...
Is she the one?
Yes.
Please refrain from using the phrase "Food Talk" that hasn't been confirmed.
Defense, please be mindful of that.
Then, I'll ask you this way.
Witness, did you go with deceased Seo Ji Ah...
and go to a place be one of the teenage sex hostesses?
Yes.
On your way home from there, you stopped by the Ohsung vacation home with Seo Ji Ah and ate ramen...
and took a video clip of Yoo Tae Oh and Jo Ye Ryeong coincidentally.
Yes.
Do you think that video clip is the reason you were attacked?
That will be all.
Witness? After the attack, you were unconscious...[ Disability Diagnosis ]
There's a record that shows that you could not speak for awhile.
Could we really think that you're remembering things that happened on the day of the incident clearly?
I remember.
I just didn't speak.
Why did you go to that vacation home?
She said they'd pay me.
How much did you receive?
250,000 won.
- How many times did you go?  - Twice.
So, now... in a way, you were selling sex.
Objection. She was a minor and had left home at the time...
She was invited without knowing what she was going to do.
Defense, it's true that she sold sex regardless.
Are you going to deny that?
That's all.
Witness, you can go back to your seat.
I call Lee Byung Dae to the stand next.
For your information, Lee Byung Dae has confessed that he's the real culprit to the crime.
He's the culprit! Why didn't they catch him?
He's the one! He's the real one!
He's the one! Why don't they put him away?
Witness, at the time, you came to Seoul from Busan.
- Were you temporarily living in a homeless shelter near Suwon train station?  - Yes.
The day of the incident, you were hired by someone...
and then you kidnapped Min Na. That's what you confessed here.
Is that true?
Yes. I did that.
Someone told me to.
He gave me 7 million won and...
told me to bring him Min Na's cell phone.
Hey, give me your cell phone.
I didn't bring my cell phone with me tonight.
Are you kidding me?
I thought she was lying.
And I heard people coming.
So, I dragged her to Ohjang Park.
I really... I really left it behind.
You want to die? Hurry up and give it to me.
I'll give you money. Have all this.
Time is running out. He's waiting for me.
Hurry up and give it!
Hey, is your cell phone more important than your life right now?
Hey, hey!
So, I thought she was dead. I was scared and ran away.
I... I did it...
What did you do with the knife you used at the crime scene?
I hid it under my bed mattress...
The Busanjin Police took it.
Did you confess as the culprit behind the homeless girl incident?
- Yes.  - But how did you get released?
By chance, did you change your testimony during the prosecution interrogation?
No. The fact that I was at the crime scene...
and I explained how I stabbed Min Na in detail...
They said the case is closed all of a sudden and let me go.
I thought Min Na was really dead...
I was so tormented.
But... I'm so glad she's alive.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hello?
Witness. You're saying you were hired.
Where did you spend the money you got paid for doing that?
Living expenses...
and bought drugs...
You bought drugs?
You were arrested a few times for possession of drugs, right?
Twice...
The prosecution is doubting someone who received money from a stranger...
and got an innocent girl unconscious. This drug addict's testimony...
I'm questioning whether there's any truth to his testimony.
And... I'm wondering if someone...
hired him this time as well...
Please hear this witness' testimony with some reasonable doubt.
Geez, that prosecutor...
That's all.
I'll interrogate witness Jo Ye Ryeong.
I'll permit that.
Do you know Yoo Tae Oh personally?
No, I don't know him very well.
Since he's a model for Ohsung Fashion, I've bumped into him a few times at season fashion shows.
If that's the case, what is this video clip about?
It must be someone else or a superimposed image.
This is not a superimposed image.
Professional Opinion
As if this has your fingerprints...
it's a testimony given by a professional.
How would you explain this?
As you know, there are conflicting issues outsiders can't understand within my family.
I've had to butt heads with the family members for a long time over Ohsung Art Center director position.
I believe that video clip is a trap.
Then, are you saying that woman could be a body double?
Look, Cha Geum Joo! You were my lawyer before? How could you do this?
You ordered your secretary to retrieve that video clip...
and your secretary bribed witness Lee Byung Dae. Isn't that right?
I will deny further interrogation.
May I ask witness Lee Byung Dae one more thing?
I will permit it.
Witness, among these people...
please see if there's the person who asked you to retrieve the cell phone.
Choi Ji Hwan
Please take your time.
Over there... just before that...
Are you talking about this picture?
Yes.
The person Lee Byung Dae picked out is...
Will you continue to insist on superimposing the image or a body double?
That's all.
I'll interrogate Park Hye Joo who was defendant Oh Gyeong Hwan's lawyer at the time.
Attorney Park... this is your last chance to come back to us.
National Intelligence Service
British Intelligence Agency MI-6 is asking for our cooperation.
- Is it about helping out arresting Alan Baston? - Yeah.
Witness, you're a lawyer for Jo Ye Ryeong right now, right?
That's right.
You were also a lawyer for the defendant over there at the time of the homeless girl incident.
Yes.
As Oh Gyeong Hwan's lawyer...
you insisted that the defendant was innocent. Do you remember that?
I will not testify regarding that.
Why not?
Your Honor, I was Oh Gyeong Hwan's lawyer then, but I'm Jo Ye Ryeong's lawyer now.
I will not testify against my client.
Will that be okay?
That makes sense.
You have the right to deny testifying which can lead to legal responsibility.
You're aware, right, counselor?
Earlier, Lee Byung Dae testified saying that he was hired by Jo Ye Ryeong's secretary.
Do you know Secretary Jo's whereabouts?
I don't know.
Then what do you think about Jo Ye Ryeong's video clip?
Is it Jo Ye Ryeong?
Or is it a body double?
There's no way I'd know that. But shouldn't you reveal your source for that video clip first?
- My source? - Yes.
What if the source of that video clip is you, Attorney Cha Geum Joo...
That is exposing professional confidentiality. It's in violation of Attorneys-at-Law Act.
Even if there is a conflict of interest, if that
affects the good of all, you have an obligation to reveal the truth.
Witness, you're trying to hide the truth by using fallacious arguments.
That's all.
Your Honor, I call defendant Oh Gyeong Hwan to the stand.
I will permit it.
Defendant, do you insist your innocence?
Yes.
You wrote this letter yourself, right?
"I killed her. I'm so sorry."
I heard you've been sending this to police for several days. Why did you do that?
Is that because of your guilty conscience?
That... that's not it...
I really didn't do it...
But if I didn't write a letter of reflection, it felt like the police would come looking for me.
A scary ahjussi tried to kill me...
You must know that your back and forth testimony is hurting the stability of the law.
What do you mean "back and forth?"
The defendant is the victim to the police who ignored proper legal procedure.
Prosecutor, you're making fun of such a defendant right now.
Apologize.
Apologize?
Attorney Ma, he's cold...
Defendant, you said you were under a coercive interrogation.
By chance, did the prosecutor beat you?
That's not it, but...
I didn't do it.
It's... it's not me...
Hey...
If you keep insisting like that, you'll be in big trouble.
You have to confess if you want to go home.
Gyeong Hwan, you did wrong impulsively.
So, help me make a determination.
Whether you're supposed to be punished...
or someone I need to teach and lead...
I should know that.
Gyeong Hwan, where's the first place you took Min Na to?
Train station, right?
It was the train station, right?
For your information, Min Na was found in front of the painted rock near the garden.
Where was it?
Point it out to me.
He-Here...
Even in Yakchon intersection case, Nara supermarket case...
We've seen this from time to time...
As if to catch a rabbit, the prosecution corners the weak.
That's all.
I call Jeong Ahn Soo who was the prosecutor at the time to the stand.
Do you acknowledge your coercive interrogation?
No.
While you were the prosecutor in Busan, the true culprit showed up. Why did you stop the investigation?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Because your subordinates were digging into the case you closed
you ordered them to release the true culprit, right? A crazy guy saying he killed the homeless girl. Stop the investigation. We already have confession from Oh Gyeong Hwan. We can't start all over. It's a headache. We have other cases.
A crazy guy saying he killed the homeless girl. Stop the investigation. We already have confession from Oh Gyeong Hwan. We can't start all over. It's a headache. We have other cases.
No.
What is that angry look in your eyes?
Don't you think we should straighten this case even now?
The truth of the case is known by those kids and God knows it, too.
- God?  - What the heck is he saying?
God?
That's all.
How did this happen to that guy...
He's totally hopeless.
Prosecution, are you going to cross examine?
No, we won't.
Don't you think it's game over?
Geez, if that moron didn't say that crazy nonsense, I was going to let it go and just write up something.
I call K-fact's CEO Ham Gok Beo to the witness stand.
You've been following the homeless girl case as the CEO of K-fact, right?
Yes.
I started doing that because I met a paralegal who is extremely nosy.
I'll watch it.
Why are you so attached to this case?
A mysterious username known as Tommy Kim was geographically someone who lived in the Ohsung vacation home.
It seemed like it was relevant to the Food Talk.
Objection. His testimony has nothing to do with this case.
Witness, you're serving time for murdering Seo Ji Ah, right?
- As you can see.  - Did you kill Seo Ji Ah?
- Yes.- What is he saying?
You're admitting the fact that you killed Seo Ji Ah?
I admit it.
In the end... it was all my fault.
During the sex hostess case, I was the prosecutor on the case. I couldn't hold back my temper and quit.
For my own freedom, I lived as the paparazzi media CEO and lived a compromising life.
During all that, a woman got tangled up in this case...
but I had to sit back and watch that woman go to jail.
Having to just watch those kids being ridiculed in this courtroom...
All these things are my crimes.
That's why I'm guilty.
He's the man!
He's the man! A real man!
I'll take it as guilty symbolically.
That's all.
Witness, why didn't you expose the truth behind the homeless girl case even though you knew?
I didn't have a crucial evidence.
You kept silent because you lacked a crucial evidence.
Do you know the common denominator between a prosecutor and paparazzi media?
There are many cases that you keep quiet about even though you know the truth.
Prosecution, wrap it up if you don't have anymore questions.
I call Lee Dong Soo to the witness stand.
The defense argues that the victim was called to your vacation home.
Is that true?
I've heard some things people talk about Food Talk also.
Like gossip.
There are people who are jealous over people who got together over drinks.
Because it denied people who are troublemakers in our society.
For your information, Ham Bok Geo is also a member of our Food Talk.
If you need it, I'll submit a photograph.
- Ham Bok Geo, too?  - No, he's not.
Ham Bok Geo is also a member?
Yes, of course.
Do you know deceased Seo Ji Ah whom the defendant insists that she took her to the vacation home?
I don't know her.
Some say Yoo Tae Oh disappeared at your vacation home. What do you think about that?
I'll answer that if Yoo Tae Oh's whereabouts or body is found out.
I'm sorry, but there's nothing I can say at this point.
That's all.
Defense, will you cross-examine?
Yes.
Looking over your trial experience... it was quite brilliant.
Thank you for your compliment.
For someone like me who had to climb up from bottom to be here, there's something I don't quite understand.
Witness, you as a regular man...
you have an ability to be a great legal representative.
Thank you, but what are you trying to say...
Counselor, hurry up and make your connection to this case.
MDMA Vicious Drug Cartel, Arrested in a year
Is this a case you tried?
Yes.
What type of case was it?
So called "Dori Dori." It was a drug cartel arrest case.
How about this one?  Ohsung Technology wins against Sam Hon Technology in a patent war
Ohsung Technology wins against Sam Hon Technology in a patent war
It's a photo I took while I was a prosecutor after I tried a lawsuit where Sam Hon Technology stole Ohsung Technology's patent technology.
I hear you still keep this bolt as a souvenir?
What does that have to do with this case?
I was just thinking how amazing you are.
I feel as though I should raise my hands and feet in surrender after reviewing your trial resume.
Your Honor, please remember what the witness has just testified to.
And such an amazing lawyer like you...
makes me think there's no way you'd be involved in various controversial incidents.
That's all.
Witness, good job.
You can go back to your seat.
Cha Geum Joo... what is she thinking?
Attorney Lee Dong Soo.
Hi, you were here, too?
Yes. I enjoyed watching the trial.
Now that the charges against you are cleared up, please come to our Daeseoyang Law Firm.
Lastly, do you have anything to say, prosecutor?
I do acknowledge that there was somewhat of a coercive interrogation.
However, this case and the teenage sex hostess case are different cases.
It's not right to make the connection.
Witness Ham Bok Geo is still guilty as charged.
Defense, make your closing statement.
An innocent young man was tormented for a long time.
Also the victim was on the verge of death.
There's a conscience who yells out that he's guilty despite the punishment he'll have to face.
The judgment that can come out in front of all these truths...
I believe there's only one way.
Not guilty.
The truth can never be locked away.
Please console these kids' wounds by giving him a not guilty verdict.
Do we have to give a not guilty verdict? Then we're admitting the court's mistake.
Earlier didn't Attorney Cha Geum Joo hint at
leaving the Food Talk alone if we give a not guilty verdict?
You think she's making a deal?
Why don't we do this?
No way...
There's no way this will go wrong again.
What will I do if we get a guilty verdict?
Since the judge is god in this courtroom...
if god says he's guilty, we have to accept it.
- Since we don't have eyes of god.  - Everyone, stand.
We can only rely on the eyes of the law.
Everyone sit.
The defendant...
is not guilty.
I will declare the reasons for his not guilty sentence.
The defendant, despite being unfair to him... he thought he'd be treated with consideration and...
he confessed to the crime fearing the consequence he would have to experience in case he denied the crime.
But the defendant was still young at the time and did not receive protection of his family or guardian.
I believe he thought he didn't have anyone who'd defend him.
After the defendant arrived at the crime scene,
his testimonies regarding the circumstances were wrong and unclear.
Only after the investigative team showed him a photo...
he looked as though he was making his confession to match the actual chain of events...
I don't acknowledge the authenticity of the defendant's confession.
As a judge who doesn't have eyes of God...
I daresay I have arrived at the truth of the matter in this case.
However, the defendant... during the interrogation...
the rights he had to exercise...
and went through hardship without receiving due process of law.
Even his last hope, the court...
has no excuse for lacking serious evaluation and thought things through.
Therefore, since the statute of this case
was applied during the time when no evidences were available...
According to the criminal law article 325, latter part of the paragraph... I declare him not guilty.
For the defendant who was tormented and his family, the court...
conveys the apology for not reviewing the case more carefully.
You're under arrest for hiring an attacker for the Suwon train station homeless girl case.
- You may remain silent...  - I'm her lawyer.
Please remain silent for now.
Since it's an urgent arrest, if the arrest warrant isn't issued within 48 hours, you'll be released.
Just wait until then.
You suffered a lot!
- Min Na!  - Unni!
What will you do now? You're stuck. You have to go back to school.
That's why I'm so happy! It's all because of you! Thank you!
Just try and say you don't want to go to school! You'll really get it from me!
- Okay.  - Gyeong Hwan.
I gave you this as my attorney fee.
You said it's everything you have. I should give it back to you.
Thank you, everyone.
Lawyer...
I'm more thankful since you treated me so well.
- You suffered a lot!  - Please look over here! Please say something!
- This way please.  - Look over here.
You became a lawyer after struggling so much for so long. What is your reason for taking such a difficult case like this?
The law was made to be used for something like this.
The judiciary has the responsibility to look at the facts of the case clearly.
Lawyer Cha Geum Joo, do you think the same?
I'm working for the public good.
The public good?
When I work for my personal benefit, there are times when the good of others come about.
It's only because I wish to be famous!
Ah, then, you became really famous. Are you satisfied?
- Not yet.  - Why is that?
There is still an unsolved case.
Seo Ji Ah's murder case and Yoo Tae Oh's missing case.
Once those are finished, please come and interview me then.
Okay!
Congratulations again!
Congratulations!
We'll take a picture. Please do a pose!
1...2...3! Good!
Sam Hon Technology...
Cha Geum Joo...
Did she dig a trap in the courtroom?
What are you thinking about?
I'm leaving today.
I wanted to give you a present for the last time.
Ah, I should tell you the address of the present, right?
Restricted Mountain Area
Subtitles brought to you by The Feisty Team @ Viki
This is an announcement.
The passengers who would board the Zenus flight heading to Dubai from Incheon, flight A380...
Thank you.
Please come to the gate number 21 and start the boarding procedure.
I will repeat.
Park Hye Joo
Passengers who are to board flight A380 leaving Incheon to Dubai...
Please come to gate 21 and start your boarding procedure.
About Lawyer Cha Geum Joo... Why is she like that to Lawyer Lee Dong Soo?
Was she kissing up to him? For her future down the road?
Wow! Sunbae! I met you a lot of times before,
but isn't this too much?
No, no! It's not me! You know I have no reason to do something like this!
We can investigate that ourselves. We were looking in wrong areas just because of that badger.
Where's Hae Joo?
Where's Park Hye Joo?
I looked into Alan's crime pattern. He seems to have an M.O. [  M.O.  Modus Operandi ]
M.O?
There are common denominators in the murders he has committed.
He accuses someone else of the murder and escapes it.
Like planting my button and all...
If Yoo Tae Oh's body were to be discovered, I'm sure he has left something behind.
I heard Lee Dong Soo's patent bolt disappeared.
If Attorney Park and Alan are on the same side...
His target this time is most definitely...
Lee Dong Soo.
What is your name?
No worries. Your name doesn't matter for now.
I've been looking into the file...
We caught on to the fact that you've been aiming the domestic stock market to increase your shares
by hiring the Fixer Alan Baston.
We found crucial evidences relevant to Seo Ji Ah and Yoo Tae Oh's cases. What will you do now?
Release Ham Bok Geo?
There's evidence that Lee Dong Soo ordered Seo Ji Ah and Yoo Tae Oh's murder in order to hide Food Talk.
Consider the media and cancel the arrest for Ham Bok Geo.
No, isn't there no evidence yet that Ham Bok Geo isn't Seo Ji Hye's murderer?
Document on K-fact  Top Secret
Why is he like this when there's been a cancelation of his arrest?
Ah, really.
Where is she really?
- Is that hurrying?  - Ah, I said I would do it for you!
Lawyer Ma, stop it.
I'm scared he'll be embarrassed and run outside.
Aigoo.
You're doing the things I did back then.
Do you know where Hae Joo is?
You haven't found her yet? She's probably somewhere doing well.
If you tell me where Hae Joo is, I'll do well from now on.
I don't have a reason to make myself look good to you anymore.
I'm missing someone very much. Alright then...
Lawyer Ma, let's go.
Please go ahead first.
Okay.
Fighting!
What's with the fighting?
Why? What are you going to do?
Are you okay?
Let go!
Ma Seok Woo, you think you can work as a lawyer after beating up a prosecutor?
I'm thinking about quitting as a lawyer because I don't want to see jerks like you.
Fine. Great! You should have at least that much resolve, punk!
Stop it! You're leaving the legal field after beating me up? Ha, wow!
No... because it's so dirty, I'm going to clean up. Here.
What?
Today, the Prosecutors Office announced that K-fact's CEO Ham Bok Geo's
charges for murdering Seo Ji Ah have been cleared.
As for the urgent arrest of the culprit who was arrested
the Prosecutors Office claims that they cannot make any announcements since they're still investigating.
As for CEO Ham Bok Geo whose guilty verdict was overturned, his sentence will stop as of today
and his arrest has been canceled. He'll be released from Seoul Joongae prison.
A quiet night I can't seem to fall asleep
I'm waiting for this night to pass by and suddenly
It's been a long time, Lawyer.
It's been a long time, Client.   For countless reasons
I thought of you
It's been a long time, Cha Geum Joo.
It seemed like you already said your greetings just now.
I purposely called you out again.
Not as an attorney, but a person.
Seeing you Cha Geum Joo...
I feel really good.
I need you today. I need you
If you come before the night is over
That doesn't seem like it'll be easy, either.
It seems like it's you this time.
Cha Geum Joo!
You've been reported for violating Attorneys-at Law Act  Arrest warrant
You were always one step behind me
Can you not see me forever?