Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Feisty Team @ Viki
She's a paralegal. A famous one.
She's playing too much. She's not even a lawyer.
You're saying that because you're not a lawyer, right?
That's why you can't reveal my innocence.
You're on your way to Oh Gyeonghwan's trial, aren't you?
This is the last warning. Take your hands off it.
- Cha Geum Joo?
- What's with you?
You're under arrest for the violation of the Attorney-at-Law Act.
Have you done rape?
Of course.
Is it true that you asked sexual favors from Kim Yoori?
Everyone, your life's companion is not far away.
It's right beside...
Hey!
Can you make it an innocent verdict?
Of course. You need to receive an innocent verdict.
Cha Geum Joo.
Paralegal Cha?
That's right! It's nice to hear you being polite.
But why did you bring me here?
To brag about your real estate?
That fear of exams... Do you think you can overcome it?
What I'm asking you right now is, can you become a lawyer?
If so, this law firm will be yours.
You're giving me this law firm?
To be exact, I'm telling you to be in charge of it.
Think about it.
Why?
Why me of all people?
I was in two lawsuits with a certain person.
One time, I lost because of that person.
The other time, I survived because of that person.
You probably know who that is.
Is that all the reason you have?
Well... Do I need more?
You can choose the representative lawyer
who will be in charge of the firm
until you get your lawyer's badge. You can take of the rest slowly.
Of course... I'd have
to accept it, right?
It's good that you
answered right away.
No. I have fast intuition.
With a proposition like this, it's one of two options.
There must be something fishy about it or
Or?
Or you have fallen for me.
Right now, let's just say I've fallen for you.
Can you not live in this neighborhood without a car?
Oh my! Who could this be?
Why are you here?
Why else? I came to meet a client.
Client? Who?
Why? Are you going to intercept?
You can be honest with me.
Did you come here as a housekeeper?
Even housekeepers here get a big daily wage. Cheer up!
In this whole country, the only person who can find the culprit is
you, Ham Bok Geo.
A young boy's future is hanging on this
and the only person who can help him
is just you, Ham Bok Geo.
You're asking what's in here?
Why is it so packed like I'm a solicitor?
Inside Joojoo are the evidence that I'm working hard.
My sweat and tears, my precious career.
It's also a place for my client to rest.
♪ Say that you love me first ♪
♪ So what if your face turns red ♪
♪ We need a keepsake ♪
JO EUN SEON: Starperlis Couple Murder Case
Woman with a Suitcase
Episode 3 Being Someone's Subordinate
Jo Eun Seon (DEFENDANT, CHARGED WITH MURDER)
I'll be right there so just wait.
(DOGUK-DONG STARPERLIS COUPLE MURDER CASE)
Your husband is here!
No...
Congratulations.
You've gotten the most handsome lawyer in Seocho-dong.
Tomy Kim
Right now, let's just say I've fallen for you.
K-fact is slowly becoming a bundle of lawsuits.
While I try to protect celebrities' secrets,
I've chosen you to resolve that.
Instead of getting drenched with rain
on the road while giving out flyers,
you need a job too.
Is my intention clear now?
Did you think I will just accept that?
Is that a no?
Since it seems like you're not used at being rejected,
let's say I'm considering it for now.
When he gets drunk, I got beaten to the point of death.
There was one time when he tied me up.
In front of me, he called a call girl and...
Can you prove it?
That he called a different woman.
If you look through my husband's phone record,
it will probably be there.
I will insist on the primary requirements of self-defense.
Primary requirements?
Yes. For victims of ongoing assault or sexual assault,
self-defense is possible as prevention before the impending assault.
Thank you.
Also, the autopsy result is out.
There were traces of being bound on his wrists.
Did you tie your husband up with something?
No.
Then, do you know how he got hurt?
My husband has a unique sexual preference so probably...
I understand what you're trying to say.
Ah! It's okay if you want to change your lawyer.
You probably has the financial freedom to
do so. If you want to designate a lawyer...
No.
Please just do it.
Then, I will do my best.
Jo Eun Seon Case Files
You look like something's not working out for you.
Should I help you?
I'm an expert in that field.
I liked her too but...
I guess we won't see each other again.
Lawyer Ma Seok Woo
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Hello, Paralegal Cha!
Why are you so surprised?
What are you doing here?
What else?
I'm cleaning my office.
Your office?
Why? Are we not working together then?
Oh my! What did I do?
Oh my!
Lawyer...
It's a welcome greeting.
Why did you have to be so aggressive?
Lawyer... What are you going to do about these?
That... I'll gradually...
Follow me.
Where are you going?
To do some gleaning.
Dream Law Firm
Excuse me.
How can I help you?
It's nothing.
By any chance,
do you need a consultation?
How did you know?
You went to petition for
bankruptcy but you were
scared to even open the law
firm's door, weren't you?
Yes. That's right!
You were scared that they will take money
from you when you already have none.
- Is that right?
- You're right!
That's right.
Our Ma Seok Woo's Law Firm will do your
bankruptcy petition for a shockingly cheap price.
Once we take your case, until you rebuild again... all the way!
Yes. Here you go. It's true.
You don't have to worry about anything in the future.
- Paralegal.
- Yes?
There's a case I want to discuss with you.
Ah, yes. Wait a second.
It's nothing big but it's a contract. It was sudden and...
Oh my. Such a waste of his face.
I know, right?
How can such a guy like that apply for bankruptcy?
Why are you here?
Ah! Did you come for the receipt?
No. I came to get her.
You're going to take my paralegal?
Lawyer, go ahead and give consultations to them.
Let's go out and talk.
Let's do that then.
Ah, the smell.
You're persistent.
First of all, you've succeeded in provoking my competitiveness.
Take it.
What is that?
There must be a cheque for a billion won in here.
It's a contract. Call me after reading it.
Wait! Are you not going to tell me what you're scheming?
I really don't want to go to prison again.
Cha Geum Joo, I won't let you go to prison.
I will give you a week.
Then...
Good bye.
You've worked hard.
By chance, is he hitting on you?
Well? I guess you can say it's something like that.
But why are men like that?
Why do men think that a woman's "No" means she's playing hard to get?
I know. Why do they all do that? I don't do that though.
If you're really bothered, you can report
him as a stalker... that's another way.
Ah...
There is that.
When I satisfy my first need, I'll have to do that.
You first need?
He hit on me twice.
If he comes looking for me again, he's a stalker.
I heard the Star Palace murder case will be a jury trial?
Are you sure it's my husband?
To where?
Motel?
How dare he cheat on me, Goo Ji Hyun?
How care he...
This is the case file on announcer Yoo Mi Ra's trial.
Pen.
What did you learn learn from Cha Geum Joo?
This. This!
Right here!
You get 0 points for the argument, and zilch for the evidence!
Did you only study English in Boston, not learn the work?
Or just date around?
Um... Sunbae, I'm sure it's a hassle for you,
but please teach me one thing at a time.
I heard you're the best attorney when it comes to divorce cases.
How dare you...
Paralegal.
Be quiet.
Here.
It bothers me that it's Ham Bok Geo.
There were lots of rumors about him when he quit being a prosecutor.
So, you want to stop me, right?
Yeah.
This guy right here is telling me again that
this doesn't feel good. Like last time.
How about the follow up interview on the man
Yoon Mi Ra's having an affair with? Announcer
Yoon Mi Ra Divorces in 7 years, Her affair
proven to be true, creates a huge stir
It's scheduled for this afternoon.
Bring in tons of things we can chew on. Spam
Why did she get a divorce?
Did you make your decision?
Yes.
You'll reject?
Thank you for your proposal.
Can I ask you the reason why?
You think I'm full of it, right?
Honestly, yes.
Perhaps I am.
But I know now.
All things have consequences.
Your proposed salary and conditions don't come free.
Don't expect me come back to you and ask again.
As you know, I'm not used to being rejected.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Feisty Team @ Viki
I took a look at the tie...
Our guess is that a cable tie was used.
A cable tie?
The one you use to tie up and organize electric cords?
Yes, you're right.
Don't you find that cable tie thing strange?
It's not like it's a scarf or handcuffs...
Don't you think? To call it a sexual preference...
Personally, I prefer handcuffs, but...
it's not like you can't use anything else.
We haven't confirmed them as cable tied yet.
It's just a guess.
Yeah...
I hope we find something very affective.
Good enough to move the jury's hearts.
But why aren't you opening that up?
Pardon? Where?
That envelope.
You know... the one that CEO Ham left you.
I just decided not to open it.
Is that so?
Because I like you, Attorney.
You mean it?
No way.
Paralegal, I beg you. Please don't joke around like that anymore.
You get me excited for no reason.
Oh, are you serious?
Of course not.
I have to go downstairs...
Attorney! Just a moment.
Yes, I'm coming.
Oh, no...
You think this is the murder evidence?
Her husband showed up with a hunting rifle,
so she had no choice but to push him and...
she used a pillow to suffocate him.
That's her
testimony, but it's too far
fetched compared to this.
Attorney, don't forget that we're Jo Eun Seon's defense.
Also the fact that we can't
change the argument that
it was in self defense due
to domestic violence.
But Jo Eun Seon lied to me, too.
Honestly, I don't know how much of it I can believe right now.
Attorney, you don't defend someone according to what you believe.
That's right. As you said...
Let's say the defendant tied her
sleeping husband with these cable ties.
But what does that have to do with you?
What do you mean?
Paralegal, there's a regulation that
say a lawyer shouldn't cover up truth
or make a false testimony.
Even if I'm her defense lawyer, I can
contemplate the truthfulness of the case.
How about a lawyer's ethics?
Even when the lawyer finds a disadvantageous truth to the defendant,
putting the defendant's benefit first,
you have no obligation to reveal that
disadvantageous truth to the client.
You know this, too.
But I think differently than you.
I believe I can defend only as much as I
believe. I must believe to defend the person.
We have the autopsy results right here. But...
if we deny even the fact that her husband was tied up...
Would the jury agree with that?
Until I can find the reason why Jo Eun Seon had to tie up her husband,
I'd like to deny her my strong defense.
I'll warn you as a paralegal.
Anything that would ruin your credentials...
Don't do anything like that.
This is my job, too.
Protecting you, Attorney.
Now that I see you...
everything seems so simple to you, Cha Geum Joo.
Now that I see you, you're...
very complicated in everything.
If you don't like this, change your occupation.
You can become a prosecutor even if you were a lawyer these days.
Did you get rejected again?
Is it... two outs thus far?
The formidable CEO Ham gets ousted twice already...
This is interesting.
I did expected it. She always...
exceeds my expectations.
But did you tell her the reason why you opened up a law firm?
Wouldn't it be better if you told her the details?
You also had to quit being a prosecutor over similar case and...
this homeless girl incident is extremely similar to that case.
So, you two can combine your strengths and...
can reveal the truth.
What if you open up everything to her like this?
Well? If she finds that out...
she might want to run away even more.
I guess... that could happen.
My proposal to Cha Geum Joo...
That case isn't the only reason why I asked her.
Excuse me?
How she'll survive from now on...
I started getting really curious.
Like the old me.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Feisty Team @ Viki
Let's go in.
Did you bring the cable tie by chance?
Oh, no. I left it inside the safe and completely forgot.
I've never been like this before.
I can go get it right now.
Oh, no... you know how Seochodong streets
are like a parking lot at this hour.
So, I was thinking, Attorney...
Let's go in. We'll be late for the trial.
Okay.
Witness, you're the victim's older sister, right?
Yes.
How was your brother and defendant Jo Eun Seon's relationship?
My brother was so good to her. He worked so hard and
that woman lived it up without having to work.
She said he didn't give her any home expenses.
Whenever she had money, she'd scoop
it all up and give it to her family.
I'm sure he didn't give her a huge amount of money.
Then, could there be a reason why
the defendant would want to kill your brother?
Probably because of her son.
Are you talking about your nephew who's studying abroad?
Yes.
If my brother died, the assets would
go to her son.
Instead of spending several years in prison,
she probably wants the assets to go to her son.
That's all.
Defense, cross examination?
No.
As a result of the autopsy, did she tie him up with the cable ties?
Yes, that's correct.
That's all.
Defense, would you like to cross examine?
No.
Attorney, you should object to this...
The victim was in a position where
he couldn't not fight off defendant Jo Eun Seon when he died.
No matter how threatened she felt the danger of violence,
the fact that she asphyxiated her husband while he slept...
You can't look at it and think the "Imminence of
the Threatened Attack" exists. Imminence of the
Threatened Attack - A condition necessary for justification
of self-defense, existence of impending danger
With that, I want to settle with the defense counsel.
For the defendant, I request 15 years for the crime of murder.
Please give her that sentencing.
Defense, present your final statement please.
Defense!
Defendant Jo Eun Seon...
...is guilty.
She had been struggling from domestic violence for a long time, but
she didn't ask for help from others.
So, she's guilty.
The defendant is guilty.
When Imminence of the Threatened Attack did not exist and
the crime took place at that time so she's guilty.
At the least, when her husband was holding a knife or a stick...
It wasn't at the moment when he's holding his fist up but
She's guilty for letting him die while he was sleeping.
And crucially...
the defendant is guilty.
Her husband's wrists...
His wrists...
were tied up with something and she hid
that fact. Therefore, she's guilty.
These are cable ties that are thought to
have been used to tie up her husband.
Maybe, as the prosecution insisted, this murder
didn't have the condition of Imminence of the Threatened Attack.
This is the defendant's medical records from three months ago. Here...
The same one that her husband did to the defendant,
it's that tie.
It's a record of diagnosis from 10 years ago.
It's the same trace here.
The idea of tying her husband in cable tie,
where did it come from?
I understood after finding these.
The reason why the defendant had no other
way to protect herself other than murder,
maybe more than the defendant's sin,
don't you think it's proof of her fear of her husband?
From Star Palace to the door of the house in Gurodong,
if you open the gate where you can
hear the sorrowful screams of a woman,
Jo Eun Seon, the domestic
violence victim who couldn't
find a rational way to run
away from her husband,
will be there.
To those women, I hope this case verdict...
doesn't become another ball and chains.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Feisty Team @ Viki
Why don't you talk to Attorney Park about my winning fee?
Shouldn't you win the case in order to receive that?
I should look up the contract again.
Didn't we just win our case?
I have to give up 700 million won of my money. What do you mean win?
Isn't this same thing as losing?
Um, Yoon Mi Ra, since it's been concluded
that both of you committed adultery...
you got to get the divorce you wanted.
So, it's not entirely a losing case.
I mean, you know...
But why did that wife of his follow him to the trial and do that?
Her husband clearly rejected her. Did
she have to hang onto him like that?
Seriously... she has no pride.
Did you see what she looked like?
Since she doesn't take care of herself...
no wonder her husband fell for me.
You know... you make a living with words.
Why don't you speak kind words?
Attorney, you're the one who make a living with words.
Why didn't you speak more clearly?
I asked you to clearly point out how
problematic his wife was as a woman.
Attorney! What are you doing! Let her go!
Do you really want me to cut off your meal ticket?
That's right! Go ahead, cut it off. Cut it off!
Cut it off!
I turned over your losing case
and won it for you. A home
wrecker like you should feel
sorry for what you did, yet...
how dare you dis his wife to the end?
Who started it? Did Yoon Mi Ra start it
to get a discount on her winning fee?
Then did Attorney Goo?
What's wrong with her these days? Do you know anything?
I think she's struggling a bit these days.
What are you talking about?
Well, I think she's having a hard time
controlling her emotions with her family issues.
Family issues?
I can't tell you in detail, but...
She's not doing a good
job of prepping for her
cases and even gets angry
at the clients easily...
I feel bad saying this, but I think you should at least know, CEO.
You have a talent at turning around a punch.
That wasn't my intention.
Do you think you can take over Attorney Goo's position from now on?
Thank you.
Oh, did you confirm that rumor?
Daebak! Yoon Mi Ra's hair?
Yeah, you know, like this and...
Omo, omo, omo...
Was it like this? She held her
like this and pulled then...
Dragged her back and forth...
And yank her hair like this and...
What? Why don't you continue?
Are you okay?
Oh, no... I just got fired.
Who'd like to work with me?
Why not? I may have a bad temper, but...
I do a great job. Don't I?
I think she's guilty. How could she
kill her husband? Jury Deliberation
I think she's innocent.
There are so many evidences that say she got beat up all this time.
By chance, could she have gone after
the money like the prosecutor said?
That's what I mean. You can't treat trash with trashy methods.
I mean, he called an escort when he had a wife.
It's more strange that she didn't stab
him to death. Don't you think so?
Did you reach a verdict, members of the jury?
Defendant
We, the jury, conclude that the defendant's
act was an act of self defense.
We agreed to give her a not guilty verdict.
The defendant Jo Eun Seon committed a cold-blooded
murder enough to shock the world, but
because the assault she endured for a long time was severe,
She will not be accounted for this case.
The members of the jury acknowledged it as self-defense
and gave a not guilty verdict but in the
court, to say that tying her husband's wrists
and killing him in his sleep is self-defense
is not acceptable.
However, considering various circumstances,
I sentence her to 1 year and 6 months.
Thank you.
You went through a lot.
Thank you, Attorney.
I came to say hello.
To say hello?
The attorney you used to work with, Attorney Goo, had to leave.
I guess the rumors of you throwing
yourself into the battle is true indeed.
Well? I can't tell you. I'm afraid you'd write an article about me.
I'm a little nervous.
I heard you were a very capable prosecutor.
You resigned because of a scandalous case but
Few cases you worked on are legendary.
Legendary? No...
I guess it's better than being known as the
doggone crazy prosecutor who abetted perjury.
Are you alright?
I'm not alright.
Your defense argument was very good.
Do you want to eat?
Now that I think about it, we skipped lunch because of the trial.
Then, I'm the first attorney...
who bought you dinner?
I didn't come as an Oh Seong client.
What do you mean by that?
Oh, I heard you studied media related cases
a lot in the States.
You know a lot about me.
Me removing the cable ties...
I thought you might make the wrong decision.
I shouldn't have done that.
I would've done the same thing.
My defense argument.
But you didn't trust me.
You even took away a chance for me to make the decision on my own.
With a partner who can't trust me...
how can I work with her?
I'm so sorry. I didn't think this through.
It's not that I didn't trust you.
For making you not trust me...
That upsets me more.
I think you and I can only go this far.
I...
will wander around some more alone.
Oh? It's my sister.
I don't think I should say hello seeing how the mood is.
I had no idea she had a man.
Thank you for everything.
♪ I couldn't sleep ♪
♪ in this quiet night ♪
Thank you. I shouldn't have drank the last glass.
♪ All of a sudden, ♪
♪ because of a lot of reasons, ♪
♪ I'm reminded of you ♪
♪ I'll tell you if you'd come, just as is,
right now, in front of me, not too late ♪
♪ I'll tell you if you'd
come closer, just as
is, in my embrace, before
this night is over ♪
♪ I need you, I need you ♪
♪ If you'd come as is before this night is over ♪
Fine! Go ahead and wander alone some more!
Geez!
Kim Soo Young, 1813785, Kim Eui Chan
You're the only person I can trust, Ahjussi. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. My dog must be thirsty.
Can I have some water from you?
Thank you!
CEO Lee.
Isn't that Cha Geum Joo?
She's come down a lot.
I heard you're opening up a law firm.
Is that why you wanted to see me?
I felt bad that we couldn't wrap up your
case well and the rumors were rampant...
Isn't it better to write an article
rather than issue an arrest warrant?
It's not that fun in our industry these days.
You don't practice law for fun.
This guy accepts my joke as truth. He's embarrassing me.
I'm joking, too.
The economy in Seochodong
these day's isn't that
great. The paparazzi media
is a hundred times better.
Actually, I'm still thinking about it.
As you know, I've had a lot of headaches.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Feisty Team @ Viki
Yes.
That guy...
It's pretty refreshing to see you this way.
Oh, this is on the house. Their specialty is octopus sushi.
If you're trying to be considerate not to embarrass me..
you don't have to go to that extent.
Oh, this one, too.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Hye Joo
Isn't that your older sister?
Pardon?
Over there.
Unnie!
Hye Joo...
You had to quit over that?
You should've begged him a bit. A newbie
like him is perfect for you right now.
So, what are you going to do now?
By chance, do you know of any law firms you can introduce me to?
I'm fine with a team leader position as well.
How could there be?
You're a paralegal with flaws. Like me a long time ago.
Because what you said to me then, I worked really hard to overcome it.
And I've come back this far.
I hope you overcome it on your own.
I will look into it, but it won't be easy.
Oh, I should go. Bye.
Hye Joo!
Unni!
Sorry. You were worried, huh?
You said you won't run away this time.
How about your bar exam ID? Where is your ID?
What's this? Cha Geum Joo
I got a job!
Unni!
You should go to law school.
What are you talking about? How can I afford to go to college?
I found a job.
I'll take care of your tuition.
Unni...
What did I do so wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong.
If I were to pick one out, the fact
that you tried to have everything.
Money, husband, humanity, sense of justice...
Cha Geum Joo... I told you to take it easy.
What's going on at this hour?
Spam
Yes?
Can we meet?
I believe we have no reason to meet.
I have something to ask you.
What now?
Are you rejecting me?
I want to ask you what you want to ask me.
I'll give you one chance.
Thank you.
Too early to thank me. Come to my office in an hour.
Alright then.
My hair...
Is this what you wanted?
To make me stare at you?
What would you do if I rejected you because I'm not confident enough?
Actually, I'm not... confident enough to pass the bar.
Bar is different from taking a midterm. If I don't pass...
I took that exam, too.
There was pressure, too.
I'm saying you're not the only one who went through that.
No, you don't know, Ham Bok Geo.
What fear of failing means to me.
It must be scary since the punishment is so scary.
Didn't you see that contract?
I thought... you got scared after reading that and rejected me.
What is that?
Do you want to know?
Yes.
Oh, my!
What are you doing?
It's not bad, right?
I was more scared of getting flicked
with my fingers than taking the exam.
Are you that a**hole's family or relative?
Why is a public defender coming over here
asking for a settlement and whatnot?
Settlement? I can never settle.
I'll throw that a**hole in jail for sure.
Alright, then I'll see you in court.
And before you come, please read this.
What's this?
Oh, um... excuse me...
Contract
What? It's not enough?
If you need, I can comfort you, too. Like this.
I thought it was a pretty good offer.
Article 2, what the heck is this exactly?
Acquired goods should attend events that the owner demands of it...
and accompany the owner.
You said you're a companion.
Anyway, what's "owner" and "acquired goods?"
An owner and servant?
Don't you think it's better than gap-eul
relationship? (SUPERIOR AND INFERIOR PARTY)
I purposely changed it because you suddenly said no.
Fine, let's leave it at that.
On article 3, item 3...
When the owner calls for the goods, within an hour if in the city...
or within five hours if in the country,
should show up at the designated location.
I mean, will you buy the whole world for me or something?
It's the KTX generation.
This the most horrendous one.
The goods must study things the owner requires such as...
foreign languages, working out, musical instruments, cooking, wine,
needs to complete related programs to these.
I mean, why should I do that?
My attorney's dignity is same as mine.
I've been around the block more than once in
Seochodong for more than ten years, but...
I've never seen such a ridiculous contract before.
I guess you don't object to my offer of the
investment, transportation, and meals.
Then sign there and go.
Who says I'm going to sign it?
I thought you had no where to go.
I have no place to go, but I have lots to do.
I see. So?
Fine. But I have a condition.
Take it off! Take it off! You being
old isn't something to be proud of.
We're all working here. How can you bother others like this?
I'm sorry. I'll do a good job.
It's a problem because you're no good!
What do you mean he can't do no good?
This man is an extremely high class worker.
I'm begging him, so I can scout him.
Golden Tree Law Firm
Golden Tree! Yay! Golden Tree!
I've moved to a new law firm this time.
Please help me out from now on.
Ah, yes. Thank you! Goodbye!
Who's the leader of the law firm?
Our Paralegal Cha isn't an attorney.
I thought someone was coming by today.
What brings you here?
I'm here for a job interview.
I think you're mistaken.
You asked her? Are you crazy?
Go out.
- Is this a payback?
- Why don't you have a seat?
Why? Did you want to check?
Yes.
Whether you wanted to work with me or not.
Fine then.
- Shall we talk about the offer first?
- Tell me what you want.
I need a car. Of course, including a chauffeur.
500 million won minimum for my salary
guaranteed. Incentive 30% on profit.
More than that, the most important thing is...
could you endure my temper?
I guess I will.
Right now, we need an attorney license, CEO.
Why did you call me?
- Why don't you keep your promise?
- What?
When the owner calls for the goods, within an hour if in the city...
or within five hours if in the country,
should show up at the designated location.
I think you're 31 minutes late.
I don't think I signed the contract yet.
You didn't forget my condition, right?
I'll ask you once more. Do you really need that?
If you bring in Attorney Ma...
I'll sign this contract.
What are you going to do with that newbie?
Such a naive lawyer isn't helpful at all.
No, I absolutely need him.
A naive lawyer who focuses on his original passion.
Me and Attorney Goo are enough to fill in as the experienced ones.
I need someone who'd sit on the opposite end of the seesaw.
For the balance of Golden Tree.
Is that really the only reason?
Yes.
Why do you need me?
I never said I needed you.
You made me an offer.
Cha Geum Joo said she needed you.
I'm sorry, but forget it if it pertains to that.
An attorney should hire the paralegal. Not the other way around.
It's fortunate. Thanks for saying no.
I was worried that you'd jump up and come to us.
I think Cha Geum Joo misunderstands your lack of talent as innocence.
You... if you eat this and don't take responsibility...
I'll sue you.
Please help all the cases the Golden Tree takes on.
So, that we can set a 100% winning record.
Yay!
Hamburger
Yes, Ham Bok Geo?
Right now?
Calling me to come and go...
You even tell me what to wear.
You shouldn't have signed it if you don't like it.
The contract... can we change it a bit?
You're the one who inspired
me on the part about
the companion. You were
the original companion.
Should you tell your companion where we're going at least?
This is for the profit of the law firm. Let's not whine and go.
♪ My forever companion ♪
♪ The best gift in my life was ♪
♪ Meeting you ♪
♪ Living well ♪
Grace Bazaar, Sponsored by Oh Sung Group, 9-30-2016
Hello, Madam. I'm Paralegal Cha Geum Joo from Golden Tree.
Please take good care of me from now on.
Whenever we have an event, a fly like that flies in here.
That's why we put together the event. Please endure.
Please pay special attention to us.
I feel like I've seen that woman before.
It's Cha Geum Joo.
Golden Tree of Seochodong.
But what's her relationship with the K-fact CEO?
I'm Paralegal Cha Geum Joo of Golden Tree.
Please pay special attention to us from now on.
- Hello. I'm Paralegal Cha Geum Joo of Golden Tree.
- Ah...
Golden Tree... Nice to meet you.
Oh, my... the bags are so nice.
I'll buy this one.
You have a good taste.
Let's get together one of these days.
I'd love that.
I should be helpful to you since you're doing good work.
- Oh, this is so pretty, too.
- Isn't it?
Let's go.
Thank you.
Even if you have to die, don't die tonight.
I won't let you tire me out anymore.
Thank you.
Cha Geum Joo. Cha Geum Joo.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Feisty Team @ Viki
Cha Geum Joo! Cha Geum Joo!
Cha Geum Joo! Cha Geum Joo! Cha Geum Joo!
♪ I'll tell you if you'd come ♪
♪ just as is, right now, in front of me, not too late ♪
♪ I'll tell you if you'd come closer ♪
♪ just as is, in my embrace ♪
Woman with a Suitcase
What's with your sister getting stabbed in place of Ham Gok Geo?
What's the nature of their relationship?
Get better soon. I'm not paying you to rest up in the hospital.
Don't be too happy. Even then...
you can't even leave a case record under your name.
That's why you should come soon, Attorney Ma.
You really don't want to share the case?
Make it clear whether you're in or out.
Stop roaming around Cha Geum Joo. You're making me worry.
Holding naturally like that from earlier...
- It's my wrist.
- I know.
- Why don't we stop?
- That won't work.
I have no intention of letting you go.