[Uncontrollably Fond]
Subtitles by DramaFever
- Come on, get over here.
- Ow, ow, ow!
Let's go and tell your mom to vomit
up the seaweed soup she had
after she gave birth to a sorry
excuse for a son like you!
That makes no sense!
Come on. How is she going to vomit up
something she ate over 30 years ago?
You bastard!
It's not like Joon Young committed
murder, or sold out our country!
Why did you lock up a kid who's sick,
causing all this trouble?
If it hadn't been for Joon Young,
you'd be living under a bridge!
You ungrateful bastard!
I'm doing this for him!
What the hell did you just say?
Do you even know where Joon Young
is trying to go, right now?
He wants to go to the detention center
where PD No Eul is being held!
- What?
- Exactly!
PD No Eul is at the detention center
right now for trying to hit Assemblyman
Choi Hyun Joon with a car, and she's
being charged with attempted murder!
Mom.
Those bastards.
How dare they keep you locked up
when you're this sick?
Hey, get up.
Let's get you to the hospital.
Hurry!
Come on!
All right, let's go.
Let's get you to the hospital.
I have to go to Eul, Mom.
Please, help me.
I have to go right now.
Please, help me, Mom.
Mom!
What... did you just say?
Did you just say Choi Hyun Joon?
Yeah!
This woman tried to kill an assemblyman!
If she acts like she's close with Joon
Young and he suffers backlash for it
what will we do then?
That's why I locked him up in his room!
Happy now?
Um...
I don't quite understand
what you're saying.
The... assemblyman's name...
is Choi...
Choi Hyun Joon?
Are you sure about that?
Help me.
N-no. No.
No!
What are you saying, when
you're in this terrible state?
Mom.
Sit still, and don't go anywhere.
I'll go and buy some medicine for you.
About Mr. Choi Hyun Joon...
If you'd just stayed by his side...
he never would've degenerated
into who he is now.
If you hadn't run away,
had stayed by his side...
he never would've become
such a vile human being!
This is all your fault, Mom.
This is all your fault, Mom!
You're the one who made
things end up this way!
Everything is your fault, Mom!
This is all your fault, Mom!
You crazy bastard!
What the hell did you say? Huh?
How dare you!
Are you out of your damn mind?
Hey. Do you know what your mother
went through to raise you? Huh?
Do you know what lengths she went to
to make sure that nobody
would call you a bastard child?
And thanks to her sacrifices,
you've grown up well!
So is that really something
you should be saying to her?
- Jung Shik.
- You rotten punk.
Do you even know what your
mother is going through, right now?
You call yourself her son?
Leave.
Do you really think I'll stand
for your diva nonsense?
Do you think you're above everything,
now that you're a hotshot?
Bastard.
If you were my child, I would've
already beaten you to a pulp--
I told you to get out, Jang Jung Shik.
Leave.
If you make your mother
shed any tears, you punk
I'll make sure that you'll be
crying tears of blood! Got that?
Just remember that.
Geez.
I'll go buy you some medicine.
I'm going to go there
even if I have to crawl.
If you won't help me, I'll go to Eul
somehow, even if I have to crawl to her.
Young Ok.
Eul.
Joon Young!
What took you so long?
Don't you know how long
I waited for you?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I... I wasn't trying to kill him!
I promise! I wasn't trying
to kill Choi Hyun Joon!
I was really going to forget everything
and live my life as if I were dead!
I know.
I'm so scared, Joon Young.
Why are you scared,
when I'm right here?
- Let's go.
- Where?
We were supposed to go on
a trip together, remember?
Let's go, and come back in ten years.
Let's go.
Right now?
Yeah.
Right now.
Let's spend a century here
before we go back to reality.
Let's hide in a place
where nobody will find us...
and spend just a century there,
before we head back.
Your food is already cold.
I'll go and heat it up again.
So?
He hasn't eaten anything
yesterday or today?
That's not the problem. He doesn't
even look like he's breathing!
What are we going to do if
Joon Young dies at this rate?
Wow. A guy dying because of some girl?
Looks like I'll have to
bring a shovel over later.
Tell him to wait. I'll come and shove
food into that stubborn mouth of his.
Geez!
Geez.
Jik!
Why are you here?
You said you have an exam today!
I just left in the middle of it.
Figures. I'm sure that you couldn't
focus on a test right now.
Damn it, if only Hyun Woo were around!
I'm sure that he'd know some attorneys
since he stayed at that
student hostel for a while!
Damn it, where did he disappear to?
Who knows?
Tell both Hyun Woo and
Shin Joon Young to piss off!
We can just take care of our
own business ourselves.
But...
What if my Big Sis cries?
I've never seen my sister cry, ever.
If I were to see her cry now...
I think it'd drive me insane.
What should I do?
We're making an exception this time,
so consider yourselves lucky.
Thank you.
A middle-aged lady came in
really early this morning.
Apparently, she ran off with a
wad of someone else's cash.
But you know... you know
Mario Lee, the director, right?
She looks just like him!
Like, she totally looks like him!
I was totally shocked!
You think that you should
be laughing at a time like this?
Yeah, I shouldn't be laughing
right now, in my state.
So I said, "Oh, it's Mario Lee!
What brings you here?"
- Isn't that hilarious?
- Big Sis.
Oh. Do you not know
Mario Lee, Mr. Grandpa?
You know, the guy who dances
like this. You don't know him?
Big Sis!
You know him, right, Na Ri?
You know, the guy who dances like this!
Why are you acting like that?
You're being so embarrassing!
That's not how it goes, at all!
Mario Lee dances like this, duh!
Like this, all right?
You're right!
That's how it goes!
Like this, right?
Hey, loosen up, punk!
I'm not on my deathbed, here.
I'll be out of here soon, so just find
a place that makes great tofu stew--
Big Sis. You didn't really try to kill
that assemblyman, right?
Of course...
not.
I knew it.
All right, then.
I heard that Joon Young was there, too.
So how come he hasn't
even been here once?
He should testify as a witness,
saying you had no murderous intent--
I told you not to bring
that damn bastard up.
Jik went to go and see him,
to ask him to help you.
But apparently, he didn't even
open his door for him.
Don't trust that bastard, Big Sis.
I'll take care of everything.
I'll clear your name, and...
Student, you should go
to school and study.
Big Sis.
Also, I just heard from Joon Young.
He said that he'd come and get me soon.
He might already be on his way by now!
Shin Joon Young...
Is going to his parking lot, right now.
He's getting into his car.
He's starting the car.
The car is moving.
He has 59 kilometers remaining
until he gets here.
58 kilometers.
This is your mother's spicy beef stew
that you wanted to eat so badly.
Eat just one spoonful, at least!
If you're planning to protest
by starving yourself, forget about it.
I'm not to let you out, even if that
means starving you to death!
That's what your mother told me to do.
How is that not a day goes by
without some mishap?
I was just waiting for it to happen.
Here, put this on your finger.
Hey, why did you cut your finger if you
can't even put a band-aid on properly?
- Huh?
- Ow.
You need to be focused when
you have a knife in your hand!
About Mr. Choi Hyun Joon...
If you'd just stayed by his side
he never would've degenerated
into who he is now.
If you hadn't run away,
had just stayed by his side...
he never would've become
such a vile human being!
Young Ok.
Young Ok!
Where are you going, Young Ok?
What brings you here, without any notice?
Please release PD No Eul.
Do you have feelings for that woman?
Since when?
From the moment that you started
hiding the truth to Mother
and ruined that girl's life.
Really?
You've always been a compassionate
child, since you were young.
Even if you were walking by
and saw someone crying
you'd ask them, "why are you crying?
How can I help you?"
Father.
But you have far too much to lose in this
case if you were to wage everything
for the sake of that compassionate
streak of yours, don't you think?
I'm not scared.
All right, then.
Then, go outside right now
and shout this to the world.
"Choi Hyun Joon received a request he
couldn't refuse when he was a prosecutor"
"and covered up a terrible
hit-and-run accident."
"Furthermore, Lee Eun Soo agreed with
doing this, and ruined a girl's life."
"And in exchange for that, two people
got everything they could ever want"
"and are shamelessly showing that off."
"Those two people are my parents!"
Go and tell that to everyone!
What, you can't do it?
If you can't muster the
courage to do that
keep your mouth shut,
and become a coward.
Just like me, a long time ago.
Sheesh, I'm so upset!
I was actually just
about to contact you.
It seriously looks like
he'll die, at this rate!
He won't sleep at all,
or drink any water!
He won't even eat your spicy beef stew!
I'm so upset!
What about that person?
What did he do, huh?
Do you know what a great man he is?
You couldn't possibly compare
people like us to him!
So how dare you... who told
you that kind of nonsense, huh?
Tell me their name! I'll rip their
lips off, so tell me their name!
Tell me their name, punk!
I saw it myself.
What?
I saw it with my own eyes.
I saw for myself...
just how much of a miserable, selfish,
violent person Choi Hyun Joon is.
Why did you love a scummy guy, Mom?
I'm sure that you
mistook someone else for him.
You probably made a mistake!
That man is the type of person who
gives poor people everything he has
even if he can't eat what he wants to
because he has no money.
When everyone treated me
like crap because I'm uneducated
he hid the fact that he's a law
school student until the very end
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
and said that he was poor and uneducated
so I wouldn't feel bad about myself!
He was so generous and
considerate toward me!
Mom.
Eul's father...
died due to a hit-and-run accident.
Why are you bringing that up now?
And Mr. Choi Hyun Joon, who was
the Chief Prosecutor at the time...
was so focused on
becoming more successful
that he framed someone else as
the perpetrator of that crime.
What?
I thought that she'd gotten
over that incident
and that she'd forgotten about it since
a lot of time has passed since then.
But Eul still remembered.
I thought that she was completely
over that incident by now...
but it turns out that Eul is still
living in hell, being haunted.
And Mr. Choi Hyun Joon,
who caused all this...
had completely forgotten about
the incident altogether.
And he's pretty much living in heaven.
That's not right, Mom.
Such things should never happen. Right?
Jung Shik was right.
You've become crazy for that gold-digger
and you're not in your right mind.
Mom!
That man is the coolest, greatest,
most wonderful man in this whole world.
He's a great man that a bastard like
you could never hope to measure up to!
You crazy bastard!
You don't know anything!
Also, how dare you call him
"Mr. Choi Hyun Joon?"
- He's your father!
- And then!
I almost killed Eul.
I acknowledged such a
disgusting man as my father
and I was trying to help him
cover that up.
And in doing so, I almost killed Eul.
So...
is that why you dropped
out of school, too?
Is that why...
you said that you have no right
to become a prosecutor?
And that you were rotten
to the core from the start?
Yeah.
How could I accuse others of committing
crimes, after doing such a thing?
On his way here,
he was held up by his fans.
So he was delayed by
two hours and thirty minutes.
And then, the traffic light
broke on his way here...
so he was delayed for another
hour and 50 minutes.
And then, he ran out of gas
so he had to go and refuel.
And he had to get an oil change, too.
And since he was there already,
he got his car washed, too.
He has 43 more kilometers left to go.
42.9 kilometers left.
42.8 kilometers left.
How could something like this happen?
Um, I have such great hearing that
I heard your entire conversation.
That's why I'm planning to let
Joon Young out after I drop you off.
If I leave a punk with his temper alone
like that, he might just end up dying.
I heard you won't be able to see her
even if you try to go visit her now.
My name is Shin Joon Young.
Is Assemblyman Choi Hyun Joon home?
Is he not home?
No, he's not home right now.
He came home not long ago, though.
What is it?
Did someone come?
- No, nobody--
- Joon Young is here, Dad!
Ow! That hurts, Mom!
What do you mean, Joon Young?
It's nothing. I think they came to
the wrong house by accident.
Go in and study, already.
Now!
By Joon Young...
does she mean that Shin Joon Young
that Ha Ru likes so much?
Yeah! That's right, Dad!
But, why would Shin Joon Young
come to our house?
I'm sorry. We can't just allow anyone
to see the assemblyman, you see.
I'm sorry for dropping by
without any prior notice.
Have you had dinner?
Yes.
Go to your room, Honey. And you too,
Ha Ru. Go to your room and study.
I'm going to speak with our guest,
so don't come anywhere near my office.
Please come this way.
I'm not imagining things, right, Mom?
Joon Young really came
to our house, right?
Ha Ru. Can you support me, please?
You don't look that great.
Have you been sick?
Yes. I've been sick.
Oh my.
So, why did come here so late
at night, when you're ill?
Is it because of PD No Eul?
Yes.
That's what I assumed.
But, attempted murder
is not a petty charge
so this won't all be solved just
because I cancel my lawsuit against her.
I'm sure that you're aware of that
much too, Mr. Shin Joon Young.
I found out that she was merely
being charged for reckless driving
but the charge was changed
to attempted murder within the week.
Why did you change your mind?
Because it's a fact
that she meant to kill me.
And why would she try to kill you?
I'm curious about that myself.
I heard that she is maintaining
her right to remain silent
so can you go and
ask her for me, please?
Ask her why she tried to kill me.
If she'd really meant to kill you
she would've had many chances
to take your life the past five years.
If she'd really meant to kill you,
she wouldn't have swerved away from you.
- Look here, Mr. Shin Joon Young!
- Of course, if I were her...
I definitely wouldn't have swerved.
Yong Deuk.
Can you tell the hospital
I'll be sending a patient their way, so
they should stay open for a bit longer?
It's a shame that I can't
help you even though
you, a famous star, took time out of
your busy schedule to come see me.
Oh, also, thank you again for going
as far as to get hurt to save me--
I regret doing that.
I harbor no ill will toward you.
I can't explain it, exactly.
But would you believe me if I told you
I feel strangely close to you, somehow?
My daughter is a huge fan of yours, too.
So please, let's have a meal
together sometime--
What's this?
I'd like it...
if we'd never have to
see each other again.
I'd like it...
if today is the last day
we ever see each other.
What brings you here?
I came to blackmail
Assemblyman Choi Hyun Joon.
Well?
Did you succeed?
I'm not sure.
Yes, Detective Im.
It's me.
- About that girl, No Eul--
- You can't!
You can't let that damned girl go free!
If you do, she'll just try
to kill you again!
Honey!
You're Choi Hyun Joon!
You can't succumb to the threats of
some lowlife like Shin Joon Young!
Please, honey!
If Eul had taken that flash drive to
a broadcasting company five years ago...
If only you hadn't taken that
flash drive from her five years ago...
Hey, stop right there!
If we'd just received the punishment
that we deserved back then...
If everyone just received the punishment
that they deserved back then...
Eul would be living a
completely different life now.
That's why you don't
deserve her, either!
You have no right to be by her side
and smile beside her, either
and you have no right to have
her make you happy, either!
You have no right, just like me!
Because you can't help the fact that you
are Choi Hyun Joon's son, just like me.
Eul!
That was hard on you, wasn't it?
No, it was fine. It was fun,
thanks to that Mario Lee lady.
Stupid girl.
Here, eat this.
Make sure you don't go anywhere near
Choi Hyun Joon from now on, okay?
Are you waiting for someone?
Are you waiting for Shin Joon Young?
I told you, that bastard isn't coming!
If he was coming at all,
he would've come sooner!
Why isn't Jik here yet?
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Ow!
Oh no! Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
[Na Ri]
The person you're trying to reach
is unavailable.
Why isn't Jik picking up?
I told you, Joon Young isn't coming!
Stop waiting for him!
You still don't get it?
He's avoiding you
because he doesn't want to be associated
with someone who went to jail!
I'll just wait for him for ten minutes.
Hey!
This won't do.
Let's go home.
Tell Jik to come home, too.
Come on, let's go.
- Come on, hurry!
- Let go!
- Jik!
- Big Sis!
- What happened? Are you hurt?
- What happened?
- No, I'm fine.
I just sprained it a little.
I'm sorry. I got a bit distracted
while driving, and didn't see him.
I'm really all right, Big Sis!
What about you?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I told him we should get him
checked at the hospital
but he insisted on coming here.
I'm really sorry.
Secretary Kim really isn't the
type to make such mistakes.
Something terrible could've happened.
If she'd stepped on the
brakes just a bit later...
Oh, I don't even want to think about it.
PD No Eul was released this morning.
As for the engagement party,
we've scheduled it for 4:30 p.m.
Go!
What... is all this? Huh?
You told everyone not to come
yet you were just drinking and playing
games instead of eating, this whole time?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I really messed up.
If you tell me, "I don't want to
see your damn face, so go and die"
I can just die right
here and now, for you.
But I regret nothing.
I think that I've fulfilled my duty
by keeping you safe and sound
without a scratch on you,
amidst all this craziness.
You call this "keeping him safe
and sound?" Huh? As if!
I took this ailing, dying child,
mustered some courage
and brought him back to life!
But look at him.
He's only playing video games.
Geez. Oh, yeah.
Hey.
I heard that PD No Eul was freed today,
and all charges were dropped.
Aren't you going?
- Ow!
- Why would our Joon Young go there?
But still, he should go!
He was so desperate to see her!
As if!
If Eul had taken that flash drive to a
broadcasting company five years ago...
If only you hadn't taken that
flash drive from her five years ago...
If everyone just received the punishment
that they deserved back then...
If only we'd paid the price for
the crimes that we committed...
Eul would be living a
completely different life now.
- Hey!
- You little punk!
I'll kill you today!
- Joon Young?
- Joon Young!
That's why you don't
deserve her, either!
You have no right to be by her side
and smile beside her, either
and you have no right to have
her make you happy, either!
You have no right,
just like me!
Because you can't help the fact that you
are Choi Hyun Joon's son, just like me.
How dare you come here?
What mess are you going to get
Joon Young involved in this time?
Joon Young isn't going to
play with you anymore.
So go on and piss off,
while I'm still being nice about it.
No.
W-what?
I'm saying that I'm
not going to piss off.
I'm not going to come
and go as you please.
Joon Young didn't even come
to see you once, right?
I'm sure that you know
Joon Young well enough
to know that nothing would've
stopped him if he wanted to see you.
I mean, he certainly has
the means to do so.
I'm sure you've realized the nature
of the situation, if you're not an idiot.
Joon Young got drunk and
confessed the truth last night.
He said that people shouldn't love
someone out of feelings of loyalty.
He also said, "I'm sure that
damn girl is going to come see me
and cling to me when
she gets released."
"Just thinking about that makes
me feel sick to my stomach."
Liar.
[Na Ri]
This is Na Ri.
Go Na Ri.
There's something I'm curious about.
Why didn't you come by
even once to visit Eul?
Just because.
"Just because?"
How... how could you do that to Eul?
She waited so much for you!
Sorry, Na Ri...
I can't really talk for a long time--
I don't want to talk to you
for a long time either, you bastard!
I should've kept Eul from going!
What are you saying?
Where is Eul going?
Stop crying, and talk properly!
Go Na Ri!
I was hoping that we'd
never see each other again.
Do you remember when
I told you after the trial
that I never wanted to see you again,
and I wanted to end our bad relationship?
So why didn't you listen?
Why are you still hanging around me?
Did you want to test me to see
just how far I'll go?
Your younger brother is quite
clever and respectable.
He seems like the type of little brother
who could grow up to be someone great
and take care of you,
as long as you heed my command.
[Shin Joon Young]
What do you want, so late at night?
Wow.
Congratulations on your engagement,
my daughter!
Thanks, Dad.
They say that one's first love
usually ends in failure.
This is all thanks to you.
I'll never forget this favor
you've done for me!
Choi Ji Tae, who my daughter
is getting engaged to today
is my daughter's first love.
Others say that it's a marriage of
convenience for the two families
but none of that is true!
Dad, why are you saying that?
Her friends wrote "lawyer," "doctor," or
"famous pianist" as their aspirations
my daughter wrote...
What did you write, again?
"Choi Ji Tae's wife."
Yes, you did! She's a fool who's
loved one man for almost 20 years!
Oh, I'm so nervous.
I feel like I'm going to go
crazy because I'm so nervous!
Dad, you don't have an
anxiety reliever on you, do you?
What are you doing?
Aren't you getting in?
You're really not going to tell me?
What happened that you're running
away without even telling Na Ri?
What, did the loan sharks say that
they'd kill you if you didn't pay them?
There's no time.
Hurry and get in.
How can we leave Mom and Dad
behind in this country, and go?
How are you going to get by overseas
when your English is terrible?
What are you going to eat?
- Even so, it's better than here.
- What?
No matter where we go
it'll be a thousand times better
than this crappy place!
No Eul!
If you're not coming with me,
I'll go by myself.
Big Sis.
Please go to Incheon
International Airport, Mister.
Who the hell is that crazy bastard?
Hey!
You can't go anywhere.
Get out of there right now, No Eul!
What?
This one doesn't work, either?
Why are you asking me,
when you already know?
Don't you have any cash on you?
Of course I do.
I'm sure I do.
What kind of lawyer doesn't
even have 10,000 won on them?
Sheesh.
You can pay for his tab with this.
- Um, who are you--
- You're Lawyer Cha Taek Joong, right?
Yes, I am, but... who are you?
You were the prosecutor during the trial
for Mr. No Jang Su's hit-and-run in 2006.
Who are you?
Who was the real
perpetrator of the hit-and-run...
who Chief Prosecutor
Choi Hyun Joon protected?
Subtitles by DramaFever