[Uncontrollably Fond]
Subtitles by DramaFever
That girl seemed to have been
heading for a bridge near the Han River.
What are you going to do if she
already went and drowned herself?
A bridge on the Han River, my ass.
Why did I actually believe Gook Young?
I'm such an idiot.
One, two, three!
Holy crap! It's Joon Ho and Lee Yo Bi!
I guess their on-screen
chemistry in their movie
transferred over to real life!
Looks like the heavens haven't
forsaken me yet, after all!
Should we take it again?
One, two...
Do you really take living
for granted that much?
Is it that easy for you
to choose death?
Fine, let's shoot that documentary.
Let's shoot the thing, you psycho!
- Get the defibrillator ready.
- Yes, sir.
All right. One, two, go!
One more time.
One, two, go!
- Her pulse is back.
- Okay.
She's no longer in critical condition,
and the surgery ended well.
Your sister isn't going to die,
so you don't need to worry.
- Thank you, Doctor!
[Dear citizens, thank you! I'll be
sure to work hard, and stay humble!]
[A clean strength,
the future's strength: Choi Hyun Joon]
You're going to drop out?
- Yes.
- But, why?
You've even passed the first round
of exams. Why now, all of a sudden?
I feel that if a guy like me
were to become a prosecutor
there really would be
no hope left for this country.
[January, 2016]
This... is me?
Wow, the power of makeup
really is spectacular!
Wait. Since we're
getting you all dressed up
should I put some gold leaf under your
eyes, like those girl group members do?
As if. Gold leaf? It's not like
we're rolling in money!
Hey! Why are you wiping it off? I worked
hard all morning to put makeup on you!
You want me to go see
Shin Joon Young looking like this?
Yeah!
Are you trying to get me
to seduce him, or something?
I'm going to see him
for work-related reasons!
Yes, go ahead and work,
Ms. No Eul.
It's not like he's the type to be
seduced easily, anyway.
Shin Joon Young has swarms of rich girls
much prettier than you around him
and there are even more girls
who've taken a number and are
waiting for their chance with him.
Someone like you doesn't stand
a chance against girls like that.
So why do you want me
to put on makeup, then?
Joon Young is way out of our league now,
but I don't want
you to make a fool out of yourself
by wearing worn-out clothes near him.
Who cares if I look pathetic?
I don't care what he thinks.
Well, I do, all right?
My pride won't allow it.
I mean, we were once his peers.
I don't want those memories
to seem pathetic now.
Where's your gold leaf?
Bring it over. Sprinkle it all over me!
Damn, I just perfected
these muscles too.
What a shame.
Joon Young!
Come out here!
Why?
That Ms. Face-in-a-plate-of-water is
here, but she looks so ridiculous!
Let's go!
Wow, she's really going all-out
to make a good impression on you!
Why do I feel so bad for her, though?
Is it because I know that she'll still be
rejected by Shin Joon Young anyway?
If you just leave her out there, the
neighbors will call the police on her.
What the heck is she doing
instead of coming in?
Wait. Can you go get Pororo?
The more I look, the more it's
becoming clear that I look gorgeous!
Eul, life must have been so hard
for you to hide your beauty for so long!
Sorry. I kept you waiting, right?
So why did you tell me to wait
instead of going in?
Take off your earrings.
I felt bad for giving you fakes.
I had a friend lend me the real deal!
- What?
- Give me your ear.
Ow. Hey.
Guys like Joon Young can tell right away
whether you're wearing fakes or not.
Whatever! Who cares if they're fakes?
It'll be utter humiliation for you!
He might even think that
you're a big fake, too.
He's going to treat me like crap
no matter what I do, okay?
He has a nasty temper!
Honestly, the way he tormented me before
is nothing compared to now!
Wow. Joon Young lives alone
in a huge house like this?
Even just looking at the front door
is making me lose my resolve.
Hey, don't be scared, okay? It's not
like he's the only one with a temper!
You've got quite a nasty one yourself!
Yeah, don't you worry, friend.
And if he gets mad, just dismiss it
as the barking of a crazy dog.
I mean, it took so much for
you to get this opportunity!
You even acted as if you were
committing suicide to get this chance!
I wasn't pretending like
I was committing suicide.
I never said that I was
trying to commit suicide!
He just misunderstood the situation!
How could I leave my Jik behind
and commit suicide?
Of course!
[Shin Joon Young's Manager]
Yes, hello, Chief Jang.
It's me, No Eul. I'm in front of Mr. Shin
Joon Young's house right now.
I've been pressing the doorbell for over
ten minutes, but there was no answer.
Oh, really?
I wonder why?
I'll look into it and call you back.
- Okay.
- All right, then!
What do you think? Obviously it's
Shin Joon Young's nasty temper.
Shin Joon Young!
Are you not inside?
I'm going to freeze to death!
Open the door!
What the hell? Is he toying with me
after calling me out here?
Damn it!
Hi.
Hello.
Oh... hello.
I think your doorbell is broken. Anyway,
the recording team is coming soon--
They're not coming.
I told them not to come.
Why?
Because I'm not going
to do the documentary.
But... you said that you were
going to, up until yesterday.
Because you deceived me.
I thought you were jumping off that
bridge because I said I wouldn't do it.
Well, I didn't deceive you about that.
You were the one who misunderstood.
Then you should've cleared up
that misunderstanding for me.
Um, well...
I was going to tell you, but...
I, uh, forgot.
At any rate, we won't be
shooting the documentary.
Pororo! What are you doing?
Let's go for a walk!
I also lost an exclusive story,
thanks to you, you know!
I saw Lee Yoo Bi and Joon Ho on a date,
but I missed it because of you!
So, you were actually in the middle
of taking a secret photo of them, then?
Yes!
If I sold that, I could've earned enough
money to keep me going for two months!
Send your bank account info
to my manager.
I'll send you twice the amount of
the money you lost, thanks to me.
How much money are you going to give me?
Do you even know
how much money that would be?
If you're going to give me money
don't give me small amounts like
300,000 won, or 1 million won.
Give me 100 million, then!
You only need 100 million won?
I could give you a billion won,
if you wanted.
I could even give you
a house, a car, a building...
and everything I have.
Ask me for more money.
How could you only ask for 100 million
when I have so much damn money?
Sure, you must be real happy
because you're so damn rich.
I don't even have money to get by
and yet you have enough money to
look down on people so damn much
and just break promises
like they mean nothing!
You must be real happy, you bastard!
Pororo!
What's going on?
Hey, did you do this to her?
Pororo charged at her
because she was bothering me.
- Did Pororo bite her?
- No. He only charged at her.
But she ended up passing out.
He only charged at her,
and yet she fainted?
It's obviously just an act she thinks
I'm dumb enough to fall for.
I'm going to go work out, so pretend
like you fell for it and send her away.
Uh, I don't think she's faking it.
Hey, Joon Young! There's definitely
something wrong with her!
Hurry over here!
I don't think she's faking it.
Call Dr. Kang.
Her blood vessels have expanded
due to the sudden shock
and then her blood pressure decreased,
which has led to hypotension.
You said that she said, "I can't breathe"
before passing out, correct?
Oh, yes.
Seeing as she has rashes and
she had difficulty breathing
I think that she has a
severe dog allergy.
A dog... allergy?
I've given her a medicine
that will raise her blood pressure and
make the inflammation go down
so she should be fine after today.
Thank you for coming on your day off.
If you're thankful, give me
an autograph for my daughter.
You're looking well.
Ah, yes. I know.
I think you may have
misdiagnosed me, after all.
I'll refrain from suing you for
malpractice since you helped me out.
Stay here today, okay?
She got sick because of you.
Also, I'm really thankful
that you were worried about me
but don't do that from now on.
If you'd bitten Eul,
I would've kicked you out, punk!
Got that?
[Hubby]
The person you are trying to reach
is unavailable at this time.
Hey!
Oh, you're here?
Wouldn't this place be great
for you and Eul to live in?
We're living here?
We don't have the money
to rent this kind of place.
A friend of mine emigrated but didn't
want to sell this place or rent it out
so all you two need to do is to take
good care of this place and live here.
- For free?
- Yeah, for free!
Isn't it great?
- No, I don't want to.
- Why... not?
Nowadays, my sister is thinking things
like, "who can I backstab for money?"
"How can I spend as little money
as I can, and mooch off others?"
"How can I turn one thousand won
into one million won?"
She's always thinking about
ridiculous things like this
so just imagine what would happen
if she got a place like this for free.
She'll say, "See? Life is all about luck.
You don't need to live righteously."
And then she'll be ruined as she'll
always be waiting for more luck.
I'm really thankful that you're worrying
about us, but I don't like handouts.
I was going to stay with a
friend for the time being
and my sister can stay
with her friend Na Ri.
I'm working part-time,
and my sister works too
so I'm sure we'll be able
to find a place to live soon.
Fine. Sorry for asking!
Sheesh, I can't fathom
what goes on in your head!
Why do you keep making me
feel bad like this?
What's this?
The mother of the kid I tutor gave it to
me because I raised their grades.
Take this and go buy yourself a nice
jacket at the department store.
Hey, my jacket is still fine!
Buy a jacket for yourself!
Oh, why... is there a hole there?
It was totally fine before.
You know that my sister
is really materialistic, right?
I'd love it if you became
my brother-in-law...
but my sister doesn't
think of you like that.
Because you're poor, just like us.
And my sister only likes rich guys.
So, buy yourself some
new clothes with this
and knock my sister off her feet!
Okay?
Oh, yes?
I won't be there too late.
Whoa, Jung Eun made all this?
Yes, Madame! I thought she
was only pretty and smart
but she's quite talented, too!
It's nothing much.
Wow, you sure are skilled!
Your mother really did raise you well!
How did you make all this
in such a short time?
Ha Ru, doesn't this make you
feel a certain type of way?
Yeah, it does.
It makes me feel like she's
a damn show-off!
Ha Ru!
Hey, how could you say that--
I'm sorry, Jung Eun.
It's okay. My friends say
the same thing to me, too.
There's definitely
something off about her.
What do you mean?
There's no way that a person
is that perfect.
Her family is crazy rich, she's great at
studying, her face is ridiculously pretty
her body is ridiculously sexy, and
her personality is ridiculously great.
And she's even ridiculously
great at cooking, to boot!
Who, Jung Eun?
She definitely can't be a mere earthling.
Maybe... she's
"an asshole from another star?"
What if, when she goes home,
she eats snakes, rats, and roaches
and then goes to a cemetery
when it's midnight, and digs there
and opens up the coffins of dead
people and sucks their blood---
- Oh, Ji Tae.
- I'm home, Father.
- Yes.
- What the hell!
You surprised me!
So why are you talking crap
about other people, then?
- Jung Eun is here.
- Yes, I heard.
It looks like she came early
and prepared all the food
that we'll be offering to your
grandpa for the ancestral rites.
Go and tell her
that she did a great job.
Yes, I will, after I wash up.
I'm telling you, there may be
something off about her!
She could look completely normal
but be a psychopath or a sociopath!
Choi Ha Ru!
I'm just kidding, Dad!
It's a joke!
Sheesh, what are you
getting so serious for?
You're making your precious
daughter all flustered.
- Sheesh.
- Daddy!
I don't like Jung Eun.
Please cancel this engagement that you
adults planned without even asking us.
Jung Eun is a good girl.
All the affluent households
want her as their daughter-in-law!
How could I marry someone
I don't love, or even like?
You two only got married
because you loved each other so much.
So why are you...
Is there another girl
that you're dating?
No. That's not it, but...
I know what kind of person
Jung Eun's father is to you.
I know that you definitely need
his help to fulfill your dream, too.
But... even so, marriage is a
lifetime commitment.
My entire life depends on it.
I understand. I'll call them tomorrow
and cancel your engagement.
Honey!
Fulfilling my dream is important,
but my son is more important to me.
I will never use you for the
sake of fulfilling my own dream.
This wine's aroma is excellent.
You chose it, didn't you, my son?
Mr. Ji Tae.
You worked quite hard, didn't you?
You did a great job.
If you really think so, give me a kiss.
You're a warm person,
but you have no passion.
You're only being nice to
me out of a sense of duty
because our parents told us to, right?
You don't even love me.
Wait, what I just said is true, huh?
Ouch. My pride hurts.
Let's get married.
Let's skip the engagement party
and just get married, Yoon Jung Eun.
Do you...
love me?
As long as you don't push me away,
I'll never leave you.
So you won't say that you love me,
until the very end.
That's fine, though. I'll just love you
more to compensate for that.
I got up, and I was really hungry.
I'll pay you back for the ramen.
No... I'll give you money
for the ramen, punk.
It's not like we're even
working together anymore
so I can speak
informally to you, right?
Is fainting your trademark,
or something?
It's because I have
a weak immune system.
I got into a car accident a while ago
and got three surgeries
so my body is on its last legs now.
Do you, by any chance...
have any cold rice?
Um, about... what you said before.
Is that offer still valid?
Um, so... um...
You said that you could give me
a car, a house, and a building.
anything that I wanted.
I know you won't give me any
of that, but I asked just in case.
What is it that you want?
Can I really tell you?
100 million won.
To me, that's the hugest
amount of money I can think of.
But... that's too much money, right?
50 million won, then.
30 million won?
10 million won!
If you just give me that, I'll never
bother you about the documentary again.
I won't ever appear before
you again, either.
If you don't want to just give it
to me, lend it to me.
With 82 months of no interest.
60 months of no interest?
You can't even lend it to me?
Even though you're so rich?
No, I can't.
Then why did you even ask me
to tell you what I wanted?
Wow, I heard that rich people are
even stingier, and they were right.
Earn that money by working! You
still have functioning limbs, don't you?
So why are you trying to get
handouts from other people?
See, that's only possible when
I actually have work to do!
Because of your stupid temper,
I lost the job I worked so hard to get!
Let's do the documentary, then.
- There you go again.
- Let's shoot it.
Oh, yes, Your Highness.
What? What's going on?
Re-write my contract for
the documentary, please.
You said that you
weren't doing it, though.
Gook Young called me and told me
that you said you weren't doing it.
I changed my mind.
I'll do it this time.
Okay. You might change your mind
again, so call me back in the morning--
I won't. You can include
in the contract that
I'll pay 1000 times the original
severance fee if I change my mind again!
Are you really going to do it?
[From: No Eul
Gift Coupon]
- Mister!
- What's this?
A present from me,
since I just got a job!
Jik and I mooched off you so much
when you don't even have money!
So much so, that you couldn't
even buy a proper pair of sneakers.
So, you got a job?
I thought that you became infamous,
so nobody would take you as a PD!
Good job, Eul!
I'm going to be shooting
Shin Joon Young's documentary.
Isn't that amazing?
Isn't this unbelievable?
People don't realize this,
but I'm quite skilled!
I'm going to destroy everyone
who looked down on me!
Hello?
Why aren't you saying anything, Mister?
Did you fall asleep?
Oh no, it's already
past three in the morning!
Are you really asleep, Mister?
Well, good night, then!
Are you mad?
I'm not kicking you out forever.
Just consider this a nice trip to a
vacation home with fresh air
and stay here for like three months.
Just until I finish the documentary.
Look, you get to see clouds,
and the sky!
And I'm sure you'll be able to see
the stars and the moon at night!
This is a great spot!
Then, do you want me to live here
and let you live inside?
- Ma'am!
- Yes?
Um, can you make sure to clean all of
Pororo's fur off the carpets and floors?
What?
Um, there's someone who's
allergic to Pororo's fur...
Forget it.
I'll take care of it myself.
Ta-da! I got the taro milk tea that you
like so much, with tons of ice!
I also got tapioca pearls,
and coconut, too!
And this is the jumbo size,
with tons of milk foam!
Well? How is it?
Also, this milk foam is to represent
how I feel about you!
Why are you being like this to me?
Wow, PD No,
your skin got so much better!
See? People need to take
breaks between jobs!
It's a good thing
you listened to me, huh?
- What are you--
- Shush!
Well, then, you've gotten plenty of rest
so how about coming back
to work now, Eul?
What work?
The Ministry of Culture and Tourism
asked us to shoot a documentary.
And I'd like it if you could
do that for us, PD No.
- Oh, I get it.
- What?
I guess you've already
heard the rumors, huh?
That I'm doing
Shin Joon Young's documentary?
Oh, really?
I didn't hear about that.
So how could you fire a skilled person
like me without recognizing my talent?
I guess you really have no talent
for judging people's character.
I'll double your pay, and pay you
more than those people are!
I'll hire you as a full-time employee,
and give you company insurance!
- Really?
- Really!
Oh, just a second. Sorry.
I have to take this call.
Whoa.
Yes, Section Chief.
Oh, um...
PD No is here at my office right now.
I'll take responsibility for her
and persuade her, no matter what.
So, don't worry too much, sir.
Thank you.
If you do convince her
I'll give you the investment rights
that we were talking about.
Why are there flowers
at Joon Young's place?
He even changed his
cushions and carpets, too!
Wow, this punk.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Isn't this great?
And he was putting up such a fuss,
saying he wouldn't do the documentary!
Well, you know how much he
secretly loves being on shows!
But, where is Joon Young?
Joon Young, are you in the bathroom?
What are you doing?
Are you pooping?
All right, take care of
your business, then!
"Why now?"
I wanted to ask.
Why now, when I've been fine?
Why now, when I've been
eating well and sleeping well?
Why now, when I just beat
by three minutes
my record for climbing
Cheonggye Mountain?
And No Eul is supposed
to come today, too.
I've been waiting for this
moment for so long.
So why now?
At that moment, I remembered the
promise I made a long time ago.
"Please, just save Eul."
"If you do, I'll give up
all of the happiness
that I was supposed to
experience in my lifetime."
"I'll give up all of my happiness."
Thank you. After all, you called me
back here and treated me so well.
No, I'm the one who's more
thankful. I was worried
that you wouldn't want to work because
you were still hung up over last time.
But as to be expected,
you're as passionate as ever!
You're not hung up over
the past, either!
That's not true.
I'm totally hung up over it.
Wait, what?
I'm not going to work at this company.
Wait, what are you talking about?
You totally love money!
I told you, I'll pay you double!
And make you full-time, on top of that!
And you'll even get health insurance!
Hey, No Eul!
All of those benefits
do sound really awesome, but...
if I betray Shin Joon Young,
he'll definitely kill me. Like, for sure.
I'm sorry. No Eul usually goes crazy
for money, but she said no--
If a demon like you
becomes an assemblyman
there really will be
no hope for this country.
If you reveal the true criminal behind
my father's case that you covered up...
I'll burn all the materials
that I have about you.
Hey!
Hey, give me back my bag!
Stop right there! Hey!
Look into the owner
of this phone for me.
Who is he?
Someone who almost killed
his own girlfriend...
to save my father.
About the guy you asked me
to look into...
His name is Shin Joon Young.
And I think that he's your father's son.
Congratulations, Doctor.
It seems like you're not
a quack after all.
The disease is progressing a lot
more quickly than I'd expected.
How long do I have left to live, then?
Six months?
Three months?
How about checking into the hospital
and getting treatment now?
We can give you chemotherapy
and radiation therapy.
- We'll do all we can--
- But...
Even if we do all that,
I'll end up dying anyway.
But still, we can lengthen the
amount of time you'll have left.
I don't need that.
Just write me a prescription for
really powerful pain meds, please.
Get me some pain meds that will ensure
that nobody finds out about my illness.
Ones that make me forget about
the fact that I'm ill, too.
If you make it so that I won't
be in pain until I die
I'll give you 100 autographs.
Isn't that Shin Joon Young?
Yes, it seems like it.
I wonder why he's at the hospital?
We'll have to hurry, ma'am.
You're late for your appointment.
Oh, okay.
[Mom]
This customer cannot currently
be reached. Please try again later.
[Mom: I'm in a meeting.
I'll call you back later.]
Look at this lying old lady.
Why would you be in a meeting
when you run a restaurant?
It's not like you're going
to call me back, either.
[Iron Maiden Ok]
[Miss Spy]
[Deuk Dragon]
Shin Joon Young is kind of fading out,
don't you think?
I told you, don't say things like
"kind of" or "a little bit!"
It'll just make you seem
unconfident and petty!
Say "he's definitely fading out!"
Got it?
You need to sound like
you're full of confidence
for people to be like,
"ah, that must be true!"
Yes, ma'am!
There are tons of people who
look like Shin Joon Young.
People like him are literally
littered all over the street!
Like this, Boss?
Let me see.
To be honest, there aren't too
many people who look like him.
Why don't you go outside and see for
yourself whether or not that's true?
Come on, Yong Deuk!
If you say something that's
so obviously untrue
people will think you're just petty,
and won't even read your comment!
They won't even press
"like" on your comment, either!
Yes, Boss.
Shin Joon Young should just retire.
I change the channel
every time he's on TV.
I do tend to change the channel
whenever Joon Young is on TV...
from a channel he isn't on
to a channel he is on.
Oh my, look at you people!
Are you writing malicious comments
to get Joon Young to retire again?
Here, raise your heads.
I'm going to take a photo and report
you for online harassment.
Hey, Yong Deuk!
I told you to peel garlic
because I'm making pickles, didn't I?
But this is all you've managed
to peel in two hours!
Instead, you were busy writing hateful
comments about Joon Young, weren't you?
You know our boss. She
prioritizes that over peeling garlic.
I have to listen to the boss.
I'm a mere worker, after all.
Sheesh.
And you, Man Ok!
You're Shin Joon Young's
wardrobe assistant.
And yet, you're his anti-fan?
What did I do?
Honestly, don't you remember how happy
Boss was when Joon got into law school?
But he didn't even talk things over with
any of us, and dropped out!
No proper human being should
do such a terrible thing!
He's not even a proper human being.
Joon Young is just more
with the times, is all!
Geez, you kids are so old-fashioned!
You people really don't know
what's trendy nowadays!
That's enough.
Stop it, already.
You're the worst of them all!
Who cares about Choi Hyun Joon?
Do you think he'd really care that
you made Joon Young into a prosecutor?
Do you think he'd say, "Oh, great job,
Ok!" if you managed to do that
and cast his own family aside
to live with you instead--
Joon Young didn't become a celebrity
because he wanted to be one!
Your stupid son got himself in trouble,
and Joo Young needed to help him out
which is why he took the signing bonus
and ended up like this, because he's
trying to pay that money back now!
Do you think I don't know about that?
That's...
How did she know about that?
Wait, how has she not
killed my family yet, knowing that?
Joon Young knows that you write mean
comments on articles relevant to him.
He's not suing anyone who
writes mean comments about him
because he's scared that it may be you.
Crazy bastard.
These are the materials that
the Resources Team collected
to catch internet slanderers.
And this is a petition signed
by over 1 million people
saying that they want the
slanderers to be punished.
These are documents revealing the
identities of some of these people.
This person definitely deserves
to rot in jail forever!
I know this person, too.
What does it matter if they keep
changing their ID and IP address?
All they do is keep copying and
pasting the same stupid comment!
What is this?
The PD working on Joon Young's
documentary... is a woman?
And to top it all off,
she looks... weird...
So this hussy is going to stick
around our Joon Young, 24/7?
Is this woman actually a PD?
She looks really young,
and she looks totally unskilled!
It seems like there's some
foul play involved, right?
- Yes!
I think that we should focus on getting
this woman before that slanderer.
You're right.
Her name is... No Eul?
Wow, her name is No Eul?
At any rate, I sent this woman's
photo to the group chat
so try and dig up some intel about her.
- Yes.
Find out if she's actually a PD,
and where she went to school.
And where she lives!
Oh, and about her family.
Anything about her past would be great,
so find out as much as you can.
I'll do my best to do
some searching, too.
- Yes.
Excuse me.
When you said "No Eul," were you
talking about the female PD?
- One who shoots documentaries.
- Yes, so?
Do you know her, by any chance?
Yes, well, a bit.
You're telling me that you
really know this woman?
What kind of relationship
do you two have?
Are you... her boyfriend,
by any chance?
I'm working right now,
so I can't chat for very long.
But if you give me your phone number,
I'll call you when I leave work.
You're not... lying, are you?
If you can't believe me,
never mind, then.
Don't you dare think of voice
phishing me, or selling my number!
My dad used to be a really famous
prosecutor, back in the day!
What should I save your name as?
What's your name?
No...
I mean, Oh Jik.
What about you?
Choi Ha Ru.
But, um, your name is
Oh Jik (means "only")?
This project is to try and overcome
our nation's shameful title
as the country with the highest suicide
rate among the OECD countries
for ten years straight, and is a
part of a suicide prevention campaign
that the Ministry of Education and the
Ministry of Health and Welfare are doing.
In order to do that, we've chosen 10
people who are influential among teens
and are revealing those
10 individuals' bucket lists
to teach teens how
to live life to the fullest.
Our aim is also to show them that
setting concrete goals for their lives
and living honestly will help them feel
enjoyment and purpose in their lives.
And thus, they will come to
treasure their lives more--
Stop.
Turn the lights back on.
I really don't get what you're saying,
so can you put it in simpler terms?
Simpler terms?
But this is as simple as it gets.
I'm kind of an idiot, you see.
It's quite simple.
It's to tell teens who want to give up on
life because it's hard, to not give up.
And to tell them to live,
no matter what.
Or to tell them to not die,
All you have to do is convey that sort
of message through your bucket list.
- Wow!
To tell people that life is worth living,
no matter what price you must pay
and that life is a beautiful thing
and that it's like a blessing from God,
so one mustn't lose hope and be brave--
You didn't tell me that would
be the concept for this, CEO.
What are you talking about? I sent all
the materials to you via Chief Jang.
I left them on your desk!
So that... you would read them.
You didn't read them?
Hey, he's not going to say he's not
doing the documentary again, right?
If he does, I'm done for.
If that happens, Ms. Face-in-a-dish...
I mean, PD No Eul...
is going to pull out a knife and
go on a murder-suicide rampage!
Seriously!
Damn it!
Who wants to bet that Shin Joon Young
is going to change his mind again? I am.
- Me too.
- Me three!
Hey, hurry up and pack everything!
This project is over!
I'll try to convince him.
Let's start the filming.
Mr. Shin Joon Young. What's
the first item on your bucket list?
All right.
Let's say that you'll die in a year.
What's the first thing you'd want to do?
Would you want to go somewhere,
or do something special?
Or would you want
to see a certain someone?
Don't you have anything like that?
You'll die in a year.
You only have a year left.
Isn't there anything you'd
want to do, or see--
A year is too long.
Let's say that I only had
three months left to live.
Fine. Let's say that you
only had three months, then.
I'd live recklessly.
I'd take care of the bastards
who look down on me
and kill everyone that
I don't like very much.
That doesn't go with the
theme of our documentary.
It's to show people through
these bucket lists
that life is a precious
and beautiful thing--
- I'd go to clubs and seduce women.
- Excuse me.
And I'd sleep with a different
woman every night.
Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
Let's stop the interview.
Don't stop it.
Let's keep going.
Does this production seem like
a joke to you, Mr. Shin Joon Young?
I'm not joking.
I'm being honest.
I could do anything if
I were going to die soon.
Don't you want to try drugs,
too, while you're at it?
What about drunk driving, peeing
on the streets, and gambling--
Do you want to go
out with me, PD No Eul?
Let's pretend that I'll
really die in three months...
and have a really passionate
romance for those three months.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Uncontrollably Fond]
I can go online and say
that I'm dating you, right?
Damn it!
Looks like all your personal
info has been leaked, PD No Eul.
You conniving snake.
I don't owe you anything
anymore, all right?
Can't you make me your wife?
I'd like it if things went
well for you and Hyun Woo.
That way, you'll be happy.
I said that another PD besides
Ms. No Eul will come tomorrow!
Are you her husband,
or something?
Are you her husband?
- Am I your husband?
- Yes.
Is it your first time
seeing a rich person?
Is your husband unemployed,
or something?
Judging from his voice,
he sounded really ugly.
Boy. Friend.
I'm doing a concert today.
Put this on, Dad, and come
to Joon Young's concert!
Joon Young lives in a totally different
world than you do now, Big Sis.
Don't fall for Joon Young, Big Sis.