[UNCONTROLLABLY FOND]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Episode 5
All right. Let's say
that you were going to die in a year.
You're going to die in a year.
You only have one year left.
Isn't there anything
you'd want to do, or see...
A year is too long.
Let's say that I only have
three months left to live.
Fine. Let's say that you
only have three months, then.
I'd live recklessly. I'd take care of
the bastards who look down on me
and kill everyone I don't like.
That doesn't go with
the theme of our documentary.
It's to show people through
their bucket lists
that life is a precious
and beautiful thing...
- I'd go to clubs and seduce women.
- Excuse me.
And I'd sleep with
a different woman every night.
Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
Let's stop the interview.
Don't stop.
Let's keep going.
Does this production seem like
a joke to you, Mr. Shin Joon Young?
I'm not joking.
I'm being honest.
I could do anything I wanted
if I were going to die soon.
Don't you want to try drugs
while you're at it?
What about drunk driving, peeing
in the street, and gambling...
Do you want to go
out with me, PD No Eul?
Let's pretend that I really will
really die in three months...
and have a really passionate
romance for those three months.
Let's have a dangerously fiery
romance, for just three months.
Well, today was just a test shoot
so I guess our Joon Young is joking
around to loosen up for the real deal...
I told you, I'm not joking.
I clearly said that I wasn't joking.
Joon Young.
You don't want to, Ms. PD?
Of course I'd want to! Heck, I'm really
grateful that you asked me out!
Shin Joon Young, a top star,
just asked me out.
I'd be a crazy fool
to refuse that kind of offer!
- PD No!
When should we start?
Are we going to start today?
If we start dating, it'll be
officially announced, right?
That'd be fine with me, too.
Oh, I can announce that I'm dating
you on my social media pages, right?
Hello.
What's with her?
I don't know. I guess she caused
some sort of trouble again.
She's been like this
for about 30 minutes now.
You really want to end
your life in such a pathetic way?
Did you cause trouble again?
I think I'll probably
get fired, Mister.
What?
I think I'm going to get fired from
working on Shin Joon Young's documentary.
Why?
Well... because I took what he said
as a joke for the documentary seriously.
No... because I treated
what he said seriously as a joke...
Wait, no.
Because I treated seriously what
he said, when he was being serious.
What are you saying?
She sounds like
she's finally lost it.
No, I haven't!
Why do you only ever say
things like that about me?
Because you look down
on me so damn much
everyone else in the world
does the same!
All right? Even though none of you
can say a thing to Shin Joon Young!
Nobody says anything to him
when he's saying crazy nonsense
so why is everyone only
calling me the crazy one?
Do I seem like I'm that
easy to take advantage of?
- You little... hey!
- Ow!
When was I never able
to talk back to Shin Joon Young?
Why the hell are you
unloading all this on me?
Do I seem like I'm that
easy to take advantage of?
Exactly. I really
must be crazy.
It's for the best.
Forget about shooting
a celebrity documentary
and go back to doing investigative TV.
It's what you do best.
I'll help you find a job.
You're unemployed too, though!
You're in no position to be helping me.
Hey, I'll get a job soon, punk!
When you get a job, should I
go and get a job from you?
I'm so tired of dealing
with other people.
What?
You wouldn't let me or Jik starve
at the very least, Mister.
So... couldn't you hire me
for the position of your wife?
What did you just say?
Another PD will come to replace Ms. Face-
in-a-dish-of-water starting tomorrow!
I know that you asked her out on
camera today as a plot to get her fired.
Our CEO is really pissed off right now
and said, "What kind of crazy PD is she?"
And that he couldn't entrust
you to a psycho like her!
So he went and told that
to the production staff.
Are you happy now, Mr. Joon Young?
What was she supposed to say
in that situation, anyway?
"Oh my gosh, you roach-like
piece of crap!"
"Are you out of your damn mind?"
And then say, "You and I will both die
here today!" and fight you, like that?
If she did, she would've
been yelled at
for daring to talk back to a top
celebrity when she's a mere PD!
Just think about it!
It's really not right for
the production staff to be doing this.
I mean, even if she's just a freelance
worker, how could they just say
that they were thinking
of getting a new PD?
Seriously, how can people be so cruel?
I mean, even if she has no power, how...
That was the last bit
of my spiel. Sorry, I'll shut up.
Call the CEO.
And tell him that I won't shoot
a single scene of the documentary
if PD No Eul isn't working on it.
Tell him to re-hire PD No Eul
if he doesn't want to find
a new celebrity to be
his company's main cash cow.
Mister. Here's a snack
to go with that.
All right! I take back my proposal!
I take it back, damn it!
Why won't you just be honest and say
that you don't want me as your wife?
Why are you drinking so much
soju on an empty stomach
when you have such
a low tolerance?
"Oh, come on, Eul! Why would I turn
down such a lovely woman like you?"
"I like you so much, and it's just that
I don't know how to react to all this"
"because I can't believe
that it's happening."
So you won't say
that either, huh?
Wow. So you won't say anything at all?
Damn it.
To be honest, I don't like you
that much either, you know!
Wow, he's not even coming
out here to stop me.
He has high standards for someone
who has nothing to his name.
Damn it, how embarrassing!
Both my job and my proposal
ended in disaster.
Damn it!
It's just because I'm stuck in a pit of
bad luck right now. That's what it is.
Sheesh, Eul really
needs to learn her place.
How dare she flirt with someone
like you, of all people?
In your opinion, do I seem
like I'm better than Eul?
Of course! I mean,
you're still unemployed
but you're way
better off than she is!
All she has is a mountain of debt
and a terrible temper!
And she keeps accepting
bribes all the time.
So I was thinking, I know
a woman who cooks well
and has some money saved up,
and is a decent looker...
I...
don't deserve to have her.
I don't deserve Eul...
which is why I can't accept her.
What?
Oh no, she left her phone.
That klutz!
That guy definitely
isn't normal, either.
Eul!
No Eul!
[ASSHOLE]
What the...
Yes? This is No Eul's phone.
Hello?
Why are you answering No Eul's phone?
We were together,
and she left her phone.
And who am I speaking to?
Who are you?
I asked first.
It's only polite to
identify yourself
when asking others
to identify themselves.
Can't you read Korean? I'm sure
my name popped up on the caller ID.
It just said "Asshole".
"Asshole?"
Wait, what?
At any rate, Eul can't come
to the phone right now
so please call her back later...
If you happen to be Shin Joon Young,
you don't need to call her again.
I heard that Eul was fired from
your documentary project...
Who the hell do you think
you are, telling me what to do?
Oh. Oh.
Are you her husband,
by any chance?
Huh? My phone.
Are you Eul's husband?
Hello? Why aren't you answering?
Are you her husband? Huh?
Why did you answer my phone?
Hello?
Hey, do you have a death
wish, you son of a bitch?
[ASSHOLE]
[NAMPYEON (HUSBAND)]
So I'm "Nampyeon"?
Yes.
Whenever I get into a spat with
someone, you always take their side.
You're never on my side.
You're always on someone else's side.
"Nam" meaning "other people", and "pyeon"
meaning "side". So you're "Nampyeon".
I'll be going now.
Eul.
You'll meet a good person.
Someone who'll have
your best interest at heart.
Who will love you,
and make you happy.
I'm sure you will meet
a person like that.
Wow, I didn't know that you were this
kind of person, but you're really cruel.
If you're rejecting me,
you should just do it
instead of acting like a nice guy!
Eul. I...
I'm cutting my ties with you.
Don't ever contact me again!
Why did this bastard
even call me, anyway?
I can't even guess what he's thinking
because he's such a psycho.
Why the hell did you call me,
you psychotic bastard? Huh?
Are you that desperate
for me to yell at you?
I'll be damned if I ever
pick up your calls again!
I'm sorry that
I couldn't pick up your call.
I'm really regretting
my foolish actions and tasteless joke.
Could you possibly find it
in your generous heart
to ask the CEO for one more chance...
Forget this.
I'm not doing it.
It's not like I won't be able to
earn any money without your help!
There's a place telling me
that they'll pay me double
and even hire me as a full-time
employee, with health insurance!
Huh? That looks like
Shin Joon Young's car.
What, is it your first time
seeing an asshole, or something?
Um, how did you...
I asked the production
staff, and they told me.
Why the hell are those people
releasing my personal info...
How come you're living with Na Ri
and not with your husband?
Oh. Um. So, about that.
So, you managed to get married?
Do you have kids, too?
Is your husband unemployed?
Or did his business fail?
Did he tell you to go out
and make money any way you could?
What kind of crazy guy would want
to get married to a bum like me, huh?
Would you want to marry
such a poor person?
I don't have a husband, and
obviously, I don't have kids.
I don't have a place to live,
or money, or any pride, either.
That's why I'm mooching
off my friend. Happy?
Thanks to a certain psycho, I got fired
again, so I'll continue to have no money
no place to live, no husband!
Is this funny to you?
Do I seem like a joke to you?
Damn it, why am I
telling you these things?
I must be crazy!
[PD YOON FROM SKY PRODUCTIONS]
- Hello?
- This is PD Yoon.
I think you'll have to continue working
on Shin Joon Young's documentary.
I thought you said
you were replacing me?
Shin Joon Young said that he won't
do a single scene unless you work on it.
He also told us to fire
most of the staff, except the director
so I think we'll have to have a meeting.
You can come in now, right?
Hello?
PD No?
Are you listening,
PD No? Hello?
Hey, it's urgent!
Hello? PD No!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Say "ah!"
What's all this?
I won't be able to take care of
you very well after I start working
so make sure that you eat up!
She didn't get any sleep last night
because she was making this for you!
It tastes like a terrorist is attacking
your taste buds, though
so just be aware of that.
Geez, it's so damn salty!
Geez, I'm so upset!
What's with your face?
Do they not feed you
at your friend's house?
- Big Sis!
- Sheesh, you're like a mom.
If you're that worried,
why not drop everything
and follow Jik around everywhere,
with a bowl of rice?
Should I really do that?
Should I drop everything
and follow you around?
Sure. Quit working on that documentary
or whatever, and just follow me around.
You can come to school with me too.
Let's go to school.
Jik.
Of course I want to follow you
around everywhere, but...
You know that Shin Joon Young's
fans are no joke, right?
What?
They say that Shin Joon Young's fans
are worse than any other singers' fans.
There are tons of psychos, too.
They're trying to dig up
information about you right now.
If you end up getting
on their bad side, you...
[FROM: JERK OF ALL JERKS]
This is Mr. Oh Jik's cell, right? You
said that you'd tell me about PD No Eul
but you didn't contact me!
And you won't pick up your phone.
If you're lying to me, you're dead!
She is the chairwoman
of Shin Joon Young's fanclub.
You remember me telling you that my dad
used to be a famous prosecutor, right?
If you approached me because
you have a personal interest in me...
What are you going to do with
information regarding PD No Eul?
Do your parents know that you're going
around doing this kind of thing?
Wow.
Wow. Eul, you're done for.
What are you doing?
Big Sis!
That girl has nothing better to do?
Give me your phone.
Give it to her, Jik.
[JERK OF ALL JERKS]
It's that girl, right? I'll teach
her a lesson. Give it here.
No Jik!
The person you're trying to
reach is unavailable at this time.
What's the matter?
Give me that girl's number!
It must be hard for you as it is
since you're studying so hard
so why is that girl bothering you?
Is that jerk Shin Joon Young
that great? Huh?
Yeah, he is.
And honestly, she doesn't even seem
like that much of a weirdo to me.
She's totally normal!
But he's great enough to make a normal
girl like her become as deranged as this!
That's not what I'm talking about.
Don't fall for Joon Young, Big Sis.
What?
I'm sure that you'll start liking him
after you spend a lot of time with him,
while you're shooting that documentary.
- But don't even dream about it.
- You punk.
What do you take me for?
He lives in a completely different
world than you do now, Big Sis.
Don't misunderstand something
he says carelessly, and fall for him.
If you do, you'll end up being
the only one who gets hurt.
Did you have a nice
breakfast, sweetie?
Yeah, the braised beef short ribs
did taste a bit weird, right?
That's why I told you
not to eat that, punk!
I'd like it if things between you
and Hyun Woo went well.
He doesn't have much,
but he's a really good person.
And he definitely suits you.
Being with him will make you happy.
All right, that's
all the nagging for today!
Work hard, Eul!
Good luck with the documentary!
That punk is supposed
to be my little brother?
I was already rejected
by Mr. Hyun Woo, all right?
He doesn't even know
what he's talking about.
Damn it, how embarrassing!
When you get a job, should I
go and get a job from you?
I'm so sick of other people.
What?
You wouldn't let me or Jik starve
at the very least, Mister.
So... couldn't you hire me
for the position of your wife?
- Am I "Nampyeon"?
- Um...
Yes.
Whenever I get into a spat with
someone, you always take their side.
"Nam" meaning "other people", and "pyeon"
meaning "side". So you're "Nampyeon".
Come on, Ji Tae.
Yes?
Ji Tae, your father
wants to see you.
- Father?
- Yeah.
Seeing as how you're taking
your time to think about this
it seems that your brilliant move
might turn out to be a terrible one.
That's what you want, isn't it?
But such a thing won't happen.
Let's see, here.
I just have to hit both of them, right?
Yes!
Hey, hey, let's play one more time.
That's not fair!
Come on, give it to me.
The ball that Greg Norman signed.
Hey, do you know what I
had to go through to get that?
I'll give you anything else but that.
Come on, one more round!
- Come on.
- Wow, Father!
You're really going to be like this?
I'm going to tell Mom about this!
Wow, you really want to win
that badly, huh?
Wow! Totally ridiculous!
Where did you learn
that phrase, Father?
Hey, come on. Let's
play one more round!
- All right, go ahead!
- No!
Daddy!
Oh, hello, Choi Ha Ru!
Dad, I'm totally drained.
Where did you head off to
so early in the morning?
Our Joon Young's concert is today.
Here. Put this on,
and come to his concert.
It's at the Olympic Hall, at 6 p.m.
How could I go there?
Come on! The leader
of the Korean Nationalist Party
went to an EXO concert
with his daughter!
He even posted a photo of
himself there, and put it online.
His popularity skyrocketed!
You didn't know about that?
No, I didn't.
Father's busy.
Also, shouldn't you be studying?
Are you going to re-take the college
entrance exams for the third time
because you're too busy following
Shin Joon Young around?
Whatever. Come on, Dad!
Come with me!
Oh yeah. I heard that he's
also shooting a documentary.
You'll be really popular if
you're seen at the concert, Dad!
Choi Ha Ru!
I told you to stop it.
Do you think that you can
just ignore what I say?
Big... Brother.
The other people preparing for exams
don't want to waste even a second
and aren't even
sleeping that much.
So how is it that you have the time
to go see some damn concert?
Stop the Shin Joon Young
fan club nonsense!
No! Joon Young is more
important to me than college!
My life has no meaning
without Joon Young!
Why the hell are you butting into
something that's none of your business?
That's no way to speak
to your older brother!
Choi Ha Ru! How could
you say that to him?
He's acting so weird!
He's being so scary
all of the sudden.
He must've gone crazy, Dad!
I'm sorry for acting that
way in front of you, Father.
I suddenly find myself liking
this Shin Joon Young guy.
Why is it that you never
get angry, Ji Tae?
There are tons of things
that probably make you angry
so why is it that you never get mad?
Do you have some kind of mental issue?
I even wondered for a while
if I should take you to a hospital.
But it seems that I don't have to.
You know how to get angry,
and how to lose your temper.
I've finally realized that my
son is fine, thanks to this man
so shouldn't I buy the guy
a meal, at the very least?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
You changed the passcode
on the door? That's not nice.
I thought you said
that you'd call me back.
"I'm in a meeting, so I can't pick up.
I'll call you back right away."
You ignored my call,
and sent me that text.
The meeting's not over yet.
What are you going to do about it?
I'm having a concert today.
These are the best seats in the house,
so come with Uncle Jung Shik.
This is your last chance to get a glimpse
of your sexy son from the best spot.
This is your last chance.
You won't be able to see me being
so cool again, even if you want to.
Wow, what a great thing to hear.
Thanks for giving me such great
news, first thing in the morning!
Move.
- Mom.
- Let go!
Who are you calling "Mom"? Since
when have you treated me like your mom?
You dropped out of that
school of your own volition
even though you worked
so hard to get in
and you became a celebrity without
even talking to me about it!
What's wrong with being a celebrity?
It's much better to be
a celebrity than a prosecutor.
You don't know just how
rich I am, do you?
I own buildings, a house, and
three expensive cars, and...
Oh, really, now? Must
be nice to be so damn rich.
You said that you'd
become a prosecutor
and protect people like us who are
poor and have no connections
and you acted so high and mighty
about it all, saying you'd do it!
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
A guy like me shouldn't
be a prosecutor, Mom.
If a guy like me were
to become a prosecutor
people like you who are weak,
poor, and have no connections
couldn't live in this country.
You'd have to emigrate.
What?
At any rate, I'll leave those seats
open for you and Uncle.
Come over if you
change your mind.
I'm not going.
Wait until you die.
I still won't go.
Wow, my mom sure
knows how to be harsh.
I almost cried.
[INFORMATION REGARDING THE CONCERT]
Welcome to the concert. If you have
your tickets, please come to the front.
Stop crying, already!
It's not like your parents died!
I'm really hurt! How could
my brother do that to me?
How could he yell at his
one and only little sister...
and glare at me like that,
as if he wanted to kill me?
I take after Mom, so I have
a really weak heart, too.
Your mother has a problem
with her kidneys, not her heart.
It's the same thing!
My older brother must
really be out of his mind.
Way to go, way to go.
Look at you, dissing your older brother
who's just looking out for you.
- Dad!
- Assemblyman!
It's only natural that family members
who care about you would yell at you
about chasing celebrities
when you should be studying
for the college entrance exams!
So stop talking crap about your
older brother already, Choi Ha Ru!
How did you get here?
I sent him a text saying that Ha Ru
was really hurt and she keeps crying.
And that I feel like the concert hall
will flood because of her tears!
Did you come because you
were worried about Ha Ru?
Here.
Keep this a secret from your
mom and older brother, okay?
Dad!
I'm not raising my child
very well, am I?
Just between you and me, Ha Ru doesn't
exactly have a talent for studying.
It's not like her grades will go up just
because she sits hunched over a desk.
That's true.
And it's not like I'm
a huge troublemaker
since I'm too busy chasing
Joon Young around.
Sure, sure. Good job, my daughter.
Um, Assembly... um, I mean,
Ha Ru's father.
Since you came all the way here, why
don't the three of us take a photo?
Wait, um, no.
That's okay.
All right. I'll take it now!
One, two, three!
- Forever Shin Joon Young!
- We love you, Shin Joon Young!
Another day passed,
as if nothing happened.
I keep saying "It's okay, it's okay"
to try to console myself
but I'm not okay.
[VIP: SHIN YOUNG OK, JANG JUNG SHIK]
After the day that I sent you away
my heart felt completely empty...
but I can't seem to fill this void
with someone who's not you.
The look in your eyes,
the feel of your touch
stays with me,
like a wind that isn't blowing.
The picture inside my head is you.
And now, I don't have
a place to return to.
I can't see anything.
Miss you, love you,
but I have to love you.
Don't fall for Joon Young, Big Sis.
I'm sure that you'll start liking him
after you spend a lot of time with him,
while you're shooting that documentary.
But don't even dream about it.
He lives in a completely
different world than you do.
The look in your eyes,
the feel of your touch
stays with me,
like a wind that isn't blowing.
The picture inside my head is you.
And now, I don't
have a place to return to.
The picture inside my head,
the picture inside my head
is you. Is you. Is you. Is you.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
You're going to the
Prosecutor's Office, right?
I want to grow up and
be a prosecutor, too.
I definitely hope to see you
again, as my co-worker.
Yes, sir.
What's your name? You're someone I'll
be working with in the future, after all.
So I should autograph this for you.
Next time.
I'll study hard, and come back with
my bar exam results saying that I passed
so please, give this to me then.
I'll tell you my name then.
Mr. Shin Joon Young.
It looks like you won't be coming
back to the Prosecutor's Office.
Where did the Assemblyman go?
Shin Joon Young's concert?
Why... did he go there?
It seems that he went
because of Ms. Ha Ru.
What?
You've been on my mind all day.
I told you to peel the onions.
What the hell are you doing?
I was watching his concert so I could
think of more evil comments to write.
What?
But to be honest, there's not a lot
of bad things I can say about him.
He's really cool to me too,
and I'm a guy!
Go inside and peel some onions!
- And peel the garlic, too!
- Damn it!
What did you say?
How dare you!
Did you just curse at me?
That little bastard!
Why are you taking your
frustrations out on Yong Deuk?
Where have you been all day,
that you just got back now...
What's this?
What is this?
- The money Gook Young owes Joon Young.
- Jung Shik.
I gave that to Gook Young to
give Joon Young three years ago
but that bastard went and used it
all, which is why it took so long.
Where did you get such
a large sum of money?
I got my friend to pay me back
the money he owed me
by lying down in front of his house.
I also took my house's
safety deposit.
As for the interest, you
can take it out of my paycheck.
- Jung Shik.
- Sheesh.
Wow, it feels so great to get that
five-year-old burden off my chest!
I don't owe you anything
anymore, all right?
We're equals now, in material
possession, in state of mind...
and as a man and woman. Got that?
Also, let's make this
one thing clear, all right?
Joon Young didn't quit law
school just to help my son, all right?
The first thing that happened was
that Joon Young quit law school
for some reason unbeknownst to us.
My Gook Young
caused trouble after that.
And then... the third
thing that happened
is that Joon Young
became a celebrity
got his signing bonus,
and then helped Gook Young.
Got it? The correct order of events?
Yep, I'm sure you do.
- All right, he's here!
- All right!
Wow, the audience's
response to you was great!
- Hey, get some water for him.
- Yes, sir!
- All right, here you are.
- Okay!
You'll sing your last song
after the guest performance
so keep your energy up for
just a bit longer, Star Shin!
All right!
Let's do this!
It's been a while since
your last concert, right?
Yes.
Can you share your
thoughts about it with us?
Who was that man?
What?
The one who picked up
your phone last night.
He was listed as
"Husband" in your phone.
Change the subject!
Is he your boyfriend?
On my way into the concert hall
I saw some fans who came from
halfway across the world to see you.
- Can you say hello to them...
- He's your boyfriend, right?
What did you eat today? What do you
eat on days that you have concerts...
How long have you been dating him?
Joon Young.
What do you usually do
when your concerts are over?
- What are you doing...
- His voice wasn't that great.
What about his looks?
Judging from the sound of his
voice, he seemed really ugly.
Your boyfriend, I mean.
He's not my boyfriend!
Good job.
Do you know what I want to say?
I won't tell you too quickly.
Do you remember
the feelings that we had?
I didn't know, and I'm sure
that you didn't know, either.
I don't remember
when it began, exactly.
[THE PERSON I LOVE IS HERE TODAY.]
If it's not too late now
there's something I'd like to tell you.
[THAT'S WHY I'M TRYING TO MUSTER
MY COURAGE TO TELL YOU TODAY.]
Oh my gosh, what if he picks me?
I like you.
I love you.
Don't hesitate anymore.
If you feel the same way I do...
Give me your hand.
The moment you hold
my hand, and look at me...
We'll be together forever.
I like you.
I love you.
Don't hesitate anymore...
Happy 100th day anniversary!
I love you, Eul.
Give me your hand.
The moment you hold
my hand, and look at me...
We'll be together forever.
Forever.
Ha Ru.
Look at this!
Whoa!
[EXCLUSIVE: SHIN JOON YOUNG'S
WOMAN'S IDENTITY REVEALED!]
Whoa. What the hell is this?
This article came up online as
soon as Joon Young pulled that stunt
with Ms. Face-in...
no, I mean, PD No Eul.
- Where the hell is that punk right now?
- He's right there!
He did that in front of all of
his fans, but got rejected
and now he's totally depressed,
so he's just sitting there like that.
I'm sure he feels like he wants to die.
What the hell is this?
I asked you what
the hell this is!
Someone who used to go to high
school with PD No Eul posted this photo.
They took this a long time ago,
and put it on MyWorld.
Who the hell asked you?
What the hell? Did you
date PD No Eul before?
No Eul stole her friend's boyfriend.
Shin Joon Young was her friend.
Wow, all of PD No Eul's private
information is online now.
Wow, these comments are really harsh.
"Everyone in Suyuri
knows this story."
"No Eul's friend was in
so much pain over this."
"I heard she tried to commit suicide."
"Is Shin Joon Young crazy,
going out with a woman like her?"
"This makes no sense!"
"She looks like a gold digger!"
Damn it, I'm going to go crazy!
Who was it? Who the hell
wrote that kind of nonsense...
"He makes his fans
look like total idiots!"
"He shouldn't do that to his fans just
because he's crazy about a woman!"
"How do you leave
Shin Joon Young's fanclub?"
Keep reading them.
"The seducer and the one
who was seduced are both terrible!"
"You're supposed to be shooting
a documentary, not a drama."
"What's Shin Joon Young's vision?
Judging by his taste in women..."
Take screenshots of all these comments
and report it to the police.
I want to meet the people spreading
these baseless rumors face to face
and kill them all myself.
That's not the issue
right now, though.
Now that all her personal info out there
I feel like PD No Eul
is in more danger.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
- She's No Eul, right? Wow.
- Wow, how scary!
- What's wrong with our Joon Young?
- I know.
Who does she think she is?
Bitch.
Are you talking to me?
Hey!
Stupid gold digger.
Who the hell are you
calling a gold digger?
Oh, you're all mad about
the "proposal event", right?
That was all a sham, though!
It was all fake.
Did you really think that was real?
What are you doing?
Stop recording me.
Congratulations on getting such a
wonderful proposal from Shin Joon Young!
It's not like that.
I heard that you two dated
since you were in high school?
What? Who said that?
Stop saying such ridiculous things,
and get this camera out of my face!
You don't know that the internet is
full of stories of you two right now?
[EXCLUSIVE: SHIN JOON YOUNG'S
WOMAN'S IDENTITY REVEALED!]
Stop it, already.
You didn't even check
to see if this was true.
This seems like a clear
violation of human rights to me.
Mister.
Are you her husband?
Well, I don't care about
things like that.
Someone's recording this.
Are you okay with that?
People will think that
all of this is real now.
It doesn't matter.
Will you be okay, though? I'm fine since
I'm a celebrity, and everyone knows me.
But you, it's only a matter of time
before someone digs up dirt on you
if you're caught on camera.
It's Shin Joon Young!
- Joon Young!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[UNCONTROLLABLY FOND]
If you drink any more,
I'll throw you into the ocean.
Have you seen my phone?
Can't you think it over
one more time, Mister?
Let's go out!
Please?
Because of what
you did, Father, I...
I can't go to Eul.
Let's just die. I don't really
want to live, anyway.
That psycho!
Let go of me!
- Hey!
Mister...
Eul. You didn't cause
any trouble, did you?
I heard that your husband is missing.
Joon Young!
Over here!
What if he fell into the ocean?
Looks like Joon Young's
fans will kill Eul soon!
People are calling you
the National Gold Digger!
People even know
what brand of underwear you wear!
Eul.
Should I just give up and
let that other guy have you?