[Uncontrollably Fond]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Episode 6
Where are we going?
I don't know.
And don't ask me to let you out,
because I'm not planning on stopping.
- Oh?
- It's quite late.
I'd like to say the same to you.
I was listening to my
friend's complaints for a while.
Complaints?
My friend...
and my friend's...
younger brother...
liked the same woman.
Oh no.
But my friend's father has a bad
relationship with the woman's family.
So my friend had no choice
but to give up on the girl...
but his little brother
took her hand, and ran off.
This sounds like the plot of
a drama that Mrs. Jang likes.
Right?
How about we ditch our workout
today, and you buy drinks?
Looks like this is the end of the road.
It's not like I can drive
into the ocean and die.
Let's just drown.
I don't really care for
being alive, anyway.
So let's just drown.
I'm sure you wouldn't be able to die
with me if I asked you to, though.
Coward.
- What are you doing?
- I thought you wanted to drown?
Crazy bastard.
You really are a crazy bastard.
If you want to die, die by yourself.
Where are you going?
No Eul!
[Gook Young]
[My Number One Treasure]
The person you're trying
to reach is unavailable.
She's not picking up?
Where did Joon Young take Eul?
I knew he was the type to do
whatever he wanted
but how could he
put on such a spectacle?
Damn it.
Wow... the top ten searched
terms online right now
are all about Shin Joon Young and Eul!
And wow, look at these comments.
It looks like Joon Young's fans
will end up killing Eul soon!
[Jerk of all Jerks]
[Oh Jik]
Hello?
Don't you dare touch
a hair on No Eul's body!
What?
You said that you're the chairwoman
of the Shin Joon Young fan club, right?
If there's even a scratch
on No Eul's body
I'll pay you back 1000 times over!
Tell that to the other stalker-fans, too!
Hey!
And let them know that if they
don't stop with the nasty comments
I'll track their IP addresses and
IDs, and destroy all of them!
This little punk. Do you
even know who I am?
How dare you threaten me?
And you, in particular... you told
people to dig up dirt on PD No, right?
You're dead if I catch you,
so you'd better watch your back.
What the hell?
Where are you? I'll tell my dad and send
the cops there. Tell me your address!
Unit 201, 102 Yeoul Villa,
Ssangmun-dong, Dobong-gu, Seoul.
I'll be happy to face you,
so come and see me any time.
[Dad]
Dad, where are you? Some crazy
bastard is threatening me!
What are you talking about?
Be more clear, Choi Ha Ru.
Why are you answering Dad's phone?
I'm drinking with Father.
He just went to the bathroom.
So? What happened?
I mean, Joon Young--
It's nothing.
Never mind.
Do you even know me?
Why are you prying into my business?
- Oh my.
- Are you all right?
Oh my, why do I feel so drunk?
I don't even think I drank that much.
Your tolerance has gone down, Father.
That's because your mom
is overprotective of me.
- Let's go home.
- Yes.
Huh? Where's my phone?
Is it over here?
Where did it go?
Hey, have you seen my phone?
No.
Where is it?
Here.
Um... what was my number, again?
Um... three, nine.
No, no, that's Na Ri's number.
Seven, three.
Why did he drink so much?
Did you ask him to drink with you?
Yes. I asked him to buy me a drink.
You know that he needs to watch his
health, and that he shouldn't drink!
He's not even getting
much sleep nowadays
because of his work
with the judiciary committee.
I'm sorry.
How can you children
be so self-centered?
I'll go make some honey water.
Change his clothes for him.
- Yes, Mother.
- I'm so mad at you!
Hello?
Hello? You should say
something since you called me.
Do you know...
just how hard it was
for me, all this time?
I tried so hard to pretend
that I didn't like you...
You don't know how hard
that was, do you?
Why were you so good to me?
Why did you always buy me food,
when you didn't even have money?
And why did you buy me clothes?
Why did you buy me clothes, and
worry about whether or not I ate
and even take me to the hospital
when I wasn't feeling well?
Why did you do
all of those things for me?
Even though you were going
to go and reject me twice, like this.
And both times, it was in front of tons
of people! How humiliating!
Why did you make me so confused? Why?
What's so great about
you anyway, Mister?
Huh?
You're older than Shin Joon Young,
and have less money than he does.
You don't even have a car, and
yet Shin Joon Young has three!
You don't own a house,
or a building!
So what right do you
have to reject me?
Give me my phone back.
Mister... can't you just
think it over one more time?
You know, I'm not
really that bad of a catch.
I'll be really good
to you from now on...
so please, say yes, Mister!
Be my boyfriend!
Please?
Hey!
Give me back my phone.
This isn't yours.
It's mine!
Still! Give it back!
I still have stuff to say to Mister!
What else do you have to say?
You've been enough of a nuisance!
Give me back my phone!
Hey!
Are you all right?
Do you want some water?
Yeah.
It's all your fault.
It's because of what you did...
that I can't be with Eul.
Go get my phone.
I told you. It's not your
phone. It's mine.
Go get my phone!
I still have stuff to say to Mister!
If you have that much to say,
go get it yourself!
That damn psycho.
- Get out of there!
- Let go!
- Get out of there.
Stop it!
Let go of me!
Hey!
Ow.
Damn it!
Hey!
Do you not see me?
I just did something
crazy because of you!
But... you still don't see me?
Mister... Mister...
Mister!
Ow!
Mister...
Ow, my head.
Ow.
Why are you guys over there?
Don't you have a hole in your stomach?
I heard that you had five bottles
of soju on an empty stomach.
- I did?
- Well... oh, geez.
Here, the hangover soup is ready.
I'll bring you breakfast
on a table, so just wait a bit.
Wait, but, um...
why are my clothes
hanging over there?
And why am I wearing
these strange clothes?
Wow, I guess you really
don't remember anything.
I heard that your clothes got all wet
because you fell in the water!
And then you drank a ton, and
threw up like crazy on your clothes.
Sheesh, how disgusting!
Your husband went through so much,
changing your clothes for you.
- Husband?
- Yeah.
You don't even remember
your husband?
He's tall, and speaks
with a Seoul dialect.
He's not your husband?
Um, so you're telling me
that my... husband...
no, that bastard...
- changed my clothes for me?
- Yeah.
Who cares? He's your
husband, after all.
It's not like it's the first time
he's seen you naked.
I can't believe this.
[Neungpo - 01]
Damn it.
Where did that bastard go?
Your husband went through so much,
changing your clothes for you.
Who cares? He's your
husband, after all.
It's not like it's the first time
he's seen you naked.
Damn it, I can't even
remember it! Ugh!
Oh, whatever.
[Top Star Shin Joon Young
Flees With Lover After Concert?]
Your phone is all charged, ma'am.
Oh, thank you.
Oh!
You know, I was born and raised here,
and have never left this town!
So you won't charge me
for charging my phone, right?
Oh, of course!
But you know, it's funny that
you're using a Jeollado dialect
when this is Gyeonsangdo.
When did I ever?
Huh?
Hey, Jik. Sorry. You were really
worried about me, right?
Why, did something happen to you?
You didn't see the news,
or the online articles?
When would I have time to do that?
I've been busy with school.
Why? Did something happen?
Um, it's nothing. I'm totally fine,
and nothing happened.
- Are you at school?
- Yeah. Where are you?
I came to the countryside
because of some work.
But I'm on my way
back to Seoul now.
Okay. I'm hanging
up now. Class is starting.
Okay. Make sure
you don't skip meals.
Why did you lie?
You didn't go to school this whole
time, and you haven't gotten any sleep
because you were so
worried about your sister.
If I told her that I was worried about
her, she would have been more upset.
Shin Joon Young, just you
dare and come back here.
I'll kill you.
Wow, I can't believe Mister.
How did he not even call me once?
I guess he wasn't worried about me.
[Husband]
Mister!
- Stop it, already.
- Mister!
Hey, my name is
Shin Joon Young, all right?
I'm not someone who you
should be treating like this!
You honestly don't even realize
how lucky you are right now!
Mister!
If you say "Mister" one more time,
I"ll throw you into the ocean!
Damn it!
Ugh, get off!
Oh... damn it!
[Department Chief No]
I'm sure that expanding overseas would
help improve our company's image
and help our sales increase.
That's what business
is all about, after all. But...
where can I find a proper
proposal for said expansion?
Well, um, you see...
on page 32--
I'm asking because such reasoning...
is unacceptable to me.
Whose fault is this?
Excuse me--
Is this the fault of your employees,
who were told to do this
and made a mistake
due to fatigue from working all night?
Meanwhile, you went
to a sauna to cure your hangover
and then went to play golf?
Or you did do some work,
on this very rare occasion
but because it's been so long
since you've actually done any work
you left in what
should've been taken out
and took out what
should've been left in?
And that's why you submitted
a proposal devoid
of all grounds, meaning,
uniqueness, and creativity?
- That's what I'm curious about.
- I apologize.
I'll fix the shortcomings,
and during the next meeting--
No, don't bother.
- Team Leader Jung.
- Yes, sir?
Please take over this
project and develop it.
Yes, Section Chief.
That concludes our meeting for today.
[Department Chief No]
Oh, it's Mister!
[Shin Joon Young's Manager]
Hello?
- Come on, not you too, Reporter Kim!
- Why didn't you pick up your phone?
- She's not his lover!
- Where are you?
Our Star Shin is under a
lot of stress these days, so...
Joon Young isn't picking up his phone!
Come on, save my hide just
this once, Reporter Kim!
PD No says that she
doesn't know, either.
Please. Please?
All right. Bye.
Why the hell doesn't she know?
She seduced our innocent
Joon Young, took his hand, and left!
In front of all the reporters, too!
You heard all of that, right?
Just tell me.
I'll keep it a secret.
I didn't seduce him!
I'm a victim--
I'm a victim too, all right?
And who the hell are
you calling innocent?
That bastard is such a jerk
and so seductive...
Oh, geez.
Here.
You're not going to fix anything
by just wiping her off like that.
Change her clothes
so she doesn't catch a cold.
Thank you.
- Um, excuse me.
- What?
Um, I'm really sorry, but could you
put these new clothes on her?
Are your hands broken?
Why are you asking me to do that?
You said that she's
your wife, didn't you?
Yes, that's right.
But, um, you see...
I find having to change out of
my own clothes such a nuisance
that I've been wearing these
clothes for a week now!
Mister...
Seems to me like Shin Joon Young's life
is like a ridiculous drama now
just because of one woman.
No, no.
I feel like this isn't harsh enough.
"Shin Joon Young is a has-been now.
He's on an express train to retirement."
How's that, Ms. Shin?
- It's pretty good, right?
- Oh, nice, "Pretty Spy"!
"Wow. Shin Joon Young, who
was so popular, has totally lost it."
How was that, Boss?
- It's pretty good, right?
- Nice, "Deuk Dragon"!
"Good", my ass!
I've caught you all now!
I left you all alone because
we all know each other
but do I look like
an idiot to you? Huh?
"Pretty Spy" and "Deuk Dragon". Prepare
to have lawsuit paperwork sent to you!
- Ms. Shin!
- Boss!
They didn't do anything wrong.
I told them to do all of that
so if you're going to sue someone
or send someone to jail, send me.
- Ms. Shin!
- Isn't that a little extreme?
Your one and only son is embroiled
in this sort of situation
the least that you could do
is worry about him!
Is that really something
that a parent should be saying?
- Are you really even his mother?
- Please, not you too.
No, don't hold me back. I held
back all this time for Joon Young
but I can't stand it anymore.
I really need to say my peace today.
Say your piece, eh?
What the hell do you have to say to me?
Wow, are you speaking
informally to me right now?
I'm older than you, you know!
Don't you see all my white hair?
Why don't you speak informally
to me too, then, punk?
Ms. Shin!
You went and took my son,
who was studying so hard
and you turned him into
some damn road show!
What could you possibly
have to say to me?
Road show?
Road show!
How could you call the greatest
Hallyu star a mere "road show"?
Other parents treat people
like me as if I saved their life
if I get their kids to be
as popular as Joon Young!
They bow down and thank me.
Then go and make other
people's kids into stars
and have them kiss your ass
for the rest of your life!
Why did you have to go
and hang around my Joon Young?
Wow, I totally get it now.
I totally get why Joon Young is such a
mess and does whatever the hell he wants!
It'd be weird for him to be normal, when
he was raised by such a psychotic mom!
Wow, I feel so bad for Joon Young!
What did you just
say, you little shit?
"Psychotic?" I'll
show you psychotic!
Father!
- Let him go, Jung Shik.
- Apologize right now!
Say, "I'm sorry, I couldn't tame my
tongue because I lost my temper."
and apologize
to Joon Young's mom right now!
Let him go, already!
Ok, do you know
what "psychotic" means?
It means the same thing as
"crazy bitch". That's what it means.
He just called you a crazy bitch,
so how could I do nothing?
Just do nothing.
Please, just do nothing!
You, leave Joon Young alone.
And you, leave Joon Young alone!
And you two, leave him alone!
Just back off
for a damn second, all of you!
No, we can't just do nothing! We have
to find Joon Young before we do that!
Gook Young... get me out of this.
Father, let go, already!
Ms. Shin told you to just sit still!
- Ow!
- Why, I ought to...
Ow!
I am being still. How could
I be more still than this?
My Ok told me not to lay
a finger on him, so I'm not!
Let me go.
- Come on, Dad.
- What?
Where did that punk go?
And who the hell is that girl?
Ok, Choi Hyun Joon went
to his son's concert.
Did you find out why
Shin Joon Young was at the hospital?
Hallyu has surpassed
our expectations in China.
There's a lot of demand for Korean
movies, movies, music, and beauty items.
I'm quite surprised at the popularity of
Hallyu in China. And I'm so thankful.
The most popular Korean celebrity
among Chinese people is...
Shin Joon Young.
Shin Joon Young is
quite popular in China.
Oh, my daughter
really likes him, too.
That's why I didn't like him
that much, to be honest.
I'm sorry, but please
excuse me for a second.
- Escort these gentleman.
- Yes, sir.
Shin Young Ok?
Young Ok.
Oh, it's been a while.
There you go again,
calling me Young Ok.
It's me, Madame Song.
From Bovari, in Samsung-dong,
five years ago.
You remember that place, right?
I was waiting for you
for a really long time.
I can't believe that you didn't
come back once after you were elected.
That was quite disappointing.
[Madame Song's Salon]
Drop by sometime.
I started a new shop
in Cheongdam-dong.
- Do I really need to do all this?
- Yeah, you do.
You're the National Gold Digger
right now!
Everyone in this country has become
stalker-fans, and they're out to get you!
What?
Do you know how bad
it's gotten online?
People are saying that you're
shooting Joon Young's documentary...
- because you did something bad to him.
- What?
Apparently, you have a secret video,
and you're blackmailing him with it!
Who the hell is saying
that kind of nonsense?
And you're telling me that people
are actually buying this garbage?
Yeah, they are. And even if it's
revealed later that it isn't true
people will still believe
what they want to believe.
Well, still, they blurred out
my face on the newspaper.
Only newspapers are doing that.
Your face is all over the internet!
Your address, and even the brand of
underwear you wear has all been exposed!
What should I do, then?
Do I really have to emigrate?
- [Shin Joon Young's Manager]
- Damn it.
You really don't know
where Joon Young is?
You're with him, right?
And you're just lying to me!
I'm not lying!
Are you not satisfied with making
me the National Gold Digger
that you're trying to make me
out to be the National Liar, too?
I don't know where
Shin Joon Young is
so report him to the cops
if you're so frustrated!
He's the one who
kidnapped me, anyway!
Report him for kidnapping, and--
What?
Damn it.
You kept inviting me to your place. But
you're wussing out, now that I'm here?
Not exactly.
It's just that someone so ugly
is standing so close to me.
So I was a bit taken aback.
You little...
What's your relationship
with that woman?
What is she to you that you're
so intent on protecting her
and you threatened to kill
me if I laid a hand on her?
That's exactly our relationship.
It is justifiable for me to act that way.
So be careful, so that I don't
have to keep nagging you.
Where is that woman right now?
Why? So you can tell other people,
and actually end up killing her?
No, it's not like that! Whatever.
Just tell me where she is.
I don't know, either.
Joon Young has been off our radar
ever since he disappeared with that girl.
I've been on social media all day,
but nobody has seen him!
I heard that woman goes crazy for
money, so what if she sold him off--
Hey! Hey! Hey!
If you have any other garbage thoughts,
toss them in here before you come out.
- You little--
- No, no.
Just make yourself
at home in here, okay?
You'd better get ready for a lawsuit!
I told you that my dad used to be
a famous prosecutor, right?
Why should I be punished for throwing
trash into the correct receptacle?
Shouldn't I be praised, instead?
Ow! Ow!
[Shin Joon Young's Manager]
Damn it.
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
Why'd you get up? Do you feel like
you're going to throw up again?
Damn it.
Do you really not know where
Joon Young is? Are you sure?
I really don't.
He was already gone
when I woke up.
His car was still next to the ocean,
but I'm sure Joon Young...
no, Mr. Shin Joon Young,
took his car and left by now.
I'll text you the address.
Damn it!
Eul, you're a real star now, aren't you?
Um... that's not me.
I know that you can't
be caught by others.
But where did you
leave Shin Joon Young?
And why are you sitting here,
with another man?
I told you,
none of that is true!
- Bong Sook.
- Yeah?
It looks like
the tripe is burning!
It's all right. Those little suckers
will just take care of themselves.
What?
That was a joke!
It was funny, right?
You didn't know that I was
a funny woman too, did you?
Leave me an autograph
before you go, Ms. Star!
Isn't it a bit of a nuisance
to wear sunglasses indoors?
You're so clumsy as it is...
Yes, it is a nuisance.
You're jealous, right?
If you hadn't run away, you
could've become a star, like me.
I know, right?
I guess I'm not as blessed.
You're a coward.
Yeah.
You're despicable.
Why are you here?
If you let go of my hand and left,
you shouldn't have come back
if only out of sheer embarrassment.
You're right, but...
And I really tried to stay away, but...
the fact that I'm sitting
across from you like this...
is honestly just as shocking to me
as it is to you.
The noodles will get soggy.
I should've taken you to eat hangover
soup since I bet you're not feeling well.
Oh.
But, um, how did you know
that I drank last night?
You called me,
while you were really drunk.
When did I do that?
I checked my call logs,
but I didn't see you there.
You used Shin Joon Young's
phone to call me.
Was... Shin Joon Young
next to you when you called me?
I don't know.
So, what did I say to you?
What did I say when I called?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
[Jung Eun]
Just a second.
Let me take this call.
What kind of trouble did you
cause this time, No Eul?
- Yeah, Jung Eun?
- What are you up to, Ji Tae?
I'm in a meeting.
Oh, sorry for calling you
while you were working.
It's fine. You're okay, right?
Of course.
But, Ji Tae...
Did you go to Shin Joon Young's
concert yesterday?
- No.
- Oh. So you didn't.
Why?
No, it's just that someone told me
that they saw you at the concert.
I don't have enough free time to be
going to see celebrities' concerts.
Exactly. I guess they mistook
someone else for you.
I told them that they
were probably wrong.
Jung Eun.
Do you want to have dinner
with me tomorrow, if you have time?
What's so great about
you anyway, Mister?
You're older than Shin Joon Young,
and have less money that he does.
You don't even have a car.
Shin Joon Young has three!
You don't own a house, or a building!
So what right do you have
to reject me?
Give me my phone back.
Mister... can't you just
think it over one more time?
You know, I'm not really
that bad of a catch.
I'll be really good
to you from now on...
so please, say yes, Mister!
Be my boyfriend!
Please?
Enjoy.
Eul.
What should I do, No Eul?
This crazy girl who has her back turned
toward me... has never once cared for me.
And wants some poor guy who
threw her away... so what should I do?
Despite everything, I am
the one and only Shin Joon Young.
Should I try to convince you
to stop wanting him?
Should I threaten you? Say I'll
hit you if you keep wanting him?
It's clear that there's
something off with you...
so should I drag you to the hospital
tomorrow to get you checked?
Or...
I may have waited too long
to tell you that I like you.
Should I give up on you,
and let you go to that guy?
- Did Eul go somewhere?
- She left not too long ago.
You didn't see her?
Is she actually from
a really rich family?
It looks like I'm right, judging
from your expression.
So that's why Shin Joon Young
took her hand and ran away.
Oh my. I hope I haven't
done anything to upset her!
Taxi!
- Where would you like to go?
- Geoje.
What?
Please take me to Geoje. Hurry!
We're here.
[402,800 won]
Here.
Thank you.
Wait, can't you give me
a teensy discount?
- There's a fixed price for taxi fares.
- Oh.
Can I pay it off in installments
for 12 months, then?
Oh, Ms. Face-in-a-dish-of-water!
You still haven't found him?
I've gotten people
to search this whole area
but nobody has seen him!
He didn't go back to Seoul?
A big star like Joon Young
wouldn't have left his car here
to take public transportation!
Did you report this to the police?
What? If something bad happens
and reporters find out about this
we'll be in even more trouble!
He didn't... fall into
the ocean, did he?
Joon Young!
Where are you?
Tell me if you've fallen
into the ocean and died!
What if he actually
fell into the ocean?
What do you mean? We'd have to go
in there and get him, of course!
You didn't kill him to try and take
his money and valuables, did you?
Even his watch alone
is worth millions of won!
What?
You really like money, right?
Yeah, I killed him! I wanted
his money, so I killed him!
How much money do you have?
Want me to kill you too? Huh?
Um, no. I have no money. I, um...
all I have are loans and debts.
I can't believe you rejected his
proposal in front of so many people!
Joon Young has a huge ego, you know!
If he really did something bad
because of you, I'll make you regret it!
Where did he go?
Oh my. You didn't go back to Seoul yet?
Granny!
Here, eat this.
I heard that your husband went missing.
A bunch of people came by my place
last night asking me when he left
what you two did, and whether
or not he said anything strange.
They were interrogating me like
an adulterous wife, I tell you!
He really didn't say that he
was going somewhere?
No, he didn't!
He just gave me a huge fistful of money
asked me to make you some hangover soup
when you woke up, and to give you
clothes since yours weren't dry.
Damn it!
Eul, you really didn't
cause any trouble, did you?
You didn't say, "You asshole! Go die! A
ghost should come and get you!" Right?
You didn't say those kinds of
things to Shin Joon Young, did you?
Damn it!
Granny!
Where is this place?
That? That's the island,
way out over there.
Is it close?
Yeah. A 40 minute boat ride
will get you there.
[First Boat: 7:30 a.m.]
Um, I'm really sorry, Captain, but could
you give me a ride on your boat?
Joon Young!
Shin Joon Young!
Where are you,
Shin Joon Young?
if you're not here?
Where are you hiding,
you bastard?
Hello, it's No Eul. You still
haven't found Joon Young?
No, I haven't. I really feel like
something happened to him.
If I can't find him after looking for him
today, I'm reporting it to the police!
I...
How can you manage to fall asleep,
when you've worried so many people?
Are you shooting a movie, or something?
Way to look like a movie star.
I must be crazy. I did such crazy things
because I was worried about you!
I took an expensive cab
ride from here to Seoul!
I couldn't even sleep
because I was shivering
in the cold, waiting for a boat!
I even got bitten by a seagull!
Oh my gosh, my money!
I could've bought my Jik so much
meat with that kind of money!
You're thinking that
all of this is a dream, right?
It's not.
I'm really Eul.
I came all the way here to find you!
Wow, you must really
think that you're dreaming.
I'm telling you,
I'm really Eul!
Sheesh.
You'll come to your senses
after I pinch you.
Leave.
What?
I said leave.
I'm telling you to go screw yourself.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Uncontrollably Fond]
I didn't tell you that I become
a total nutcase when I drink?
Oh, I really want to apologize!
Hit me until you're
not mad anymore. Here.
If I ever drink again,
I'm a dog! A damn dog!
A neurological disease?
It seems the location of the tumor
is making it hard to perform surgery.
I heard that you saw that photo.
Christmas Rose... I have
nothing to give to you.
I'll make you regret it.
If Shin Joon Young wasn't
messing around
but he was actually being serious...
if he really does like me...
What should I do, then?
I'm not going to let you have Eul.
I'm going to keep her for myself.
Stop it already, Mr. Shin Joon Young.