Then let's end it here.
With this gun,
Cho Myung Geun, you...
and I...
will all lose.
Do you really think so?
Cho Myung Geun ran away from the company knowing all the secrets.
If you don't get rid of him,
the organisation will collapse.
I'm holding the key.
Don't you know that?
Do you have the nerve to pull that trigger?
Well...
We'll see.
Kang Tae Woo.
Especially in choosing a woman.
We're dating right now.
Protect Yu Jin.
It's...
too late to go back now.
You need to get used to it.
Drink it.
It's a lot harder than...
you thought, right?
How do you feel?
You're not...
regretting it already, are you?
Of course not.
I like it so much.
Now that I gave you what you wanted,
let's finish talking about Cho Myung Geun.
No.
There is a problem that we have to solve first.
A problem?
Jung Yu Jin.
(Case 11, In the Collapsed World)
Tae Woo.
We're in trouble. I think they know who we are.
Untie me.
I think we should get out of here.
Let's hurry up and go.
We have to go now.
- I'm not going.
-  What?
I won't let you go, either.
Now,
it's too late to go back now.
What are you talking about?
Yu Jin.
Listen to me carefully.
You look strange.
Of course.
I've changed.
What?
How is this possible?
Challenger.
This is the real secret that they've been hiding.
They already know who we are.
What we can choose is...
to die now...
or to die later.
That's the only choices we have.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
And now,
I'm going to do a test...
in order to save you.
What happened?
It looks like we can't issue a warranty right now.
Are you just going to sit back and watch?
Let's wait.
- How much longer? After they die?
-  Hey!
Watch your tongue.
Tae Woo.
Where are you? Hey!
- Hey! What are you doing?
-  Hello. Is Yu Jin all right?
San.
We don't have much time. Listen to me carefully.
We found out where Cho Myung Geun is hiding.
And?
And...
- they captured Yu Jin.
-  What?
I'll go and save Yu Jin.
You should catch Cho Myung Geun.
I'll send you the address.
What did he say?
What are you trying to do?
Everything is up to San now.
He will either come to rescue you...
or go to catch Cho Myung Geun.
What difference does it make?
If he goes to catch Cho Myung Geun,
he will die with honour.
If he comes to rescue you,
I will kill him.
Tae Woo.
Are you out of your mind?
You're mine now.
Please...
let me kill San.
If you kill him,
I won't be able to see you.
Is that so?
Then promise me one thing.
Promise me...
that you'll become one of us.
Hey!
- Are you crazy?
-  I have to go.
Those two are discovered.
If they find out about you, what happens to our mission?
We're detectives.
Our mission comes first. Follow orders.
- Sir.
-  No.
Goo Hyung.
Please.
I promised Yu Jin that I'll protect her.
I have to go.
You're following us, right?
We'll take a right turn after about 2km.
Check again when the backup force will be here.
As I said, be careful. I have a bad feeling about this.
Check your equipment again.
Gosh, you look really tense.
I have to be. We must catch him today.
This will be our last chance.
I don't feel good about this.
No matter what happens,
we should trust and protect each other, okay?
Wear it at all times.
Thank you.
This is totally a rural area. I don't think we can find him here.
Don't act hastily. Stay sharp.
He may not be alone.
Four of you, follow me. The rest will go from the back, okay?
San.
Where's Yu Jin?
You go that way, and I'll go this way.
Okay.
Are you all right?
Why are you here?
Yu Jin, I think we need to hurry. Let's go.
Let's hurry.
(Hot spots 15 dollars, children 10 dollars)
Yu Jin, we'll get out of here. Don't worry.
It's okay now.
San, get on!
Get them!
Isn't that...
Isn't that someone's jacket?
Yu Jin, are you all right?
Yes. I'm fine.
- What about you?
-  I'm perfectly fine. Don't worry.
We'll be reprimanded.
We ruined the mission.
It's okay. We'll just quit if we have to.
I'm sorry, but I feel really sick.
Can you pull over?
Sure.
Hold on.
Look at me. Is it really bad?
What you did today...
was too dangerous.
I did it to protect you.
- It's cold. Let's go to...
-  No.
Then...
keep this on for now. I'll get you a blanket.
I'll be right back.
San.
Yu Jin...
Watch out!
I'm sorry.
Yu Jin! Yu Jin!
Yu Jin!
Here.
Let's eat.
It's been days. Just a spoon, please?
You need to get better.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
You disgust me.
Don't act like you care.
Just leave me alone.
Drink a little bit at a time.
If you drink a lot at once, you might get disgusted.
I don't need it.
Take it away.
It's hard, isn't it?
That's how it is in the beginning.
You become sensitive...
and sharp.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
I'm relieved.
I didn't let you kill San.
He died anyway.
I'm here with you.
You'd better get used to it.
Yu Jin, you know what?
When you're reading a book or focusing on something,
you're really pretty.
- You know what?
-  What?
You said the same thing when you asked me out for the first time.
- Did I?
-  Yes. Who else did you say that to?
Who else would I say it to? I'm just a little embarrassed.
Are you really quitting?
Someone should take the responsibility. Two of us died.
Why do you have to be the one?
It's my fault, too.
Let's have a drink sometime.
I'll see you later.
Do you miss...
the sunlight?
You still haven't let it go.
What are you doing?
Things like this...
don't suit you any more.
Why are you sitting here all lonely?
How did you come here?
How? I walked here.
Are you laughing at me? You just laughed, right?
I saw you laughing a little.
That's a little better.
I haven't seen you smile for a long time.
Why are you here?
Why?
Why do you think I'm here? I was just passing by.
Don't be surprised.
Ta-da.
I'm starting fresh.
(Private Detective Yong Goo Hyung)
- Private detective?
-  Yes.
Don't you want to join?
Do you want to join me?
Are you laughing again?
You're laughing at me.
It was hard to suggest you to do this together.
You should think about it. You shouldn't laugh at me.
One of us got fired from being a detective.
And the other got shot and has trouble living.
Do you think it will go well if those two do a business together?
Of course it will. We're the perfect partners.
Are you serious, or are you just messing around?
I'm just messing around. Give it back.
Sometimes, life gives you...
unfair incidents that don't make any sense.
When that happens, people need someone to talk to.
Even if we can't promise to solve anything,
we can at least investigate on their problems.
You have an unsolved problem, too.
You're smart and I'm a meddler. If we work together,
it might work out.
I'll be generous and give you one more chance.
You don't have to give me an answer right now.
Think about it, and give me a call if you're interested.
I'll be going then.
Goo Hyung.
If I become a private detective,
do you think I'll be able to find the answer to my question?
(Private Detective Yong Goo Hyung)
(Restricted area)
Did the taxi driver take you here safely?
- Tae Woo.
-  Stop.
Do not come closer.
I'm not sure what I will do to you.
San.
This is my last regard as your friend.
Don't show your face...
to me...
or to Yu Jin.
Hey. Where on earth have you been?
Did you get some sleep? You should sleep at home.
Goo Hyung.
He's alive.
Did you meet him?
Good morning.
Surprise! I made you some juice.
I made juice.
Goo Hyung! Goo Hyung!
This is embarrassing.
Isn't it frustrating? Why do they have so many secrets?
By the way, why did you give me juice...
when you're drinking wine in the morning?
Do you want some? Shall I pour you a glass?
No, thank you.
Anyway, it must have hurt your feelings.
You're in the same team.
I know.
Why are they always whispering? Are they going out or something?
- Se Ra.
-  Yes?
Do you think I'm troublesome?
No. Why would you think that?
My personality is more like a man than a girl.
I'm definitely not amiable.
Then again, why would anyone want to be closer to me?
You're wrong, Gyeo Wool. You're so attractive.
Stop it already.
Se Ra. Is there anything you know?
I know Goo Hyung comes here often.
I don't know anything.
There's one thing that I know for certain.
What?
Both of them care a great deal about you.
Everyone except you knows this.
That's right. I think San is looking for someone.
Who?
He asked Doctor Hwang to find someone.
He won't talk.
More.
Watch and see how long he lasts.
Where is...
Joo Young Gwang?
I didn't kill him yet.
Don't you dare touch a hair on him.
If you do, you'll regret it.
I'll let him go peacefully if you give me what I want.
I guess...
I've raised a tiger.
That tiger...
is losing his patience.
Stop.
What are you doing?
- Cut him.
-  Yes, Sir.
I'm giving you time.
How long do you think it'll take for all the blood to drain?
A day? Maybe two?
Get me the list before then.
I'll...
make a promise.
If something goes wrong with him...
by the time I return,
I'll...
rip Yu Jin apart in front of you.
- Get him.
-  San.
- Pull.
-  Get him.
- Yes.
-  That's good.
- Hold him.
-  He got it.
- Roll.
-  Go.
- Go.
-  Do it.
- Go!
-  You can do it.
You can do it.
- Nice.
-  Good one.
Yes, Kang Tae Woo.
San, are you all right?
Hey. I'll put up a better fight next time.
Please, I'm begging you. I'm sick of beating you.
What is he saying?
You should beat him in track and field next time.
- He'll lose right away then.
-  Fine.
You two just can't stop making fun of me.
Do whatever you want.
San, be careful.
Please take good care of her.
I will.
San, get on!
Yu Jin!
It's Tae Woo for certain.
I heard his voice.
You said you couldn't find him when you searched.
- It might not be him.
-  No.
They're both alive.
Fine. Let's assume they are.
What are you going to do?
You don't even know where to start.
I know that.
Take a seat.
Please...
help my brother.
What on earth is going on?
I can't seem to grasp it.
Who are you anyway?
You really have an exquisite taste.
It won't do you any good to sneak around here.
I left something really important...
with you.
What?
It'll be the key that will...
save both you and me.
Also Yu Jin.
What do you mean?
Like I said,
Yu Jin came back from the dead.
You must already know...
what that means.
What did you leave with us?
The helper list.
- Goo Hyung.
-  Yes?
Check this out.
Helper?
The helper list?
Do you mean the list from the club?
You have it, right?
You have one hour.
Bring it to me.
If you do,
I'll let you see Yu Jin.
Han Gyeo Wool.
You look a lot like Han Gyu Min.
You know my brother?
Of course.
We were...
very special to each other.
- Where is it?
-  I don't have it.
- I don't have such a thing.
-  Goo Hyung.
I won't give it to you even if I have it.
- Don't speak a word.
-  The car Yu Jin was in...
exploded in front of me,
but they say she's still alive.
I have to see her.
I have to find out...
what happened to her.
- San.
-  Goo Hyung.
Who is the woman just walked out?
Did you drink? What are you talking about?
Who is she?
She fooled us as Moon Mee Jin, right?
Why would she come here? Are you crazy?
Then who is the woman?
A client.
Come to think of it, they look alike.
Their height, hair colour and everything...
What did she ask for?
What do you think it is?
She's having an affair, but her lover is...
having another affair. She wants photo evidence.
Why do we always get such lowbrow cases?
We should get to it since we're on it.
She looked like she is mean. Hey, Gyeo Wool.
Can you get me a USB flash drive?
- A USB flash drive?
-  Yes.
For what?
We have to send it to the client.
With the evidence of the adultery.
Is that so?
All right.
Okay. Good night.
Hello. I'm the new lodger.
- Welcome.
-  Hello.
I'll take care of you until the end.
Really? You said until the end.
It means forever.
Okay.
My gosh.
You make my life so fun. Let's go.
- Goo Hyung.
-  Yes?
Let's be prepared.
Right. It can be dangerous. You've grown up.
I'll bring them now.
I guess...
this is the end for us.
Gosh.
You called me sooner than I expected.
Were you scared?
He's still...
alive, right?
You're playing it cool.
I'm sure you don't have enough time for that.
Joo Young Gwang.
Where is he?
Let me see it first.
What is this?
Hey. Is this how much Joo Young Gwang means to you?
What's up with that face?
Didn't you know?
Did you?
Those guarding Jung Yu Jin were attacked.
What did you say?
Goodness.
- Where did San go?
-  How should I know?
Maybe he's meeting a client.
Oh, the adulterer.
Do you mean here?
What are you talking about?
Don't you get it?
The USB flash drive that San took.
I put a locating device on it.
What?
You didn't think I would lend it to him so easily, did you?
That's not how I do it.
Hey. Be honest.
Did you put any tricks here?
- I did.
-  What?
You shouldn't have left me out.
Do you realise how important this is?
I don't. You should have told me if it's that important.
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
She was here, wasn't she?
- I'm asking if she was here.
-  Be quiet!
Go.
I can't stay with you.
What do you mean?
- You shouldn't be here.
-  Yu Jin.
You saw me die.
- Think of me as a dead person.
-  Yu Jin, don't do this.
Let's go.
Yu Jin, we don't have time. Let's go.
We can't run away from this.
Yu Jin, are you all right?
What's your plan?
There must be a way.
Tae Woo will come after us.
I can't let you go.
Gyeo Wool, can you check on the last location?
- I'm coming, too.
-  No, stay here.
- No, I want to come.
-  I said stay here!
It's dangerous.
I can't stay here by myself.
Gyeo Wool, please.
I'll call you if something happens.
You'll have to support us then.
When we're back, I'll tell you everything...
about what you're curious about.
Okay?
Tae Woo.
You really are alive.
How did you...
It's been a while.
How have you been?
I guess you came to find San.
Where is he?
That's what I want to ask.
I see.
It seems like...
you'll help us find him.
Get him.
Why aren't you asking...
what happened to me?
I know you don't want to talk about it.
You don't have to.
Wait here.
Bring San and Yu Jin to me.
(Vampire Detective)
I'll give you the real help.
You have to trust me. We don't have time.
Are you really with Yu Jin?
As for Yu Jin, they'll get rid of her as a runaway.
She won't be able to get away with it.
Sorry about that. I know you feel inferior to San.
I'll show you the consequences of breaking a promise.
If you can't find in time, you'll all die.
You have nothing to gain from this game,
and I have nothing to lose.
What did you do to San?
If you act hastily, Goo Hyung will die.
Kill him when I give you the signal.
You'll get to see how San breaks down.