[Personal Details Report]
I guess our past no longer exists.
Do you think...
anyone will remember us...
if we die from this secret mission?
We'll disappear without a trace.
I'll remember you.
(Case 12, The Night Again)
I think it's safe. Let's go.
Wait here.
What?
In case you lead the organisation later,
I don't think Jung Yu Jin...
should become an exception to termination through death...
since she's a runaway.
You better not just throw things out.
The number you're calling is not available...
Why can't I reach them?
Are you awake now?
You're not as fast as you used to be.
You're not like your old self, either.
You're being rude to your senior.
Is that so?
I was going easy on you because of our old friendship.
What is it that you want?
I'm sorry, but I don't have time to chat away.
Where's San?
Why are you doing this?
You, San and Yu Jin...
are all friends.
Friends?
Friends, you say?
Was San ever my friend?
He doesn't care about anyone else.
He only thinks about himself.
I guess one thing didn't change.
You still feel inferior to him, don't you?
What do you think you're doing?
We don't know the situation yet. Don't act hastily.
I don't take orders from you.
I'm the one on the field. I'll decide what to do.
- I'll go first.
- I'll go.
I'll go. Don't let pride get to you.
I think you're the one who can't let go of his pride.
But... This is real.
I'm not stupid enough to hear that from you.
He died anyway.
I'm here with you.
I'll protect you.
Are you still obsessed about Yu Jin?
You'd better watch your tongue.
Soon, you'll see...
how I destroy San.
San.
What on earth is going on?
Sun Young, I'm sorry. I don't have time to explain.
I asked my brothers to do it. I'll tell them to rush it.
Okay. Thank you.
By the way,
are you really with Yu Jin now?
Yes.
I'll explain it to you later. Please hurry up.
All right. I got it.
There must be a reason why you're doing this.
I'll get the identification cards and passports.
Okay. Thank you.
Who was it?
Was it...
Goo Hyung?
No, it was Sun Young. You remember her, right?
I do.
How are they?
They're doing fine as always.
By the way,
you really seem to be fine.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure...
what exactly happened to me.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
Don't be.
I just thought...
it's been a long time since I saw sunlight.
It's been so long since I walked along the street in the sun,
met my friends...
and had delicious dishes.
This is Choi Sun Young.
San called and asked me to get him fake ID cards and passports.
I'm sending you his location because I'm worried about him.
Is everything okay?
Wow.
Thank you, Goo Hyung.
This is very helpful.
Bring San and Yu Jin to me.
Yes, Sir.
Yu Jin. Are you okay?
I'll be right back.
Please...
let me kill San.
If you kill him,
I won't be able to see you.
Then promise me one thing.
Promise me...
that you'll become one of us.
Find them!
- Yes, Sir!
Get Jung Yu Jin first.
- You little...
- Come here!
You jerk!
Come over here!
Are you okay, Yu Jin?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Yu Jin. You need to trust me. We don't have much time.
Wake up.
Hey.
Please.
Please wake up.
San.
The number you're calling is not available...
What are they up to? Why can't I reach them?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
I said what are you doing?
Where is...
the helper list?
You!
What do you think you're doing?
Han Gyeo Wool.
That's how much time we have left.
What are you talking about?
It means everyone will die...
if you don't find it before then.
Tell me. Where is it?
The helper list.
The helper list?
I don't care about such a thing.
What happened to my brother?
Gyu Min?
I don't have...
the time to explain something so insignificant.
You little!
Also, you should be...
more worried about San right now.
What did you do to him?
You must know that better than me.
What did you do...
with that USB flash drive?
Yes. Understood.
I'm sorry I'm making you so much trouble.
No. You're no trouble at all.
Sun Young promised to come here with our passports.
It's going to be like this.
Even if we leave, we won't be safe.
Don't give up on me.
San.
Don't ever stop.
Don't ever give up.
I won't, either.
That's what you said. We shouldn't give up.
Hey, Yu Jin. Close your eyes.
- What?
- Hurry up.
Isn't...
today's weather so nice?
The ocean is beautiful.
And the sunlight feels warm.
The sunlight is so warm.
Don't lose it again.
Okay?
We found where Jung Yu Jin is.
Where's San?
Where's San? You punks.
Hey. Let go of me! I'll kill you.
You're distracting me. Stay still.
I told you...
not to be rude to me.
No way.
Your USB flash drive...
Did you turn it into a tracking device?
You better...
hand it over.
No.
It's your last chance.
Give it to me.
You have to take me with you.
I don't want to lose anyone any more.
- Goo Hyung!
- San.
San!
San, run away.
Listen carefully.
You two will have to come with us.
If you do anything hasty,
your friend will die.
You better behave well.
When I give you the sign, kill him.
If this call turns off,
kill him right away.
That girl will take the second car.
And you. You'll take another car behind her.
Where are we going?
Get off.
What are you saying?
And hand over the list.
Why are we here all of a sudden?
I told you before.
We're running out of time.
You can't handle them by yourself.
So go.
Ask for help.
Why should I believe you?
You said you want to protect the people you love.
So do I.
Listen carefully.
If something goes wrong, I will kill you.
San.
Goo Hyung is...
someone important to you.
I'll go first and wait for you there.
I'll meet you there.
Yu Jin.
Don't worry.
Detective Park!
Gyeo Wool. What are you doing here? It's late.
- We need to go right now.
- Hold on.
- Hurry up!
- Where are we going?
- Hold on. I have to finish eating.
- Hurry up.
Just one second. Hold on.
Goodness!
What is it?
Yu Jin.
I'll show you the consequences...
of breaking a promise.
- I'm coming, too.
- No, stay here.
- No, I want to come.
- I said stay here!
It's dangerous.
Can't you tell me what it is?
I just had something to take care of.
Let me come with you next time. We're a team.
There's one thing that I know for certain.
What?
Both of them care a great deal about you.
Everyone except you knows this.
Please.
Is this the fastest way?
Yes. There isn't much traffic during this time.
By the way, don't bang your head against the window.
You'll get a bump on your head.
Sometimes, I leave the toilet when I'm not done yet,
but I've never left food unfinished until today.
We're going to be lucky today.
You can trust me on this.
I told you, San.
I told you that was my last regard as your friend.
Where are Goo Hyung and Yu Jin?
Why?
Can't you figure out where they are today?
You used to take a look around and speak as if you knew it all.
Go ahead and take a look around.
Can you figure out where they are?
Can't you?
I never liked how you talk so confidently.
Today,
I'll show you that your confidence is wrong.
Tae Woo.
I'm sorry for everything.
Don't do this.
What are you sorry for?
I'm going to give you a gun.
There is only one bullet inside.
Do you see two people over there?
One is Joo Young Gwang whom Yo Na has been looking for.
The other one is Yong Goo Hyung, your dear friend.
You can't be sure of who is sitting on either side.
All you have to do is shoot one of them.
You're a private detective.
Why are you getting excited already?
It's too early to get excited.
Yu Jin.
Do you remember that lamp?
Let her go right now.
You still don't get it, do you?
Yu Jin!
Do you get it now?
I order and you listen.
You won't...
get anything from this.
Of course I will.
If you shoot Goo Hyung,
you'll spend the rest of your life regretting it.
If you shoot Young Gwang,
I'll be the master of this organisation and get everything.
You're the one who has nothing to gain in this game.
I have nothing to lose.
Give him the gun.
Gosh. I'm dying to know...
what your face is going to look like when you break down.
We don't have time. Hurry up and shoot!
When will the others arrive?
They just got notified. They'll be a little late.
We should hurry up.
All right.
I would die if I were a human.
But you and I...
aren't humans any more.
San.
I'll count to 10.
If you don't make a decision by then,
Yu Jin will die.
In 10...
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
This is why I told you to be prepared. You're still an amateur.
You always have my back.
Five...
Four...
Three...
- You're having breakfast, right?
- No. I don't have appetite.
Even if you don't, you have to eat breakfast.
Breakfast is important.
San! Wake up!
Two...
One...
Did you really shoot?
Whom did he shoot? Check.
It hurts more...
than I imagined.
How dare you...
lay a finger on Young Gwang?
If you want to hunt,
you should have trained your hunting dog well.
You!
Do you see this?
The helper list...
is now in my hands.
You should be careful to decide...
who your real boss is.
Give him the gun.
You better make the right choice if you're a hunting dog.
Three...
Two...
You better make the right choice if you're a hunting dog.
Who the owner is...
and who the hunting dog is.
You're definitely a hunting dog.
You showed up barking.
You better make the right choice if you're a hunting dog.
One...
What should we do?
Get rid of him.
Okay.
Get him.
It seems like...
- your friend needs some help.
- San...
San.
San, are you okay?
Hold on.
I'll free you.
You won't die,
but it's better to be safe.
We have to save Yu Jin.
- Hold on.
- Yu Jin...
Hold on.
Please.
I guess you didn't drink any blood for a while.
San! San!
Let's hurry. Come on.
Get up.
I can't let you go like this.
Eun Hye.
I've murdered...
so many people.
Each time,
I was really scared to be honest.
I couldn't sleep.
I couldn't eat.
I was scared.
Why?
Because I had to pretend like it was nothing.
Also,
I was scared because I had to continue living like this.
I...
always waited for this moment.
I wanted to see you face to face...
when I die.
No.
I can't end it like this.
I won't.
I'll help you.
Everything...
has its ending.
Let's...
go to them...
and ask for forgiveness.
No.
I don't want to.
Young Gwang.
Yes.
I don't want to.
I'll be here with you.
Don't be scared.
Come on.
Gosh!
Goodness.
Goo Hyung.
Please go and get help.
I'll try to stop them.
Darn it!
I'll be right back.
Stop it.
Gyeo Wool. You're going to hurt yourself.
Gosh, she's fast. What is it?
- Gosh!
- My goodness.
- Goo Hyung.
- How did you find us here?
Let's get you to a hospital first.
No, San is here.
Goo Hyung. What happened? Who did this to you?
- What happened?
- Our backup forces are coming.
We have to get you to a hospital now.
No. I have to save San.
- Goo Hyung.
- I have to save San.
I'm sorry.
Yu Jin!
No, Yu Jin.
Take care.
No!
No matter what happens,
we should trust and protect each other, okay?
Wear it at all times.
Thank you.
The ocean is beautiful.
And the sunlight feels warm.
Yes.
The sunlight feels really warm.
Hey.
Wake up.
Please.
He...
He came to me.
What did you say?
The evil blood.
Evil blood?
Evil blood.
- San.
- Where is he?
San.
San!
(After a year)
I'm looking for this person.
(Missing person, Yoon San)
Have you ever seen him before?
Hello. I'm looking for a person.
If you see anyone similar, please call. Thank you.
It's been reported that you are giving out flyers illegally here.
My goodness.
Did somebody really report us?
Yes. There is this crazy lady who calls me three times a day.
Do we have to pay a fine?
There are too many bad people these days.
Who would report this?
Don't worry, Se Ra.
I'll catch all the bad guys.
Goo Hyung.
Can't you just go somewhere else and do it?
Why does it have to be here?
Also, you're a private detective. Finding a person is your job.
Do you think this makes sense?
Someone witnessed San here.
That's why he keeps telling us to come here.
Goo Hyung isn't stupid. Does he look stupid to you?
Give me some tteokbokki.
Did your tattoo shop go out of business?
What are you doing here?
I'm getting some pocket money from this.
What about you? Did you find that woman?
No. Yo Na? Joo Young Gwang?
There are no such people.
You must have been dreaming.
Also, who says they saw San here?
We haven't seen him for a year. He must be abroad.
Are you sure you're a private detective?
Is that why you switched it to a private investigation agency?
Don't you know what loyalty is?
I'll be a private detective again when San returns.
Anyway, how can you eat chocolate in between tteokbokki?
Give it to me.
This is sweet, right?
If you eat something sweet, you crave something salty.
Same goes for the other way around. That's the truth about food.
Look. Se Ra agrees with me.
Let me see your teeth.
Your upper teeth are black and your lower ones are red.
- Are they?
- You're disgusting.
Why don't us disgusting men...
start a new business?
If you and I partner up,
we'd be like this chocolate and tteokbokki.
We'll be the perfect team.
I'm telling you.
You have no sense of loyalty.
I'm not lying.
I'm saying you have no sense of loyalty.
I'll quit my job.
This probably doesn't hurt because it's paper.
I can't understand you even if I try.
Hello?
Yes, this is Yong's Private Investigation Agency.
Long time no see, Goo Hyung.
Gyeo Wool?
Did you really change it into a private investigation agency?
Where have you been all this time? You punk!
I heard you got kicked out from your uncle's place.
Poor you.
Anyway, where are you? Where are you right now?
I told you I'd be back when I find San.
Did you find him?
Where are you?
Do something about that chocolate and tteokbokki first.
It's making me want to throw up.
You...
Detective Yong. Let me make an official request.
Do you want to come with me to get San?
- Where were you all this time?
- Ouch!
Where on earth have you been? Where?
- Well, I'm back.
- You punk!
- Let's go.
- Go where?
Where do you think? To get San.
Did you really find him?
Do you think I'm lying?
- I know you lie all the time.
- Gosh.
Let's go. I didn't know San would be there.
- Did you really find him?
- Yes.
- I'll kill you if it's a lie.
- All right.
[Missing Person]
[Thank you for watching Vampire Detective.]
[Vampire Detective]