What is this?
The kidnapper has a fan club.
This is the fan club's symbol.
It's a "W" for Wanted.
Orson Welles.
This is the ID that Lee Ji Eun gave us
when she gave us Ha Dong Min's mission.
That is Doctor Ha Dong Min's lawyer.
It's a copycat.
I got the IP.
Is anyone in there?
Police. Put your hands up.
Something is off.
They were caught too easily.
Why isn't she picking up?
She should be back by now.
Please let me live!
Save me.
That is one of ours.
Can we have information on your members?
Park Bo Yeon... where is she?
You just show up like this and
start asking me this nonsense.
You live in Seoul.
Where did you get so much dirt
on your shoes on the way to work?
Senior!
Please save me...
This is the seventh mission.
Get Lee Ji Eun to appear on Wanted.
[EPISODE 10]
Someone just jumped off the roof.
I heard someone committed
suicide by jumping off the roof.
Is the person connected to our show?
I'll look into it.
Wait.
We don't have much time.
I received the mission.
When? Why are you telling us now?
It hasn't been long.
I was going to call you on my way
to see Lee Ji Eun.
That streamer?
We better look into this first.
We released the wrong preview because
of the copycat and have no time now.
Right now, Lee Ji Eun is with
Detective Oh Mi Ock.
- I'll head over there...
- Don't go alone.
Things are dangerous right now,
so don't go alone.
Writer Yeon and I will
get ready for the show.
- Joon Gu, you go with her.
- Okay.
What about the dead...
I think it's connected to our show.
I'll look into it and call you.
Let's go, Hye In.
How did you know to come here?
I heard that it was
Lee Ji Eun's mother who died.
I'm in charge of Lee Ji Eun's case.
It was suicide.
I did not raise my child properly
and caused this to happen.
In order to apologize to the world,
I will give up my life.
I want to do something to help,
but I can't do anything.
Watching all of this unfold
is so miserable for me.
Jung Hye In, I am truly sorry.
I hope Song Hyun Woo returns home safely
and will pray for it from the afterlife.
Have you ever seen
your daughter's boyfriend?
No! She seems very excited lately.
Her boyfriend has connections
to a broadcast station.
He promised to get her a debut.
She met that punk somewhere
and has been on a high lately.
A girl like that has been missing for
three days and you didn't report it?
What about CCTV?
They were inspecting the security system.
It hasn't been on since yesterday.
How could the system not be working
in this station of all places?
Two people were murdered here.
One member of the team nearly died.
I'm sure it was the culprit.
He could have hacked in
and broken the system.
I told you, didn't I?
The culprit is definitely
in the broadcast team.
It could have been
hacked from outside.
If you focus too much on that,
you could lose...
I'm looking into it,
so mind your own business.
All right, but I want to investigate
this suicide case.
This is connected to
the broadcast station too.
If you find anything, share it with me.
Why did he send a picture of Lee Ji Eun's
family with this mission?
Lee Ji Eun is very sensitive to any
topic related to her father.
Just like Na Soo Hyun is getting revenge
for his brother Na Jae Hyun.
Lee Ji Eun got involved in this
because of her father?
Then should we discuss
her father on the show?
You'll have to go a step
further than that.
The kidnapper is being shaken right now.
There are four more episodes to go.
Once Na Jae Hyun's remains were found...
the kidnapper wanted to find out why the
commissioner closed his brother's case.
The key to this case is to find out why
my late husband and Na Jae Hyun met.
That's right.
As we keep investigating this case,
that is where it will lead us.
Once we get to ten episodes,
that will be the final big picture.
However, the police commissioner
committed suicide.
Also, Bo Yeon was kidnapped
by copycat fans.
The show is in danger.
Then was he never planning
to put Lee Ji Eun on the show?
I think that is highly likely.
I think he is getting impatient.
He is changing his plans to
expose the important points.
If only I could find out
more about Lee Ji Eun...
This is our chance
to get ahead of the kidnapper.
You should meet with Lee Ji Eun.
We don't have to put
everything we find on the show.
Just getting her to appear
is completing the mission.
It's good to do something
the kidnapper isn't expecting.
How will we get Lee Ji Eun on the show
when she's in prison?
For this mission, they need the
accomplice on the show.
That's a bit difficult.
She's a detained criminal.
Isn't this a special case though?
The Wanted program is
a part of the investigation.
The police have agreed to
cooperate closely with the show.
The public already has many complaints.
We're looking forward to seeing
how you will lead the police.
My father has very high expectations.
The late commissioner had
his image and personal issues.
He showed us his inconsistencies.
Do you have articles
written about that streamer?
I think you need to write
them earlier than I thought.
We need to get people
interested in this mission.
Isn't it kind of odd if I write it?
What do you mean by that?
I'm going to write articles
as a close member of this team.
I don't even know
the results of this case.
If I write this in the midst of things...
people won't trust my book.
That's not what we agreed upon.
Don't get upset and listen.
What I'm saying is,
that story is already...
given as a special to another writer.
Can we get it viral before the show?
It's been up for two hours now.
It's on the main portal sites.
Everyone's talking about it.
Why bother asking that?
I heard ratings went up yesterday
to 39 percent in Bundang.
The person who committed suicide
was that streamer's mother?
She's Lee Ji Eun's only family.
She hasn't confirmed it herself,
but there was a suicide note.
There was an ID too.
Lieutenant Cha Seung In met her before,
so he confirmed it for us.
Are you sure it was suicide?
It looks that way.
About Lee Ji Eun's mother's suicide,
please don't tell Director Shin yet.
Today's mission is about Lee Ji Eun.
I think we need to decide whether
this should be in the show or not.
Sure.
What were you going
to say on the show today?
It's the seventh mission.
Get Lee Ji Eun to appear on Wanted.
He sent a picture of your family too.
I'm guessing he wants you
to talk about your family.
I don't know why you kidnapped Hyun Woo.
And I don't know why
you helped him kill people.
You have to talk to us
for all of this to end.
I can't go on the show.
Then tell me now.
Who is behind everything
and where is Hyun Woo?
Hyun Woo...
I'm sure Hyun Woo is safe.
Did the culprit tell you you'd
have to appear on the show?
Did he tell you the commissioner
would commit suicide?
That the crew would be taken
hostage and buried alive!
Now...
Ji Eun, you need to make a choice.
Shouldn't we tell Lee Ji Eun about this?
She may become emotional when she
hears her mother committed suicide.
She might tell us everything.
It might end up backfiring on us.
What do you mean?
I'm saying it might not be suicide.
If she figures that out,
Lee Ji Eun might become more reckless.
She will want revenge for her mother.
What do you mean it's not suicide?
Then who would it be... Na Soo Hyun?
It would be the person who
hired Jo Nam Chul as a hit man.
This person was able to get the late
commissioner to close Na Jae Hyun's case.
He covered up the death
of the son of the SG Group.
Why would this person
kill Lee Ji Eun's mother?
Because Lee Ji Eun is connected
to what happened seven years ago.
Lee Ji Eun's mother must
know something too.
Perhaps, she was trying
to get in touch with that person.
I should have thought of it earlier.
But, there was a suicide
and the reason makes sense.
Isn't your theory too far-fetched?
The suicide note isn't quite right.
What about it?
90 percent of unnatural
deaths are suicide.
Most of time, there is no suicide note.
Before committing suicide,
people are in a state of anxiety.
Even if they do write one,
it's hard to write one so logically.
Lee Ji Eun's case happened very suddenly.
She wouldn't have prepared
for the suicide in advance.
Lee Ji Eun's mother
didn't seem very educated.
I'll do my best to rush the autopsy.
Don't be too sure
about anything until then.
The only person who would know
anything is Ha Dong Min.
I'm going to meet Ha Dong Min.
Senior, Lee Ji Eun's in danger too.
- Be careful with her.
- Okay, I got it.
We have permission for now.
We're going to take her once
Hye In is finished talking.
Okay, call me.
Have they identified
who committed suicide?
No, I think they need
to look into it some more.
I see.
Sign this.
This is a first for us.
Two policemen will have
to be with her at all times.
Once the show ends at 11:00 p.m.,
the police will bring her back here.
Okay.
Wait here a moment.
He talked to his lawyer just an hour ago.
I made sure he went into his cell.
He was acting no different than usual.
Actually, he seemed like
he was in a good mood.
Can I take a look at the scene?
That could a bit difficult.
You should leave for now.
I believe in him.
Why?
Right now, the thing you and the police
couldn't do seven years ago...
he is doing it.
Seven years ago,
you lived your lives without a care.
Only now, you're all starting
to think about what happened.
That's why he is right.
So tell me about it.
What happened seven years ago?
What is it that you want?
Your show... I will go on it.
I will only say it in
front of all the viewers.
I don't trust you either, Jung Hye In.
I think you need to come with me.
What is it?
A delivery came for Park Bo Yeon.
There was something
strange written inside of it.
And the deliveryman?
Our security has him for now,
but he's creating a commotion.
What do we do about here?
Someone needs to stay here.
Yes, someone is coming.
- Watch the door.
- Let's go.
Excuse me.
Is this Park Bo Yeon's room?
Her doctor told me to check on her.
[SONG YOUNG SOO]
Ah...
You're going to stay here, right?
A suspicious person could come by,
so stay with her until the police come.
I was actually paged to go to room 301.
Okay. Don't worry.
Are you all right?
Don't be afraid.
I'm not here to hurt you.
I'm sorry.
Other people deserved it.
But, Bo Yeon...
that should not have happened to you.
You haven't done anything wrong.
Because of what happened to you,
you will continue to struggle with it.
I know that and I'm very sorry.
But, I don't have much time.
I have one last thing to do.
I am very sorry, but...
I need to ask you a favor.
This note...
Please deliver it to
Lieutenant Cha Seung In.
What... is it?
That's all you need to do.
I thought he was drunk.
He was drunk.
That's why he was acting like that.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Are you really going to go on this show?
Haven't you considered the fact that
you're being used by the culprit?
Everyone who appeared on this show died
or had bad things happen to them.
Look at me.
Just tell us who it is.
If you tell us everything,
you won't be an accomplice.
We'll say that you were kidnapped by
Park Sae Yong and had no choice.
Could you step outside for a moment?
Don't you know she has to be escorted
by two policemen at all times?
That's why there are two of them outside.
You can go out there
and keep watch if you want.
Why should I have to do that?
Didn't the police give permission
for her to appear on the show?
Let her rest for a bit.
She's just a young girl.
Let's leave for a bit.
She not going to talk.
You two stay put here.
We'll check on you later.
I will.
Detective Park.
What? You're on the
broadcast team, aren't you?
You don't have any business with me.
That's not true!
You're one of the main characters.
Remember what you said before?
You said would help your investigation
if I gave you inside information.
I wonder if this will help.
It's an audio file of a conversation
with Director Shin Dong Wook.
There's one of him talking
with Writer Yeon too.
Why are you giving me this?
Honestly, Director Shin is someone
that's a concern for you.
I know you consider him a suspect.
And?
He is suspicious.
A kidnapper that's demanding a show
that looks impossible to do.
Then there's the director past his prime
who is looking for his comeback.
He is strangely focused on the show,
to the point that it seems cruel.
He doesn't come off like someone
desperate to find a child.
So, what?
I wanted to confirm my theory.
You think Shin Dong Wook is the culprit?
People become more honest in front of
people they think are similar to them.
Give it a listen and think about it.
What do you get out of this?
Behind-the-scenes!
When the book is released,
would an observer's story be very fun?
Or would the story from the man on
the front lines be more exciting?
If people aren't on my side...
they won't trust the stories
coming from my point of view.
I heard you visited Bo Yeon.
You said you wouldn't go with us.
Bo Yeon was happy.
Going in a big group isn't my style.
I just wanted to see her face.
Why are you doing this show, Director?
Are you thinking of a comeback
after making it a big hit?
No.
I think this show could end my career.
Then why are going so far with it?
Should I be honest?
A chance to make a show like this won't
come again in my lifetime.
I'd bet no one else in
the world will get this chance.
Chance?
The kidnapper has his plans and
I just need to carry that out faithfully.
I have to make it good and entertaining,
so that many people want to watch.
Whether the people watching go crazy
over it, criticize it, or copy it...
that is their problem.
What do you get out of this?
To see how a show can provoke
and stir people up.
To see how people make this show.
I want to see for myself,
how it all ends.
Call me again. Okay.
I've been curious about something.
Can I ask you about it?
Yes, go ahead.
A long time ago, you used to make
documentaries on corrupt companies.
You got sued often for defamation.
I got my house seized.
The writers had their
personal emails inspected.
I went to court often too.
I recall seeing some of them.
Yet, you continued to make
documentaries on those issues.
That was my job.
Not just anyone has a job like that.
Why did you keep doing them?
I had a very pure heart back then.
I thought broadcasting was
for doing work like that.
You had to inform people about things.
Something like...
I had to change the world.
What about now?
What? Now...
I don't know.
I thought that I had a part to play here.
I couldn't put a stop to anything bad.
I just don't know.
Is Han Sol doing well?
He'll probably need some more time.
Still, he is eating well
and sleeping these days.
He talks about you often and
says he misses you.
I brought the files you mentioned.
Though, I'm not sure
if it's the right thing.
These are his personal files
from his work, right?
Yes, he didn't bring these home.
So, he was an assistant professor of
veterinary science seven years ago?
Yes.
Eight years ago, we met on a blind date
and planned to marry within two months.
He was an assistant professor then.
He was so busy then.
We fought a lot.
You don't know why he was so busy?
Well, I... I wouldn't really understand
it even if he explained his work to me.
Back then...
I think he was researching something
an external company requested.
He was assigned as
the research team leader.
That's all I remember.
Even after we married,
he was so busy for about a year.
Senior.
One moment.
[2008 MAY RESEARCH COSTS]
So...
Does Han Sol's father's death have
anything to do with something back then?
We're looking into many
different possibilities.
Could we take these and look at them?
Of course.
Don't be good to me.
I hated you a lot, at first.
No, I still hate you.
You could say one word.
If you would just tell us who...
I could find Hyun Woo right now.
But, now...
I can't help but think
you're a victim too.
I'm doing this because I want to.
Don't act like you know me.
I don't understand what it
means that you want to do this.
What kind of person are you?
What was your life like?
I started acting when I was seven.
I had to recognize what
people wanted when I was seven.
I learned how to do what they wanted.
I was always around adults.
Why are you saying all this to me?
I never thought about
what it was that I really wanted.
About how I want to live...
I have never thought about it.
When my husband died,
I ran off to another country.
When I announced my retirement on the
day that Hyun Woo was kidnapped...
I did everything to protect Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo is the most
precious thing to me.
More precious than my life.
Hyun Woo is more important.
Did you have something you wanted
to protect like that too?
Chief, we just entered
Lee Ji Eun's house.
I think it's been empty for a few days.
I'll call you if I find anything.
Yes.
You can't always
enter without permission.
It may not seem that way,
but there is a criteria.
Oh.
What should I be looking for?
Look for anything belonging
to Lee Ji Eun's father.
Also, traces that anyone
entered by force.
Look for blood too.
Look for signs that Lee Ji Eun's
mother was attacked.
All right.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[SG GROUP]
- Young Gwan!
- Yes.
Take the files from Han Sol's
father and these too.
Go to the police station
and look them over.
What about you?
I have somewhere to go.
My dad...
I once told him that
I wished he would die.
Ji Eun, are you okay?
You could've been in trouble.
Who are you?
I'm your dad's friend from work.
I saw you a few times
when you were young.
I guess you don't remember.
Hello.
Why are you out so late?
That guy was really following you.
I was on my way to see your dad.
You could've been in trouble.
Thank you.
Your dad is home, right?
Gosh, that looks heavy.
- You must study hard.
- It's okay.
No, it's okay. I'll carry it.
Come on, let's go.
Dad! Your friend is here...
You... you punk!
How dare you show up here.
Why... why would you be with my daughter?
You little punk!
Dad, Dad!
You're very drunk.
Dad.
Has your dad like this lately?
No, the thing is...
I guess today won't do.
I'll come back another time.
Don't walk around late at night.
It's dangerous.
With a dad like this,
how can he protect his daughter?
Be careful.
See you next time, Ji Eun.
Let's go inside.
Who told you to go around with
people you don't even know?
He said he was your friend.
He said he saw me when I was younger.
Get inside now!
If you ever do that again,
I won't let you out of the house.
How long are you going to keep this up?
I wish you would just die.
Then Mom would come back.
That was the last time I saw him alive.
The next day...
I'm home.
Dad!
My mom didn't come to my dad's funeral.
I had been living alone for two months
when my mom showed up.
I haven't spoken to my mom since.
So, it's not that you
want to protect something.
Your mom and dad couldn't protect you.
Are you this way because
you're angry about that?
No.
My dad did that in order to save me.
He had to die.
He thought that was
the way everything would end.
It wasn't my dad who couldn't protect me.
Jung Hye In, it was you
who couldn't protect Hyun Woo.
That day, you could have stopped
him from taking Hyun Woo.
I bet Hyun Woo was thinking that too.
"My mom couldn't protect me."
Hyun Woo!
Mom!
Hyun Woo, are you hurt at all?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Are you all right?
Is this because you were
talking to Lee Ji Eun?
No.
I'm okay.
I know.
I know it wasn't easy.
She's a smart girl.
She has you shaken up like this.
She opened up only
as much as she needed
then shut down the conversation.
Then what do I do now?
She will likely only say what
she needs to on the show tonight.
You said we need
to go further than that.
You know the body you saw
in front of the station today?
That is Ji Eun's mother.
She left a suicide note.
Are you sure it was suicide?
We'll have to wait a bit for the autopsy.
We're investigating.
Does Lee Ji Eun know?
No.
Why are you telling me this right now?
Not everyone on
the crew knows about it.
Detective Park told me that
Writer Yeon knows about it.
She asked him not to tell Director Shin.
I don't think she wants it on the show.
You can use it at
the right time, just once.
When Lee Ji Eun is not expecting it,
you can use it to shock her.
[LIEUTENANT CHA SEUNG IN]
Yes, Lieutenant Cha. I'll be right down.
I think I need to head downstairs.
I can't leave Lee Ji Eun alone.
I'll stay with her. You can go.
Okay.
Lee Ji Eun is with Jung Hye In.
Nothing else is going on. Okay.
You must be tired.
You know that woman who fell
off the broadcast station roof?
I hear she's a UCN employee.
I heard she criticized Wanted
and committed suicide.
Sort of like burning yourself to death,
like in protest.
Who told you that?
My friend.
He's a writer for Youngjin Daily.
He's publishing an article tomorrow.
He has a source at the police.
He even has a copy of the suicide note.
What nonsense. Is he crazy?
We haven't even officially confirmed the
body because Lee Ji Eun was in prison.
What does Lee Ji Eun being
in prison have to do with the body?
Is it Lee Ji Eun's mom?
No, it's not.
Don't be like that and just tell me.
I just met with Lieutenant Park and
gave him some really good information.
We're very close, you know.
You won't get in trouble
with him for telling me.
I'm not going to write an article.
It's just for my book.
I have to record everything that
happens on the scene daily.
You can't write this article yet.
I told you I won't.
You know we're going to have
an audience today, right?
Director Shin.
I need to see you for a second.
Are you lucky or what, Director Shin?
The whole world is helping Wanted.
What is it now?
The woman who fell from the roof today.
[SUICIDE NOTE]
She was Lee Ji Eun's mother.
How could it be that on the day she's on
the show that her mother commits suicide?
And Lee Ji Eun doesn't know about it.
Looks like you'll get
a great dramatic moment again.
Hye In.
Did Hye In go somewhere?
Give her a call.
She had some business to take care of.
I see.
It will be hectic on the show.
It would be better if you could tell her
or Jung Hye In something beforehand.
You don't have to say anything on
the show if you don't want to.
Like anything about your past
or your personal life.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
What are you doing?
Wait, wait.
Why are you going around doing this?
I thought Director Shin
had talked to all of you.
You took photos when Bo Yeon
was being rescued, right?
No, when did I do that?
Give me that phone.
- I don't want to.
- Don't want to?
Oh, do you know that person?
Gosh, seriously.
Ten seconds to air.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Everything on this show is real.
We are doing this show at the request of
the person who has kidnapped my son.
Jung Hye In's Wanted is starting now.
Put in this caption.
Bring in the audience members.
Hey, what the...
Audience is entering. Read the prompter.
Why are there audience members?
On other programs you've done,
if you had a guest like this
wouldn't you bring in an audience?
Bo Yeon got hurt because
we did it like this.
She nearly died!
If Bo Yeon should make us change,
we should've done it with Han Sol's dad.
We can't do things for personal reasons.
Jung Hye In, what are you doing?
Say your lines.
On today's Jung Hye In's Wanted,
we have 30 audience members with us.
Let's welcome the audience members.
Please come in.
Sit in the back first.
Wow, Shin Dong Wook is going too far.
He really is something.
Coconut TV, a streamer
is broadcasting a meal.
User ID Jieunjjang.
Lee Ji Eun, a woman in her early 20s,
was kidnapped by a masked man
during a live webcast.
That was three days before my son
Hyun Woo was kidnapped.
The kidnapper Park Sae Yong
had met Lee Ji Eun online
and they had been dating.
Three days later...
Park Sae Yong disguised himself
as a P.A. on my movie's set
and took my son.
On the day this show started...
Park Sae Yong was found hanging
by a noose in his own home.
The demands to make this show
and the second mission
were delivered to me by Lee Ji Eun
who was initially thought to be a victim.
Also, the target of the first mission,
Kim Han Sol's father.
Lee Ji Eun was found at
his murder scene and was arrested.
This is the seventh mission.
Get Lee Ji Eun to appear on Wanted.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Start with audience questions.
Today, we will start with questions
from the studio audience.
I was a fan ever since you were on
the Africa TV food broadcast.
I read an article that Park Sae Yong
was paying you to date him.
I heard that the Coconut TV program was
a bit racy so that you could earn money.
Was the kidnapping all
just a ploy for money too?
No, it was not.
Did you and Park Sae Yong kidnap
Hyun Woo together because of money?
No.
Lee Ji Eun is an accomplice.
When you provoke her like that,
you are provoking the culprit.
It's my show.
If you don't like it, then leave!
I don't care about standards or whatever.
A person almost died
because of your work.
Shouldn't you change things
for the sake of that one person?
You can leave with him if you want.
No, I can't leave.
This is my show too.
This time I will ask a question.
Lee Ji Eun.
Why did the culprit send a picture
of your family with the mission?
I will ask a different question.
Seven years ago...
there was a person who
claimed to be your father's friend.
I heard that he used you to
skillfully threaten your father.
Do you know the reason why?
I have a question for Jung Hye In.
You are with an accomplice
to your son's kidnapper.
How can you be so calm?
Are you trying to pardon this person
by showing us she has a sad past?
Did you make this entire thing up
to save your husband's station?
Is this whole thing fake?
Let's follow the order
of the program and...
Jung Hye In, don't
take any more questions.
We'll go to commercials.
Let's get this under control.
Camera three, it's not time
for commercials yet.
Jung Hye In, you have
to get through this.
This is how the viewers
really feel about you.
See if you can change
these people's hearts.
I live in this area.
Today, I saw a woman commit suicide
by jumping off the UCN building.
What? Suicide?
It's 6,400 won.
Someone seemed to have
committed suicide over there.
Did you see it?
That woman? Yes, I saw it.
Why? In the daytime...
Did you get a picture or video,
by any chance?
Why would I do that? So scary.
I just needed it for something.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Excuse me!
I have a picture on my phone.
What's going on?
What is this?
What's wrong? Is it a blackout?
- Look into it now!
- Okay.
Damn!
I apologize to all our viewers.
Where did Lee Ji Eun go?
Where did she go?
What's going on here?
Was she kidnapped?
Captain, there was a blackout
and Lee Ji Eun disappeared.
Chief, are you watching the show?
The police are keeping the UCN building
contained and investigating.
Once again, I want to apologize
to all the viewers.
There was a brief blackout in
the studio for unknown reasons.
Our show could not air during that time.
And my son...
The accomplice to his kidnapping...
The seventh mission target, Lee Ji Eun,
has disappeared during that blackout.
Jung Hye In, calm down.
Listen to me.
There is still time left in our show.
You have to take questions
from the audience by yourself.
You have to finish the show.
The seventh mission is complete with
the appearance of Lee Ji Eun on our show.
For the remaining time,
I will take questions from the audience.
Go on, please.
As of yesterday...
you were looking for a connection between
several people from seven years ago.
Have you discovered what happened
seven years ago yet?
Good job.
- No one can leave yet.
- Let me go!
You were with Lee Ji Eun the longest
and you were there for the blackout.
The only person who knows who
has Hyun Woo has disappeared.
Let go of me!
Let her go.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever