This is the seventh mission.
Get Lee Ji Eun to appear on Wanted.
Someone just jumped
off the station's roof.
Is the person connected to our show?
We don't have much time.
I received the mission.
Get Lee Ji Eun to appear on Wanted.
They want you to talk about your family.
I can't go on the show.
It's time to make your choice.
I heard the person who died is
Lee Ji Eun's mom.
It might not be suicide.
If Lee Ji Eun figures that out,
she might act up even more.
The only person who might know
about this is Ha Dong Min.
I'm not here to hurt you.
Please deliver this message
to Lieutenant Cha Seung In.
Bring in the audience members.
On today's Jung Hye In's Wanted,
we have 30 audience members with us.
This is the seventh mission.
Get Lee Ji Eun to appear on Wanted.
I live in this area.
Today, I saw a woman commit suicide
by jumping off the UCN building.
- What is that?
- What's going on?
Why is this happening?
Captain, there was a blackout
and Lee Ji Eun disappeared.
The police are keeping the UCN building
contained and are investigating.
The accomplice to my son's kidnapping...
and the seventh mission's
target, Lee Ji Eun
has disappeared during that blackout.
[EPISODE 11]
- No one can leave yet.
- Let me go!
You were with Lee Ji Eun the longest
and you were there for the blackout.
The only person who knows who
has Hyun Woo has disappeared.
Let go of me!
Let her go.
Ha Dong Min is dead?
He hanged himself in his cell.
[BEFORE JUNG HYE IN'S WANTED EPISODE 7]
Why would both Lee Ji Eun's mother
and Ha Dong Min kill themselves?
It wasn't suicide.
I think someone disguised it
to look like suicide.
Is it about what the kidnapper
is trying to expose?
About what happened seven years ago.
Yes, I think so.
If Jo Nam Chul was telling
Director Shin Dong Wook the truth...
I didn't kill Im Hyung Soon and
that detective on my own.
I was hired to do it.
Why didn't you tell anyone
seven years ago?
Do you know what kind of people they are?
Even the prosecutor ignored me
and covered it up.
Then you people made all this noise
and now they're trying to kill me.
Whether I get caught by the police
or run, they'll kill me either way.
The accident yesterday was
caused by them too.
A person that can contract out murders
and has the power
to manipulate prosecutors.
Also, a person with
the ability to hire someone
to kill a man in
a private cell in a prison.
Who do you suppose that is?
Is it by chance...
Han Sol's father was working on research
for a large company seven years ago.
So, he was an assistant professor of
veterinary science seven years ago?
Back then...
I think he was researching something
an external company requested.
He was designated as
the research team leader.
That's all I remember.
Senior.
I believe that external company
was the SG Group.
The funds were deposited into
the professor's personal account.
The amount was very large.
I don't think it was official research.
Lee Ji Eun's father worked at SG Group
from 2006 to 2009.
We haven't been able to confirm
which department yet or the position.
All of the targets or accomplices
are somehow related to SG Group.
Then the people who ordered the hit on
Na Jae Hyun and my husband...
are you saying it could be SG Group?
How could that be? He was family.
My late husband would often say
his family was so inhumane.
It broke his heart.
Still, they want to maintain
their power and strength.
They are very protective of their family.
We will look into it.
Is SG Group at the center of it all?
Or is there someone else behind it
who is connected to everything?
Now there's only one person left who
knows what happened seven years ago.
Lee Ji Eun is the only one left.
That's why the kidnapper...
Then was it never in his plans
to put Lee Ji Eun on the show?
I think that is highly likely.
I think he is getting impatient.
He is changing his plans in order
to expose the important points.
If only I could find out more
about Lee Ji Eun...
This is our chance to get
ahead of the kidnapper.
If Lee Ji Eun talks about SG Group today
that will be following
the culprit's plan
but Hyun Woo will be in danger.
The kidnapper will want to finish
the remaining three episodes.
But, SG will want to disrupt this show.
I don't know what
the kidnapper is planning.
However, if she doesn't talk
about SG and returns to prison...
Lee Ji Eun may end up
murdered like Ha Dong Min.
Help me, Lieutenant.
We need to hide Lee Ji Eun.
Jung Hye In just entered
Lieutenant Cha Seung In's home.
The Lieutenant's home?
Things should be going crazy
because of Lee Ji Eun.
Check to see if Lee Ji Eun is there.
Don't harm Jung Hye In or the lieutenant.
Just check for now.
Why did you bring me here?
To tell you the truth...
your mother didn't commit suicide.
- Who is it?
- This is security.
Sorry to come so late.
Hello, what is this about?
Well, he's saying
there's a leak downstairs.
He insisted he needs to check now.
The grandmother downstairs said that?
She didn't mention that to me.
Oh, he says he's her grandson.
It will me take just a moment.
I just want to see if I need to call
a repairman tomorrow.
Go ahead.
Do you know where the leak is?
Can I check the bathroom?
It might not be a good idea now...
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
There was a leak downstairs.
Can you please leave?
Yes.
I guess it might not be the bathroom.
I will check tomorrow.
Yes, I will check too.
Why don't we leave now?
I'm sorry.
It's all right. I'll call you tomorrow.
Okay. Let's go now.
Let's get out of here.
We need to move to a safer location.
There's a place we can go to.
I go there before I start a new project,
or when I need to rest.
Both my manager and my husband
don't know about it.
There's nothing in Jung Hye In's bag.
She figured out that we were
following her and tricked us.
Okay, just wait for now.
Yes?
Jung Hye In is here. What should I do?
Tell her to come in.
What brings you by
so late without even a call?
I'm sorry.
I had something urgent
to discuss with you.
Please sit.
Did you see the show?
Lee Ji Eun disappeared.
- Have you found her?
- No.
But, I think I found a lead.
What do you mean?
Someone has been tailing me
since I left the station.
They followed me all the way here.
Who and why would they do such a thing?
It must be the people
who are after Lee Ji Eun.
They mistakenly think that I have her.
It could be the kidnapper.
Or they could be the people the kidnapper
is trying to expose from seven years ago.
So, how is this a lead for you?
I've told the police
that they are following me.
They are coming up with
a plan to catch them.
If it is the kidnapper,
we will be able to identify him better.
If they're the ones trying
to cover up the truth...
then we will learn more about
the kidnapper's motives.
I have heard that SG Group
has a better intelligence unit
than the government.
I was hoping you could
look into it for me.
Yes, of course.
There are people tailing Jung Hye In.
I would like you to look into
who they are right away.
I understand what you are saying.
I apologize. We will withdraw for today.
Look at the email that
Professor Kim Woo Jin saved.
It was sent to Lee Yong Hwan.
That's Lee Ji Eun's father,
who worked at SG Group.
It wasn't an SG email account.
It was a personal account.
Yes.
His research funds were also
deposited into a personal account.
Professor Kim Woo Jin was
doing research for SG
that the public couldn't know about.
The person in charge of
that project was Lee Yong Hwan.
After that, Lee Yong Hwan suffered
depression and alcoholism.
He ended up committing suicide.
Professor Kim Woo Jin was targeted
by Hyun Woo's kidnapper...
But, I don't think it was only
because he was abusing his son.
Yes, it was because of the incident
related to Na Jae Hyun seven years ago.
Then, what about Ha Dong Min?
It's not the illegal human testing.
He has a connection
to what happened then.
By the way, have you seen Lieutenant Cha?
Have you heard from him?
You haven't spoken to him?
Cha Seung In, where are you?
I was about to call you.
I'm going to send you an address,
so meet me there.
Don't tell Young Gwan.
I'll explain it in person.
You said my mom didn't commit suicide.
Are you certain?
I won't be sure until
the autopsy report comes back.
Who killed her?
Was it them?
SG?
There were police stationed
everywhere in the station.
How could you let Lee Ji Eun get away?
That's what I wanted to ask you.
Where is the emergency generator?
Also, who knows how to use it?
And who destroyed it in advance?
Who would be able to take Lee Ji Eun
during the blackout and duck the police?
Who would that be?
It has to be this team.
At the very least,
it has to be someone within UCN.
We heard it all already,
but let's go over it again.
Writer Yeon, it was confirmed that
you were in the studio.
Director Shin, the engineer confirmed
that you were in the booth.
Executive Director Choi?
Where were you?
I told you I was in the hallway.
No one can confirm that though.
I was on the phone with Bo Yeon.
I showed you the time stamp earlier.
Even if one of you did it,
I'm sure you planned ahead of time.
There is probably an accomplice
that helped.
Na Soo Hyun could have been here.
Then it is the job of the police
to figure out how
the accomplice got inside.
- What?
- Or...
You should have caught
Na Soo Hyun by now.
You shouldn't sit around suspecting us
and repeating the same thing
over and over.
It might not be the kidnapper
that took Lee Ji Eun.
He wanted Lee Ji Eun on the show
and for her to reveal something.
It may have been someone
who feared that happening.
One of the people trying to cover up
what happened seven years ago?
It's good and all to theorize.
We'll have to confirm
your movements for today.
Please cooperate if you
want to go back to work.
Director Shin, come with me.
Executive Director Choi, go with
Detective Yoo.
Writer Yeon, please wait a moment.
We need to retrace
your movements for the day.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
You were awake?
I thought maybe you were sleeping,
so I wasn't going to call.
How are you feeling?
Are you in pain?
Should I go there?
No, I'm a lot better now.
My mom is here
and I'm getting discharged.
Already?
You should rest your body.
If you're doing this because of the show,
you really don't have to.
You don't have to come back and
put yourself through this, Bo Yeon.
I... want to quit.
I can't do it anymore.
All right, then.
You should quit if you can't do it.
It's not like I don't
understand how you feel.
Someone has died so
how can all of you be like this?
Whatever the reason is,
if something big has happened
you have to see it through to the end.
That's what it means
to take responsibility.
No matter what the result is.
[THAT NEVER HAPPENED.]
[THE POLICE COMMISSIONER DIDN'T STOP IT.]
[A MAN NAMED CHOI PIL KYU GAVE ME
MONEY TO START MY OWN BUSINESS.]
[- KO HYUNG JOON]
No, I'm going to keep working.
I'll rest for today
and come in tomorrow morning.
What made you feel this way?
Just like you said before,
I started this job without a clue.
No one wanted to hire me with
my experience and resume.
And now? Has something changed?
You're right that something's
wrong with our show.
I want to find out why the kidnapper
is going so far as he is.
Also, I want to take responsibility until
the very end.
If I can even make things
better by one percent...
I'm going keep doing it.
There are only three episodes left.
Even if we follow our plan,
it may or may not work out.
If we use this mission
on finding Ji Eun...
No, just listen to me.
Ji Eun and I put our lives on the line
when we started this thing.
We were prepared for this to happen.
We have nothing more to lose.
No.
If this is how we were going to do it,
we never should have started it!
I...
killed a man.
I trusted in your plan.
My brother and my younger sister.
And how they died.
I wanted everyone to know about it.
I believed that they would
pay for what they did!
I'm going to follow our original plan.
Save Ji Eun some other way.
Lawyer Choi, are you okay?
I called a designated driver.
You just need to get in the car.
Why can't you get the timing right?
What's with you kids?
Are you the designated driver?
Hurry up!
Gangnam-gu, Cheongdamdong 278-1.
- Okay.
- Drive him home carefully.
Call us once you drop him off.
Good job.
What is this? Who are you?
Na Soo Hyun?
You're the one who killed Jo Nam Chul.
What is all of this? Untie me.
Untie me right now!
Be quiet!
Stop the car, you punk! Stop the car!
Stay put.
I'm not going to kill you.
Stop the car, you punk!
What's going on?
Lee Ji Eun is here.
My mom ended up dying because of me.
Just like my dad.
It's not too late now.
Tell me where Hyun Woo is.
Tell me who is behind
it all and this will end.
If it ends like this,
this will have all been for nothing.
Don't try to get information out of me.
I'm not trying to use you.
I'm trying to protect you.
[LOOK FOR YOUR EIGHTH MISSION HERE.]
[BELOW SOUTH WONHYO BRIDGE, 14-2318]
Will the kidnapper try
to protect you too?
The best way for him to get you back...
it would be to give me
a mission to bring you back.
I don't know what the mission is yet.
I'll go and see what it is.
You can make your decision then.
I don't know what his goal is.
Don't think that it's more
important than your own life.
It's South Wonhyo Bridge.
The mission is inside the car.
Meet me there now.
[MAKE THIS MAN PAY FOR HIS CRIME
HE COMMITTED SEVEN YEARS AGO.]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Who is this?
He's alive.
This is South Wonhyo Bridge.
Someone was been kidnapped
and he's lost consciousness.
Hey, hey! Are you okay?
Hey!
This person, Choi Pil Kyu.
He got a scholarship from SG Group.
Then he finished training.
He's been representing SG since
he started at the law firm Ohsung.
It won't be easy to look into
his background in one day.
There's no other way, but we need
to get him to confess like Ha Dong Min.
Security and his law firm, Ohsung,
are all there at the hospital.
Lieutenant Park and Detective Yoo
are there too.
I told you we shouldn't
have taken him to the hospital.
The kidnapper took Choi Pil Kyu and
put him there without killing him.
It meant we should have kept him
there restrained.
Whatever the kidnapper wanted
we can't take part in
forceful confinement.
Let's think about it.
There must be a way.
Hye In.
Is something wrong?
I haven't received proof
that Hyun Woo is alive yet.
I hadn't even thought of that yet.
We're only doing this
show because of Hyun Woo.
Lawyer Choi Pil Kyu only worked on
SG Group while at Ohsung.
Two years before Jo Nam Chul was paroled,
he represented him, as well.
Choi Pil Kyu seems to have visited often.
He's a lawyer. He's very famous.
He works for the law firm, Ohsung.
I guess they represent violent
criminals sometimes too.
The law firm, Ohsung.
Jo Nam Chul couldn't possibly
have that much money.
I think it must've been a girlfriend or
friend who got him the lawyer.
Jo Nam Chul was intent on getting parole.
He was on almost
perfect behavior for two years.
I don't know what caused that change.
Jo Nam Chul claimed that Im Hyung Soon,
Na Jae Hyun, and Senior Sang Shik...
were all killed because
he was hired to kill them.
Senior Sang Shik was looking into
Na Jae Hyun's disappearance.
That's when Jo Nam Chul killed him.
Why do you think Detective Kim Sang Shik
was looking into my brother's case?
And what do you think he found
that caused him to die at
the hands of Jo Nam Chul?
Find out and expose it before
it's too late, Lieutenant.
The day after Jo Nam Chul was paroled
he told his girlfriend that
he would be going to do a job.
[I AM FINALLY GETTING OUT TOMORROW.
I GOT MYSELF A JOB FOR TOMORROW TOO.]
Where is Jo Nam Chul?
- Are you in touch with him?
- No.
He doesn't have a cell phone.
He said he'd buy one and call me.
I can't reach him.
Where did he say he'd be going?
He said he was going to work.
Then he went out to get some
potassium chloride.
He killed Im Hyung Soon.
Lawyer Cho Pil Kyu could
have promised Jo Nam Chul parole
in exchange for a murder.
About Im Hyung Soon who
Jo Nam Chul killed...
He called me telling me
he had a tip for me.
I had stopped working on the case.
That detective Kim Sang Shik
was asking a lot of questions.
All I did is tell him where
he could meet Im Hyung Soon.
Im Hyung Soon called in a tip to the
detective who was on Na Jae Hyun's case.
Jo Nam Chul was waiting at the place
where Im Hyung Soon was supposed to be.
Then seven years ago,
Im Hyung Soon and Jo Nam Chul...
I think there's a chance
they were working together
when they killed Na Jae Hyun.
When Im Hyung Soon called in a fake tip
to turn in Jo Nam Chul to the police
it was Sang Shik who ended up dying.
Im Hyung Soon ran to
the Philippines out of fear.
Since he came to Korea after seven years,
he must have had a reason.
He must have run out of money.
He probably reached out to SG.
If SG got threatened,
they'd try to get rid of Im Hyung Soon.
Hey, you need to
approach this very carefully.
You don't have any irrefutable
evidence or witnesses.
If you go at this the wrong way,
you'll be in a lot of danger.
Come on in.
What brings you by?
I'd like to speak to
Lieutenant Cha Seung In.
Are you feeling better?
It must still be very hard for you.
I'm okay.
Actually...
What is this?
Last night, Na Soo Hyun
snuck into my hospital room.
He asked me to give this to you.
[THAT NEVER HAPPENED.]
[THE POLICE COMMISSIONER DIDN'T STOP IT.]
[A MAN NAMED CHOI PIL KYU GAVE
ME MONEY TO START MY OWN BUSINESS.]
Write it yourself.
Who made you stop investigating
my brother's case?
Who made you quit being a detective?
Write it down.
I heard that Choi Pil Kyu
is the target of this mission.
Let's assume Choi Pil Kyu
can't appear on today's show.
We can find evidence that
will get him legally punished.
That's not enough.
The mission was to get him punished.
He needs to get arrested
or atone for it.
We need those results today.
That's difficult unless
he's caught in the act of a crime.
And it's something that
happened seven years ago.
I'm certain he's connected to the people
that have appeared so far.
Hello.
How can I help you?
I'm President Ham Tae Suk of SG Life.
What brings you by?
I'm a bit late saying hello.
I ended up acquiring UCN
because of this show.
You are all working so hard
to look for our Hyun Woo.
I had some things to prepare,
so I could not come right away.
What do you mean by prepare?
I have been watching the show.
I know you feel you had no choice
because of the kidnapper.
But, I feel the show has many issues.
Are you saying you plan on controlling
the content of the show?
What do I know,
that I would do such a thing?
If a problem arises,
I will help you to resolve it.
I am Kim Sang Woo from
the law firm Ohsung.
Our team will be handling legal issues
for UCN and the Wanted show.
If you get any lawsuits
or any other legal issues
these people here
will take care of it for you.
We will take care of ourselves.
If there is something to take
responsibility for, we will.
How?
UCN will have to start getting used to
SG's way of doing things.
We will do our very best.
We hope you will do your best, as well.
Honestly, it can be a burden if
the risk is too high for us.
We are getting ready for lawsuits
from some organizations already.
Also, isn't the broadcast team
on the list of suspects?
There are issues with President Song too.
We are short on time just
getting ready for the show.
Keep the meeting as short as possible
to give them time to get ready.
Yes, sir.
Should we go over what
the current situation is?
You can keep sleeping.
I won't go anywhere.
I have nowhere to go.
I really have nowhere now.
So, tell us.
Who is Hyun Woo's kidnapper?
I can't ruin that person's plan now.
Even if this person uses you
and throws you aside like this?
He's not like that.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
On today's Jung Hye In's Wanted,
we have 30 audience members with us.
Let's welcome the audience members.
Hyun Woo.
I told you not to watch that.
It's not a good thing to watch.
Your mom wouldn't like it either.
Can you let us talk alone?
I'll be right outside,
so call me when you're done.
After your father passed away
you said your mom came two months later.
How did you survive on your own?
Alone...
in that house.
My Hyun Woo...
I've never seen him with
that expression before.
It's been a week.
Park Sae Yong and you.
And Na Soo Hyun.
The people who've had him have switched
and the location has changed too.
And now again...
I told you not to watch that.
Who is that woman?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Hyun Woo hasn't done anything wrong.
To your father or Na Soo Hyun.
Hyun Woo's not responsible for any of it.
Whatever horrible thing
you've gone through...
Is it that you want Hyun Woo
to go through it too?
I really don't know this woman.
But, I was promised.
I was promised that Hyun Woo
would be kept safe.
This mission is about
Lawyer Choi Pil Kyu isn't it?
So, you knew?
Do you know the entire plan?
Just up to today.
I know that today is
a very important day.
Can you bring me some paper?
This is a storage locker my mom rented.
This is the unit number and pin number.
You'll find some of my dad's belongings
that he left for her before he died.
What are they?
Go and look for a tape.
You'll find some notes
that my dad left too.
You have to complete this mission
in order to keep Hyun Woo safe.
That's why I'm telling you this.
This is everything I can do for you.
Is the investigation over?
You must be tired.
Who are you?
Our president has an urgent matter
he'd like to discuss with you.
President?
Are you from SG?
Yes.
Yes, this is Song Jung Ho.
How did you know about this place?
Do you think there's anything
I don't know about you?
There's no need to do that.
Did someone contact you and tell you
that I have Lee Ji Eun?
You can do whatever you want.
But, do not cause trouble with SG.
President Song Jung Ho came by.
We'll need to move her.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Young Gwan, keep looking
into Ha Dong Min.
Look into the circumstances of
his suicide once more.
Senior! Where are you going again?
And where is Senior Mi Ock?
Where are you going now?
You're acting strange lately.
Are you meeting someone secretly?
I'm going to buy cigarettes.
I can't even get a girlfriend
with you guys around.
I'll tell you about it
once I figure everything out.
It's not a situation
I want to drag you into.
It can cause a lot of problems.
Still, Senior...
I will explain it to you eventually.
I'll call you regularly.
Look into Ha Dong Min and wait, okay?
Okay.
He's going to call SG.
Let's get out of here for now.
Lieutenant Cha is on his way here.
Wait.
I told you I won't run.
I know but I still have to do it.
It will make it harder for us
to move together.
You know it'll be more dangerous
for you to run, right?
Let's use the emergency exit stairs.
I'll go inside.
Wait near Jung Hye In's car.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Hey! I lost them.
Run!
Seung In, Zone C12.
Senior, get in!
Do you think Lieutenant Cha is okay?
He probably didn't tell anyone
in case Ji Eun got discovered.
There were two of them there.
Na Soo Hyun will try
to avoid getting caught too.
We did get out first.
He's probably called for back-up now.
Where are we going now?
There are a few places I know
that we use for witness protection.
I need to think about which place is
the least exposed and best hidden.
I have a place I want to visit first.
Where is that?
We should get to somewhere safe...
A place that might help us
complete today's mission.
I don't think hiding like
this will solve anything.
Na Soo Hyun...
Na Soo Hyun.
Lieutenant Cha.
I don't know.
You should go to Ji Eun.
I knew this would happen to me.
I did kill a person too.
A man here has been stabbed.
He's in critical condition.
Gangseo-gu, Banghwa-dong 960.
It's an underground parking lot. Hurry!
It was some people that SG Group sent.
I know.
Hold on a little longer.
The ambulance will be here soon.
I'm sorry.
Now...
it will all end soon.
Tell me, Na Soo Hyun.
Who is behind this?
Where is Hyun Woo?
I can't tell you.
Our Young Hyun.
She died such an unfair death.
Young Hyun?
Your little sister?
Not Na Jae Hyun?
A six year old baby...
When she smiled...
she was so pretty.
She just died.
I heard about it while I was in the army.
I thought the sky was falling.
It felt like she died because
I couldn't protect her.
Up until then...
I felt like I hadn't even
done anything for her.
And my brother?
My brother found the people
who did that to her.
My brother ended up dying.
The detective who tried to find
my brother ended up dying.
Na Soo Hyun.
Na Soo Hyun!
Na Soo Hyun, you punk!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
What do we have to do to get
Choi Pil Kyu on the show?
Who are you?
I need to talk to you, Bo Yeon.
Do you need to check something?
Where did you see that video?
The kidnapper will be rushed.
He'll think he has no time and
he might end up revealing himself.
You can no longer have
the mission's target on the show.
Does that increase our chances
of finding Hyun Woo?
So, the people Jo Nam Chul was
talking about are SG Group.
Will this show be okay?
We have to get Choi Pil Kyu
on this show somehow.