[EPISODE 12]
I'll go alone from here.
Will you be okay?
I don't have much time before we air.
I think we risk exposure if
the three of us stick together.
Call someone from your team
or Lieutenant Cha
and don't go anywhere alone.
Okay.
Let me know when you find a safe place.
I'm sorry.
I can't have any more complications.
If anything happens to me,
send this to a TV station or a newspaper.
I'm sorry to put this burden on you.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
It seems like they've determined
that Ha Dong Min committed suicide.
The autopsy report isn't out yet.
What about the CCTV inside the prison?
The precinct is being very uncooperative.
We're not in charge
of this investigation
so we have no jurisdiction.
Do you have any time?
I have some questions I want to ask.
I'm really busy right now.
Come down to see me.
You're a great teacher there.
I heard you didn't join the
investigation team and I wondered why.
Don't you know how to investigate
anything officially?
Did you look into it?
You didn't have to ask me.
It's been bothering me ever
since Park Sae Yong's death
so I looked into it.
Was it suicide?
They're trying to push the investigation
in that direction and close the case.
The medical examiner in charge told me
unofficially that it could be murder.
Is that for sure?
The spot where he was positioned
with the noose around his neck
is different than where
the strangulation is.
He has multiple strangulation
marks on his throat.
He has defensive wounds
on his hands and feet.
The crime scene photos show his pants
and shirt rolled up on one side.
It probably happened when was dragged
across the floor after being strangled.
When will there be official results?
We already have the results
but they're delaying
to look for evidence.
They're trying to prove it was suicide.
Who could be ordering
them to do such a thing?
I don't know.
But, be careful.
I heard Chief Jung is being
disciplined right now.
If something happens to you,
he won't be able to help you.
Anyway, thank you.
I'll call you again.
Don't call me.
I don't like hearing from you.
Senior, can't you just tell me?
Who killed Na Soo Hyun and
how did you know to go there?
I'm not trying to keep secrets from you.
This isn't because I don't trust you.
Then why won't you tell me?
I don't want to drag you into this.
You might end up having to quit,
and it's dangerous.
Then what is it that I can do?
Tell me that, at least.
We don't have much time.
The kidnapper doesn't know
that Na Soo Hyun is dead.
He'll worry if he doesn't hear from him
and that Lee Ji Eun is missing too.
That's true.
Let's find out who he is today.
Okay.
Na Soo Hyun didn't start all this
just because of his brother.
No, his brother Na Jae Hyun got involved
because of his sister Na Young Hyun.
Didn't you say that Na Young Hyun died
of an illness two years before all that?
Let's start from there.
Find out how she died
and look into her medical records.
Okay.
Yes, Jung Hye In.
Where are you?
I'm at the station now.
Lieutenant Oh is with Lee Ji Eun.
She said she'd find a place
and contact me.
What happened to Na Soo Hyun?
He was killed... by them.
I was too late.
I'm sorry.
Na Soo Hyun, Lee Ji Eun,
and Park Sae Yong.
Now none of the kidnapper's
accomplices can help him.
He will get desperate.
He will think he has no time and
his identity may be revealed.
We have to move fast.
I found a video tape that Lee Ji Eun's
father left before she died.
I'll take a look at it
and call you if I find anything.
I need to investigate something too.
I'll call you later.
I think you all comprehend
the situation now.
We have a mountain of issues
besides what I mentioned.
You should be prepared to deal
with it personally, as well.
Are we finished now?
Yes, it's only the first meeting.
We'll end it here for now.
By the way, what is today's mission?
Does it have to do with Choi Pil Kyu,
by any chance?
I heard that Jung Hye In found
him by a Han River bridge
and called in last night.
It will be difficult if you
continue to be so uncooperative.
Whatever the case,
I'll say one last thing.
You can no longer have your mission
targets appear on your show.
Didn't you say you're
here to resolve issues
not control the content?
The best way to solve
problems is with prevention.
There was a risk of aiding
and abetting a murderer before.
Even if the person lives
there is the risk of
a defamation lawsuit.
There is the issue that this show
has an image that it is immoral.
We will take it into consideration.
Why don't you leave now?
Ah, Jung Hye In.
I'm Lawyer Kim Sang Woo from Ohsung.
I think you should know.
Starting today, we will need to know
the structure of the show before it airs.
Wait a minute!
We didn't discuss that earlier.
This is our president's policy
as per our counsel.
You have often acted on your own.
You have gone off script
on the air, as well.
You even got SG to acquire
UCN on your own.
What's your point?
We would like you to follow the script
and not act on your own from now on.
At times, you will have to
agree to some of our requests.
Will that increase my chances
of finding Hyun Woo?
That's not it.
You have handed the station over to us,
so you should follow our policies...
I can't promise you anything.
You can deal with your
management issues on your own.
How are the preparations going?
Where have you been?
I had something to take care of.
I received proof that Hyun Woo is alive.
Hyun Woo.
I told you not to watch this.
It's not a good show.
Your mom won't like it either.
Bo Yeon.
I wanted to talk to you for a bit.
Oh, okay.
Let's have a meeting once I'm back.
If you're hiding something...
If it's something we need
for the show, I'll tell you.
I won't stab you in the back
with a live audience
like you did to me yesterday.
I didn't have time to tell you
and it was a method that worked.
If you were able to do a close-up
on a picture on a dead body
then didn't some planning go into that?
I'll be back.
Why are we in the editing room?
Do you need to check something?
Make this play for me.
I'm not good at this stuff.
What is it?
I'll look at first and then let you know.
Don't tell anyone yet.
Okay, I won't.
You just need to press this.
Okay.
- Bo Yeon.
- Yes?
I wasn't sure if you'd come back.
I didn't think you had to.
No, I'm here because I want to be.
Don't feel too burdened by it.
Thank you.
Should I just sit like this?
One moment, please.
Since 2006...
I have been working at SG Chemical
in the management support team.
I've been working in administrations
and my name is Lee Yong Hwan.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
But...
I don't know if I can really do this.
I really don't know.
Since 2008, Professor Kim Woo Jin has
been doing research at Korea University.
I have been in charge of
overseeing that research.
That research involved legal issues
regarding our products.
The law firm Ohsung consulted us on it.
I was the intermediary between
Ohsung and the research team.
I was in charge of communication.
The research had to be kept hidden
until we had the results.
Unless it was very basic communication,
we did not use email or the phone.
Communication continued between
the lawyers, SG, and the research team.
There were many revisions
to the research results.
As for the research results,
I went directly to the lab.
I would bring it back in my USB.
Even money...
The company wouldn't deposit it
into the university account.
It was put into a personal account
and transferred.
It was deposited into the accounts of the
personal accounts of the researchers.
As for the documents
or instructions from Ohsung
I would receive the paperwork directly.
Park Bo Yeon, what did you
talk about with Jung Hye In?
She just said she was sorry and
asked if I could keep doing the show.
I don't know if
Bo Yeon should continue...
It's her choice. Leave her be.
Let's discuss what we should do.
We don't have much time.
What can we do to get
Choi Pil Kyu on our show?
Is that possible?
Do we have something
we can use to make a deal
like we did with Ha Dong Min?
That was only possible because we
had actual evidence he was guilty.
Right now, we can't even meet him and
have nothing to persuade him with.
SG is telling us we can't
have him on our show.
They keep pressuring us.
About this person, Choi Pil Kyu...
Is he possibly involved in Na Jae Hyun
and Ham Tae Young's old case?
That is what the kidnapper
is trying to expose right now.
They're both dead,
so we can't really find out.
I'm sorry.
This is hard to do with a clear head.
One day, I got a document from Ohsung.
They had mistakenly left
a note stuck in there.
It's this here.
It was written on July 16.
It's signed by Choi Pil Kyu
"I took care of it cleanly."
"The three men won't
be a problem again."
"Mister Na won't be speaking again."
"I have found someone to fix it."
"I will keep an eye on things for now."
"I took care of it cleanly."
"The three men won't
be a problem again."
"Mister Na won't be speaking again."
"I have found someone to fix it."
I will keep an eye on things for now.
Oh. Hye In, you're in here?
What is it?
Is something wrong?
Senior.
Yes?
How did you endure it?
When your wife suddenly passed away.
Even when I thought it
was just an accident...
I had a hard time.
I barely got through it
because of Hyun Woo.
But, you...
You never even knew why.
How did you do it?
What do you mean how?
How can anyone endure such a thing?
I'm sorry.
I can't do anything for you.
You were getting
your Ph.D in 2009, right?
Is it true that you took part in research
with Professor Kim Woo Jin for SG Group?
Your name is written here
in the research logs.
Yes, well it is true.
What is this about?
If you look at the emails from SG,
there are requests from their lawyers.
It looks like they're asking you to
modify research results to suit them.
Did that help your thesis?
You're right.
Na Young Hyun, six years old.
She was admitted to our hospital
nine years ago and died during treatment.
[HA DONG MIN]
Na Young Hyun's doctor was...
Doctor Ha Dong Min?
Yes, he was.
I forgot that he worked here.
I don't know much because
I haven't worked here long.
I heard a lot about him
when he appeared on Wanted.
They say he became very famous
when he moved to Soojung Hospital
seven years ago.
By the way...
where did you get that video?
Lee Yong Hwan died a long time ago
and his wife died too.
What is your source?
That's kind of hard for me to tell you.
I'm sorry.
To summarize, Choi Pil Kyu
handled affairs for SG Group.
He hired someone to kill
Ham Tae Young and Na Jae Hyun.
So, the people that Jo Nam Chul
was talking about was SG Group.
The reason that Tae Young
and Na Jae Hyun were meeting...
may have to do with that research.
The kidnapper is trying
to reveal that SG Group
is doing something to kill people.
And that they're trying to cover it up.
SG already knows about it then.
They created that car accident
with Jo Nam Chul on purpose.
They were trying to kill him
to keep him quiet.
They must have become
more certain after
Ham Tae Young
and Na Jae Hyun's mission.
But, you know when President Song
was going to end the show?
Why would they help?
They even bought out the station
like Senior Hye In requested.
They're probably trying to control
the show however they can.
They can shut us down completely
whenever they want to.
We need to get Choi Pil Kyu on this show,
no matter what.
We can do the show with what we have.
We're not a news program
that can just report things.
That's not good enough evidence either.
The mission was to
give him his punishment.
We need to use that
to get him to confess.
That's true, but is there a way?
We have to use his fear.
Make him think that things could be worse
if he doesn't appear on tonight's show.
We know what the kidnapper's motive is.
How are we supposed to find him though?
My brother....
He found the people who
did that to Young Hyun.
My brother ended up dying.
The detective who tried to find
my brother ended up dying.
But, I still tried.
I lost everything.
It was so...
painful and torturous.
It was just so hard.
So, I even tried to forgive them all.
But, I couldn't forgive them.
No one asked for forgiveness.
No one said they had done anything wrong.
We need to look for someone around
us with that same motive.
Let's eat first, Senior.
What if you pass out
before we can catch him?
- I'm not hungry.
- Come on!
Let's go!
Don't they need to think
of the show today?
Hyun Woo needs to be kept safe.
What is that?
It's a note that Na Soo Hyun
made Ko Hyung Joon write.
Where did heck did you get this?
Choi Pil Kyu gave him money
to start his own business?
He was probably ordered to
do so by SG Group.
Ko Hyung Joon never mentioned this.
I went to look for Im Hyung Soon,
but he had fled to The Philippines.
I felt like something would happen
to me if I pursued it any further.
So, I quit being a detective.
My life was ruined
because of Na Soo Hyun.
This mission is to punish Choi Pil Kyu
for his crime from seven years ago.
Na Soo Hyun sent me this note.
Isn't he trying to tell you
to go back and see Ko Hyung Joon?
You can hear more from him or
drag him onto to show as a witness.
Aren't you going to get to work?
Young Gwan.
Yes?
I think Ko Hyung Joon is in danger.
It's someone from SG Group.
Chief, we're at Ilsan-dong,
third floor of Jaeil building.
It's Ko Hyung Joon's office.
He may be confined in there
or even murdered.
We're going in now.
I'll go in first.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
That kid tried to kill me!
What can we do?
I think this time I'm going to kill you.
I didn't tell him about Choi Pil Kyu.
No one knows about him.
But, what can I do?
I think you might talk in the future.
That's the problem here.
What did I do wrong
that you're doing this?
All I did was work on a case.
I stopped working on it like
I was told and quit my job.
That's all I've done.
I heard you said it wasn't
enough money and took more.
That was the price of your life.
Follow me quietly.
Stay here!
Senior!
Who are you?
I'm Shin Dong Wook from UCN.
I wanted to talk you for a moment.
Weren't you people told not
to let any media people in?
What's with the poor security?
Hold on.
Should we talk here?
We're going to air this video tonight.
Then Ohsung and SG will
try to cut tail and run.
"He did it on his own and
we never ordered him to do it."
That video won't make it on air.
Sure.
Suppose it doesn't since UCN
is owned by SG Group.
Then I would be forced to send this
to other stations and newspapers.
- What?
- When I do...
I wonder if Ohsung and SG
will protect you.
Will they say you only
did what you were told?
SG Group will be hearing about this too.
They will be moving quickly to fix this.
Won't you regret this?
You'll be turned into a criminal
without the chance to even protest.
Lawyer Choi Pil Kyu has to
appear on tonight's show.
There has to be a chance
for a confession and arrest.
That way we can say
he received his punishment
without him dying or getting hurt.
I wish you would respect
the advice of the legal team.
Please look for another way.
You said you wanted to find Hyun Woo.
You said you wanted to know
the real reason he died.
You told me that UCN would be
helpful to SG's media business.
You promised me that, right.
I'm doing this to keep that promise.
You have to give me Lawyer Choi Pil Kyu.
Whether you make a deal
or cut all ties...
that is up for you to decide.
I don't know what you mean by that.
About Lawyer Choi Pil Kyu...
there is a witness who says he contracted
assassins to do some work for SG Group.
If this incident is not confessed,
but revealed by us...
all of this will be exposed.
This is the first I've heard of this.
We will need an opportunity
to tell the truth.
How about we have
Lawyer Kim Sang Woo appear too?
We will prepare it so that
Choi Pil Kyu can be legally punished.
I will order it.
Thank you.
Sit.
Weren't you guaranteed management rights?
Yes. Is something wrong?
SG has started to pry into
the direction our show is taking.
It's affecting our ability
to complete the missions.
Isn't the legal team taking on the role
that you were supposed to take?
You said you would ground this show,
so that it didn't go too far.
But, you've never done that once.
You've never stopped Director Shin.
Yesterday, Lee Ji Eun
was right next to you.
Did someone take her or did she run?
Does it make sense that you
couldn't feel anything happen?
There was a blackout
so I was in a lot of shock.
There is no reason for Jung Hye In
to take Lee Ji Eun.
Why is it that you
always call Cha Seung In
instead us when something is wrong?
Are you even trying to find Hyun Woo?
That's something I should ask you.
Have you made any progress
in your investigation?
What's going on?
When he closed his case on Na Jae Hyun,
he received money from Choi Pil Kyu.
He's willing to make a statement
on the show tonight if you need.
Are you no longer a cop?
Are you in broadcasting now?
This isn't even your case,
so why do you keep hanging around!
Because we need to secure
Hyun Woo's safety first.
I'll take care of it now so leave.
I've figured out what it is that
the kidnapper wants to reveal.
I know why your late husband...
and Na Jae Hyun met.
And why they had to die...
So, it was because of that?
That's why Hyun Woo was kidnapped?
He wanted me to know about it.
He wanted me to find out.
Are you okay?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Are you worried about Na Soo Hyun?
I just talked to Lieutenant Cha.
Na Soo Hyun.
He was killed by those people.
Something is very wrong here.
You didn't want things to go this far.
Even if we find Hyun Woo now,
we can still expose the things you want.
If you can't tell me who's behind this,
tell me who that woman is.
That woman who is with Hyun Woo now.
I don't know.
I really don't know that.
Eighth day of the show.
Cracks forming in the team yesterday.
Focus on any changes today.
Right now, I am doing extra research into
the personal lives of the broadcast team.
If the kidnapper got
what he wanted today
do you think he could return Hyun Woo?
Nothing is guaranteed.
There are still two episodes left.
He has even killed people.
He might not just stop
at letting people know.
These are Lee Yong Hwan's
meeting and work logs from SG.
It could be evidence.
Thank you.
These are emails between the
research team and Professor Kim Woo Jin
Thank you.
Once we're done with the show,
watch the documentaries Joon Gu made.
If you watch the Legend series,
he can do things I could never do.
Something that Director Shin
could never do...
A completely different show.
We need something.
Here you go.
I organized all the files.
Okay, thank you.
Writer Yeon?
Yes.
Do you think our show will be okay?
We just have to do it.
We'll do what we can.
Okay.
Joon Gu, what are you doing?
Don't even think about
bringing in an audience today.
I won't. That's not the concept today.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You look neurotic.
I heard lawyers from Ohsung
are coming on the show.
Yes, so?
You'll need this.
It's Lee Ji Eun's mother
trying to blackmail SG Group.
What does this have
to do with Choi Pil Kyu?
Listen to the lawyer talking and
turn it on at the right time.
The viewers will like it.
I need to know what's going to be said
and what the intent is.
Don't you know about media play
or fudging the truth a bit?
You're pretty good at it,
using it here and there.
Gosh, of all things now.
I'll take a look and see if it's useful.
Shin Dong Wook!
Wait.
Don't get upset.
I'll decide what to use or not.
Senior.
You've investigated the broadcast
team quite a bit, right?
Why do you ask?
If the kidnapper is on the team,
who do you think it would be?
Do you have something?
No, I'm just wondering if
I'm overlooking something.
You really are stubborn, you know.
There's no one that's a clear suspect
for me to start an investigation on.
Looking at motive, actions,
and circumstance
I think Director Shin and
Executive Director Choi are likely.
Do any of them have family members
who died suddenly or got ill?
Writer Yeon is a single mother
and her daughter isn't very strong.
She seems to visit the hospital often.
Executive Director Choi's wife
died eight years ago.
Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
I'll tell you when I'm sure.
Tell me right away if you have something.
I'm only sharing in case
you have a lead.
We're really running out of time now.
Okay.
I think you must be mistaken.
What mistake?
First, my husband died like that.
I've barely been able to make a living.
Now, look at what's
happened to my daughter.
How am I supposed to live now?
You don't even know anything for certain.
You shouldn't threaten us like this.
However, you are a family member
of our former employee.
This is to help you out.
It looks like Lee Ji Eun's mother
went to demand money.
Then it looks like she's leaving
without incident.
That...
I know. It's been edited.
Are you using it?
I'll think about it.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
The kidnapper said that
the target had to punished.
Something worse could happen
live on air today.
Everyone needs to be on guard.
Keep a close watch on any path
that goes outside from the studio.
Yes, sir.
If Tae Young died an unfair death,
I need to straighten things out now.
I took care of it cleanly.
The three men won't be a problem again.
Everything on this show is real.
We are doing this show at the request of
the person who has kidnapped my son.
Jung Hye In's Wanted is starting now.
First, I would like to address
the trouble we had on last night's show.
I want to offer my sincere apologies.
As for the accomplice Lee Ji Eun,
who escaped during the blackout
the police are doing everything
that they can to find her.
Last night, we received
the eighth mission.
The target of this mission
is Choi Pil Kyu.
He was found kidnapped, passed out,
and confined in his car.
He was taken to the hospital right away,
where he received treatment.
Let's keep today's mission simple
and get through it.
The point of all of this trying to
figure out what SG is covering up.
I told you before
when I checked the script.
We need two people battling it out,
at the very least.
Our show isn't some
sort of news documentary.
It's not up to me what
the kidnapper wants to do.
If we complete the mission,
then Hyun Woo will be safe.
Let's proceed with the mission first
and then discuss it.
We don't know how things will work out.
I'm saying this because I don't know
how things will work out.
You might do something like
you did last time.
I can't accept you acting on your own
like that any longer.
I can't predict what's going
to happen right now either.
Stop getting mad about what
hasn't happened and just work.
The crime that Lawyer Choi Pil Kyu
committed seven years ago.
What could it be?
This morning we received a video
from an anonymous source.
It was written on July 16.
It's signed by Choi Pil Kyu
I took care of it cleanly.
The three men won't be a problem again.
Mister Na won't be speaking again.
I have found someone to fix it.
I will keep an eye on things for now.
The note in the video sent to
us revealed something to us.
Surprisingly, it answered
the questions we have had
as we've been doing missions.
My late husband Ham Tae Young's
car accident.
As well as the remains we
found that were of Na Jae Hyun.
If the witness statement
we heard is true...
And if that note was really
written by Choi Pil Kyu...
seven years ago in 2009
he conspired to murder
Ham Tae Young and Na Jae Hyun.
These are the hit men
who were hired to kill them.
One of them is Jo Nam Chul
who appeared on our show
as the target of the third mission.
The other is Im Hyung Soon,
who was murdered by Jo Nam Chul.
You have to go on now.
What is Choi Pil Kyu planning to say?
There is strong evidence
against him, so...
I don't think he will completely deny it.
SG will acknowledge
they ordered the murder.
He'll say he didn't hire
them to murder himself.
Ohsung ordered it internally and
he was only delivering the message.
Ohsung agreed to take the blame?
Ohsung needs to save SG
and they need to survive too.
He's going to be too loyal.
SG will say they never
received that message.
Then won't SG get out of this?
We have round two with SG.
We have to get Choi Pil Kyu arrested
in order to succeed with the mission.
We are aiming to get at the truth
and get the facts straight.
We have decided to give Choi Pil Kyu
the opportunity to defend himself.
However, Choi Pil Kyu
is a party to the case.
There is a very good chance he would
lie in order to look innocent.
We have a lawyer from
his law firm, Ohsung.
He is here to tell us
the entire truth about this case.
Ask Choi Pil Kyu the first question.
Jung Hye In, get it together.
Start the questions.
Choi Pil Kyu.
Do you admit to the charges made
at you in the video we just saw?
No.
Then can you please
explain what happened?
That note in the video is a fake.
Neither SG Group of Ohsung have
ever hired anyone to carry out a murder.
I have never been
involved in such a thing.
Don't listen to anything he says.
Move onto Ohsung.
Your law firm said that you could
reveal the facts of this case.
- Is Choi Pil Kyu correct?
- Yes.
The man in the video is Lee Yong Hwan.
He worked at SG Chemical
from 2006 to 2009.
His claims have no credibility.
Why would you say that?
From 2007 to 2009, he was
not an employee with integrity.
Especially in 2009
he could not work properly
due to alcoholism and depression.
He was eventually fired.
He was very spiteful about
being fired and spread rumors.
He even threatened SG employees
and blackmailed them for money.
Because Lee Yong Hwan had mental issues,
we decided not to pursue a lawsuit.
Can you prove all of that?
I do have records of a lawsuit that
we had been preparing against him.
I can show it to you if needed.
- Also...
- What else is there?
I have a video for you.
I submitted it before the show.
Lee Yong Hwan's wife used
the videos that he left behind.
It's a video of her using it
to demand money from us.
Can you please play it?
- Don't play it.
- Play it.
Shin Dong Wook!
You punk!
One more thing.
Lee Yong Hwan is
the father of Lee Ji Eun
the kidnapper's accomplice.
So, that woman in the video jumped
off the building and committed suicide.
That is Lee Ji Eun's mother.
Can we trust the statement
of a person like that?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Jung Hye In, I'm going
to play an audio file.
This story was all Ohsung's idea.
What does this have
to do with Choi Pil Kyu?
Listen to the lawyer talking and
turn it on at the right time.
The viewers will like it.
I need to know what's going
to be said and what the intent is.
Don't you know about media play
or fudging the truth a bit?
This audio file that you just heard
was from before the show.
That was President Song delivering
Ohsung's demands to our show's director.
We weren't making demands.
Since our evidence does
not match what is being said...
I will ask another guest to come out.
It's better to show people
what SG has been doing.
And to show them making their claims.
Rather than trying to
prove that it's all a lie.
Was that your plan from the start?
Why didn't you consult us?
I only needed to do it if Ohsung
didn't follow the plan.
- Ko Hyung Joon.
- Yes.
You came to me after
Na Soo Hyun threatened you.
You delivered the fifth mission to me.
Yes, that's right.
Seven years ago,
you were a police detective.
You were in charge of Na Jae Hyun's
missing person's case.
Yes.
At the time...
you closed down your case at the order
of the late commissioner, Lee Tae Kyun.
I heard you quit your job too.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Is there another side of the story,
beside what I just said?
I was able to quit back then because...
I was able to quit back then because
Choi Pil Kyu came to visit me.
He gave me 100 million won.
That's him right there?
Yes, that's him.
I was just a detective with
a small salary, and I was tired.
I had no desire to investigate.
Honestly, I was greedy for money too.
I've thought about it a lot.
What if I had investigated
that case properly?
If only I had felt a responsibility to
the victim, this wouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry.
I am truly sorry.
According to Ko Hyung Joon
Choi Pil Kyu tried to shut down
the Na Jae Hyun case.
So, he bribed a detective.
- Get up.
- What is this?
Let go of me!
Let go!
Let me go!
There is a team of police
waiting outside.
Choi Pil Kyu will be arrested on the spot
and will undergo investigation.
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Just follow us.
Choi Pil Kyu.
You're under arrest for conspiracy to
murder Ham Tae Young and Na Jae Hyun
and for bribery of a police detective.
Make Choi Pil Kyu pay for the crime
he committed seven years ago.
We have now completed the eighth mission.
Now, that we have completed
the eighth mission
we have figured out what the kidnapper
wants us to discover through this show.
However...
we still have many questions.
I'm going to use the bathroom.
Why would SG Group do such a thing?
Why would they kill their
own family, Ham Tae Young?
As well as Na Jae Hyun?
The night of July 12, 2009.
Why did Ham Tae Young
and Na Jae Hyun meet?
Also, Professor Kim Woo Jin
from the first mission.
And Ha Dong Min from the second mission.
How are they involved?
We have received help from the police.
They have helped us figure out
Hyun Woo's kidnapper's motive.
Na Soo Hyun wanted to get revenge on
those who killed his brother and sister.
Lee Ji Eun was pained
by her father's death
and wanting the world to know the truth.
The kidnapper may
be like these accomplices.
He may have lost a loved one
and is looking for revenge.
It's me.
I'm with Lieutenant Oh Mi Ock.
I don't know exactly where.
Jung Hye In and Lieutenant Cha know too.
Soo Hyun... is dead.
The people from SG killed him.
Senior, is something wrong?
Yes, Lee Ji Eun called
the kidnapper's burner phone.
I called but no one's picking up
and you probably can't trace it.
I'm sorry. It was my mistake.
If he knows that Lee Ji Eun's with us
and that Na Soo Hyun is dead...
he might do something reckless.
- What's wrong with Jung Hye In?
- What is it?
Park Bo Yeon?
Is something wrong on set?
Where is Choi Joon Gu?
He got a call.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever