[EPISODE 13]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I think Senior Joon Gu is the kidnapper.
His wife died eight years ago.
She was seven months pregnant
and no one knew the cause.
If this has something do with
what happened seven years ago
it all makes perfect sense.
He knows all about broadcasting.
He was near me and able to observe me.
Lee Ji Eun was able to get
a call out to the kidnapper.
Right after that,
Executive Director Choi disappeared.
Why didn't I know?
He was right next to me.
Why? Why didn't I know?
I was suspicious even after
Jo Nam Chul died.
Jung Hye In.
It wasn't your fault.
No, it was my fault.
I'm the one who lost him.
It was me who...
We know who the kidnapper is now.
We need to find him
as quickly as possible.
I'm going to find Hyun Woo.
I promised you, didn't I?
I will find him.
I should go find Jung Hye In.
Let me call first.
Hello?
Joon Gu?
Is that you, Joon Gu?
Has something happened to him?
Writer Yeon, turn on some highlights.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Did the two of you know?
About Joon Gu taking Hyun Woo...
How did you know, Dong Wook?
Joon Gu just called me.
What did he say?
He said to finish the rest of the show.
He wants you to reveal that SG Group
ordered people to kill Na Soo Hyun.
Otherwise, he says he doesn't
know what he might do.
I can't do this anymore.
How can I stand in front
of a camera right now?
Hyun Woo... we need to go look for him.
Let's go look for Hyun Woo!
Jung Hye In.
Jung Hye In, look at me.
You have to do this.
Joon Gu will be watching the show.
He will want to do the remaining
episodes the way he intends.
So, he will do what he says.
Hye In.
Director Shin is correct.
The show...
you must do it.
Executive Director Choi is acting out
because Na Soo Hyun has died.
You need to finish the show in order
for us to find Hyun Woo safely.
Soo Hyun is dead.
The people from SG killed him.
Soo Hyun!
You know me, don't you?
I've seen you before.
What do you mean you've seen me?
Back then, you came with
Detective Kim Sang Shik.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I see I'm right.
My career has been about finding
people with just one picture.
I'm a natural at remembering faces.
I was checking to see if
Kim Sang Shik came alone.
I thought it was suspicious that you
were parked outside waiting.
If the detective hadn't stepped in,
you would be...
You're talking nonsense.
This is very interesting.
The man who kidnapped Jung Hye In's son
also brought up Detective Kim Sang Shik.
Did you kidnap Jung Hye In's son?
If I told people about this...
what would happen?
Give me your phone.
I can't have you report this.
Stand right here so that
I can see your feet.
Jo Nam Chul is here at Set I
waiting room at UCN.
My connection to Detective Kim Sang Shik
has been found out.
I think we need to get him out of here.
We can't take him out of there.
We have to get rid of him.
Are you okay?
The assistant director knows my face.
It will be easy to get the police
to come after me.
Who are you?
You have to go on air soon.
We want to film some interview footage.
I need to put the mic on you.
Hold on.
What is this? Who are you?
Me?
I'm the younger brother of Na Jae Hyun,
the person that you killed.
Soo Hyun!
He deserved to die.
What are you going to do now?
You can't get caught yet, Mister.
I'll be seen on the CCTV and
the assistant director will recognize me.
I want you to confirm that it was me.
I shouldn't have dragged you into this.
Mister...
That plan you talked about?
I want to see it through.
Even if I don't get to see it,
I want other people to see it.
I was planning on turning myself in
and paying for my crimes anyhow.
It's okay.
Also...
I got revenge for my brother.
Take care of yourself.
Keep in touch and get out of here.
I'm sorry, Mister.
I have to do this so
people don't suspect you.
I shouldn't have dragged you into this.
I made you get blood on your hands.
Now, you've died at their hands.
What's going on right now?
I'll tell you later.
Tell me right now.
Why did Jung Hye In run out and
where is the Executive Director?
What was the phone call from
the Executive Director about?
Joon Gu...
is the culprit.
Why would he?
Why would he do such a thing?
Was it because of his bad relationship
with President Song?
His wife died suddenly eight years ago.
She was pregnant and
they couldn't save the baby.
I think it's connected to
how Na Young Hyun died.
We still have two episodes left.
The accomplices are dying,
going missing, or being revealed.
Isn't this more dangerous for Hyun Woo?
He won't hurt Hyun Woo.
He's not in a normal state of mind.
We should put out a public notice
and get information.
That could provoke him even more.
We have just heard from the kidnapper.
He has asked us to reveal
one thing on this show today.
His accomplice Na Soo Hyun
was stabbed to death today.
It is presumed that SG Group
ordered for him to be killed.
Yes, did you look into it?
Choi Joon Gu has disappeared.
The police are looking for him.
Look into Choi Joon Gu
and any place he might go to.
Report back often.
Earlier in the show
we told you that we figured out
what the kidnapper wanted us to know.
This case started with the death of
Na Jae Hyun and Na Soo Hyun's sister.
In 2007, Na Young Hyun was six years old.
She died of acute interstitial pneumonia.
The cause for her illness
was unknown at the time.
The first mission's target
was Kim Woo Jin.
He was a professor of veterinary science
at Korea University.
He conducted research between
the years of 2008 and 2009.
That research contributed to
the death of Na Young Hyun.
The second mission's target
was Ha Dong Min.
He was Na Young Hyun's physician in 2007.
He knew the cause of her illness,
but distorted the truth.
Both of these men received support
from SG Group after the fact.
They continued to
thrive in their careers.
[HAM TAE YOUNG:
SG CHEMICAL VICE PRESIDENT]
Now, we have one crucial question left.
Why did Na Jae Hyun
and Ham Tae Young meet?
Na Jae Hyun found evidence of
what caused his sister's death.
Ham Tae Young was Vice President of
SG Group's affiliate SG Chemical.
We believe it is connected to
a product made by SG Chemical.
That is our theory.
Find Hyun Woo now.
Bring Lee Ji Eun to me, as well.
Ham Tae Young wanted SG Chemical
to take responsibility.
He wanted to set things right.
SG Group wanted to conceal the truth.
So, it seems these two men were murdered.
Today, we will end the show here.
We will end it by showing the connections
between all the people in the missions.
I would like to make a request to
the person who has Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo...
please just return him to me.
Even if you don't have Hyun Woo...
we will keep digging and find the truth.
I'll keep going to the end.
So, please...
Please give me Hyun Woo.
Give Hyun Woo back to me.
Mother-in-law.
What is going on?
You said you'd never come here.
I'm sorry.
It didn't work out the way I thought.
I'm going to have to go
to my last resort.
Last resort? What is that?
What are you thinking right now?
What about Hyun Woo?
You can stop now.
You've done enough.
You wanted people to know
what happened to my daughter.
But, to do that to that young child...
You don't know how much I've regretted
accepting you when you came to me.
What has that young child done wrong?
Let's return him to his mom now.
Wrong?
Then what did my Sun Young do wrong?
And what about my baby who
didn't even get to open its eyes?
What about Soo Hyun and his siblings
who all died at their hands?
What did they do that so wrong
that they died like that?
What?
Where do you think
Executive Director Choi is?
He's probably moving Hyun Woo first.
We need to find him before he does.
I was thinking about it
all through the show.
This person.
Hyun Woo, I told you not to watch this.
It's not a good show.
Your mom wouldn't like it either.
Executive Choi's mother is dead.
The only older woman who
would help him like this is...
Who else would be as sad
about his wife's death as him?
It would be her mother.
It's Choi Joon Gu's mother-in-law.
Let's go.
Everything will end tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
You should pack your things.
Once SG Group finds out and comes,
this thing will end immediately.
We will all die.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Yes, Chief.
We're on our way to Choi Joon Gu's
mother-in-law's home.
It's Songhwa Apartment in Yeoui-do.
Apartment 509.
We'll be arriving soon.
There's a chance that Hyun Woo will
be there.
It could become a hostage situation.
We will need back-up.
Okay.
Bringing Hyun Woo back safely
is the top priority.
Got it?
Things just keep going wrong.
We know who the kidnapper is.
We will catch him.
Regarding Na Soo Hyun,
I'll make sure to take care...
Right about now...
I think it's a good time to make an
appearance at the police department.
Excuse me?
A detective kidnapped a criminal
and hid her away.
He doesn't follow orders.
He goes here and there
doing illegal investigations.
I don't know how that's even possible.
I will deal with
Lieutenant Cha Seung In...
Take care of it immediately.
Hands and feet that you
can't control should be cut off.
Yes, I understand.
I told you not to come outside!
Executive Director Choi doesn't seem
like a person who'd hurt a child.
He already kidnapped Hyun Woo
just to get what he wants.
Stand guard here.
Hye In, this way.
He didn't come down. I'm coming up now.
Hyun Woo!
We're too late.
Chief, he's already left.
Our back-up has arrived.
I'll tell them to search the area.
They can't have gone too far. Okay.
I'll go out and let them know.
Is Lieutenant Cha Seung In here?
He's out at a crime scene.
Where is that, exactly?
[INTERNAL AFFAIRS]
What is this about?
He's going to have come back now.
I'll give him a call.
Hey, Cha Seung In.
Internal Affairs is looking for you.
Did you cause trouble again or what?
Lieutenant Cha Seung In.
What is it?
All right, I'll head in now.
Internal Affairs is looking for me.
It's only logical that they
would come looking for me.
It could be an order from SG.
I think I need to go for now.
If SG is getting involved
like they did with Na Jae Hyun's
missing person's case...
you may have trouble using
these tapes to find Hyun Woo.
Could I take these with me
to my broadcast team?
I'm going to pretend I didn't find these.
There needs to be one sane person
with a crazy show like this.
Why does that have to be you?
When everything falls apart...
you'll need someone
to take responsibility.
I'm a little worried about
Executive Director Choi.
If he's going be like an ethics
teacher in every situation
won't that take too
much energy out of us?
I need that.
I'm not going to think about whether
something is right or wrong.
It would be nice to have
someone think about it for me.
Writer Yeon, you're my accelerator,
and Joon Gu is my brake.
That guy who killed Na Soo Hyun
is going to be released soon.
A criminal is getting released.
A detective that worked hard to catch
him is getting called in?
How great is SG that this is happening?
I will do what it takes to find a way.
Get going. See you later.
I'll bring Hye In so
see you during the meeting.
It's a relief that we were able to help
them thanks to the show.
Let's not get too excited.
We are doing the show because
the kidnapper is demanding it.
Don't forget that we're forced into this
because we need to find Hyun Woo.
Ah... okay.
You should eat.
- Okay.
- Do you know what though?
You need to eat well
in order to last long.
I'm sure everything was
new and hard for you today.
You did a good job.
Thank you, Executive Director.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
She's alive... she's alive!
Director Shin, where are you?
Hello.
I'll be right there.
Can you take me to SG Life?
I think it'd be better if you didn't go,
especially alone.
No, I have to go.
I need to know what SG is planning
to do after seeing today's show.
If they were planning to hurt me,
they would have done it quietly already.
Just like they did to my husband.
All right.
I think... there must have been a
misunderstanding between us.
Is that so?
With the matter of Choi Pil Kyu,
let's chalk that up to excessive loyalty.
However, what you said about
Tae Young and SG Chemical...
and the way you did it.
I was a bit shocked by it.
You did everything the
kidnapper asked you to do.
You spoke of these theories
as if they were facts.
Whether they are facts or not will be
revealed once we look into it deeper.
Will you continue with the show?
Why do you ask?
I heard that Executive Director Choi
suddenly disappeared.
And the police are looking for him.
Isn't he the kidnapper?
We haven't found Hyun Woo so we
will have to continue with the show.
More so because the kidnapper
is acting very recklessly.
That is a relief to hear.
I was worried you might stop once you
found out who the kidnapper was.
It didn't turn out to be
what I imagined it to be.
Anyway...
What are you referring to?
We are looking for Hyun Woo right now.
We are using all our resources.
We know who the kidnapper is now.
I think we might find
him before the police.
We have put in a strong request
to the police this time.
The show will be a cooperation between
SG Group and you, Jung Hye In.
I would like for it to end
happily with us finding Hyun Woo.
That way, I will have justification
for acquiring UCN.
I will be thankful as long
as you can find Hyun Woo.
I did make you that promise.
I'm glad we're of the same opinion.
I trust you will correct the story from
today's show by the next episode.
I'll think about it.
Wait... I think I forgot one thing.
Whether the police find him or we do...
Hyun Woo will come to us first.
I thought you should know.
Lieutenant Cha.
From the start, were you in on planning
a UCN blackout and taking Lee Ji Eun?
Or did you later hear about it and
just not report it?
Think carefully.
Did you take part in it
or did you not report it?
You know the weight of those crimes
are completely different, right?
"Ah, how did they find out?"
You know that man you caught
at Ko Hyung Joon's office.
He says he witnessed you near
Na Soo Hyun as he was dying.
That's a bit strange.
Why were you there?
He even saw Lee Ji Eun and Jung Hye In
run away in your car.
You apparently told them to do it.
Why aren't you responding when
people are speaking to you?
Lieutenant Cha Seung In.
It only becomes harder if
you drag things out like this.
We're just here to help.
Do you have a warrant?
Should I bring one?
It will end well after
a few days of investigation.
There's no need to be so prickly.
Unless you plan to quit being a cop,
just cooperate with us.
This is from Senior Joon Gu's
mother-in-law's house.
He's been preparing for this
for a long time.
He wanted to make his own show.
It probably got stopped due
to external pressure.
Joon Gu left the station in 2009.
Everything's making sense now.
I only looked at it briefly.
Kim Woo Jin, Ha Dong Min, Im Hyung Soon,
Jo Nam Chul, Ko Hyung Joon...
the police commissioner,
and Choi Pil Kyu.
He's been watching them and keeping
track of what they've done wrong.
He started in 2009 and went until now.
There are files on Ko Hyung Joon's
detective agency too.
We better look at this quickly.
We need to know why Joon Gu
wanted to do this
and what he planned in episode 10.
We have to figure it out.
It's been exposed
that he's the kidnapper.
He might think that
this is his last chance.
We need to figure out his plan and
get a step ahead or negotiate with him.
- We can use the show to...
- What if...
What if we find out what he wants
and can't do it for him?
No, what if it's something
we should not do for him.
We still have to do it.
Hyun Woo is in more danger now.
SG is looking for Hyun Woo too.
[CHOI JOON GU?]
[REVENGE FOR LOSING FAMILY.]
Wow! It's amazing.
I think the kidnapper is
on the broadcast team.
When Jung Hye In ran off the set,
she figured it out, right?
The team is gathered up somewhere,
so it seems like they all know too.
I think so.
I think the police know too.
Lieutenant Cha Seung In came running in.
He asked where that person was.
Should I take a guess who that is?
Executive Director Choi Joon Gu.
How did you know?
I've done some investigating of my own.
Oh! It's so hot, isn't it?
I told you. I have nothing to say.
I'm only here because you begged me.
I barely managed to get permission to
write the article too, so please help me.
Just tell me what your son-in-law
was like from your point of view.
That's all I wanted to ask.
You're the only family he has left.
What do you mean family?
We're strangers now
after all these years.
He should forget
everything and live well.
It's been so long
since my daughter passed.
Then tell me how he was before
your daughter passed away.
Sorry, I'm not feeling very good.
Please leave. I have nothing to say.
Don't look for me again.
Wait, Ma'am!
You recorded an audio file today, right?
Email it to me.
By the way...
You know what you promised me?
When do I get it?
I want to listen to it first.
We'll talk if there's anything useful.
Hey, wait.
What the heck is this?
So, get me something good tomorrow.
Please do a good job.
Get me some high quality information.
They already know who the kidnapper is.
Why would they do the show tomorrow?
Of course! They haven't found Hyun Woo.
It's only fun if we get to see
the ending the kidnapper has prepared.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Hello.
Reporter Jang Jin Woong?
It's Choi Joon Gu.
I need a favor from you.
If you do it for me,
once everything is done with
I'm thinking of giving you
an exclusive interview.
First, tell me something to go on.
I need a taste of it before I decide
to gamble my life on this or not.
I must have called the wrong person.
If you don't want to,
there's nothing I can do.
- I'm hanging up.
- Wait, wait!
You didn't hang up, right?
This is like the time
you destroyed my phone.
You don't hear people out.
You should converse with people
and try to convince them.
What is this favor you need?
Hey, it looks like they're going to keep
him there until the show ends.
We can keep our eye on him here.
Who knows what happens if they move him.
Are they really from internal affairs?
They really are.
The problem is that they
report to SG not the police.
Have you heard from Oh Mi Ock?
Why haven't I seen her around?
I don't really know.
I'm worried about her too.
You hasn't even reported in to the bosses
and she's supposed to be on break now.
Do you think they will
only go after Seung In?
Do you really not know anything?
No, I really don't know.
Stop!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Senior, where are you?
I know you're with Lee Ji Eun.
Senior Seung In is being
held by internal affairs.
Can you handle it on your own?
I will go to you. I need to do something.
354 Guro-dong.
I'm being chased inside the building.
Gosh, seriously. It's so damn hot too.
Hey lady, don't make me sweat.
Just come quietly.
Hey, get over here.
You should have learned by now,
your own senior died from butting in.
You could really end up dying without
a single creature finding out.
You should know when to fear something.
Get in!
Police! Put your hands up!
Let the girl go!
You punk.
Tell Lieutenant Cha Seung In.
This happened to you
because of Cha Seung In.
Lee Young Gwan! Young Gwan.
Lee Young Gwan!
Young Gwan!
[EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR CHOI JOON GU]
This caller is currently available.
You will be directed to voicemail.
You can start recording at the beep.
Press one to save the voicemail.
Press two to leave...
Chief, this is Jung Hye In.
What happened to Lieutenant Cha Seung In?
I understand.
Every single day...
I just...
thought that I should've
pretended not to know.
It kept popping up in my mind.
That's just the way the world is.
I should have lived
my life thinking that way.
But, I couldn't pretend
that I didn't see.
They had tubes in their throats.
She was a girl around Ji Eun's age
holding a picket.
I wondered to myself what
I would do if she were my child.
I kept thinking that it was
my fault she became that way.
Ji Eun.
Your dad is sorry.
Honey, I'm sorry.
I didn't have the strength or ability
to protect my family.
I got caught up in something like this.
Are you okay, Writer Yeon?
Huh?
We have one of those products
in our house.
I've been using it too.
Many people are probably
using it without knowing.
Have you found out anything?
I think Executive Director Choi
wanted people to know about this.
I think he included the ratings condition
so that everyone could find out.
No, I don't think it was only
about informing people.
Everyone who has tried to cover
this up for SG has died so far.
If he wants to complete his
revenge in the same way...
It would have to be the person who
ordered everything from SG.
He might attempt to kill
President Ham Tae Seok.
That can't be.
Do you think he would go that far?
It could be because Na Soo Hyun
or Lee Ji Eun wanted to do it.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
This is the office for Wanted, right?
Yes, it is. How can we help you?
I was so shocked by the show
and that's why I'm here.
That product from SG Chemical...
it's the air purifier humidifier, right?
How did you know?
It was that child, Na Young Hyun.
I knew when I heard that she died
of acute interstitial pneumonia.
That's how my daughter died too.
Did you know it was
the air purifier humidifier?
No.
At first, I didn't know.
How many years ago was it?
A director came to see me
and he told me about it.
He told me about other people like me
and my daughter who were suffering.
People who became this way
because of the air purifier humidifier.
He said there were many.
I thought that director
could be involved.
You might know more about it,
so I came to tell you.
What was his name?
I had kept that card just in case.
Choi Joon Gu.
When he came to see me...
he said it wouldn't be easy
to expose this issue.
I got scared off.
I said I wouldn't do the interview.
He came to see me several times.
One time...
he even told me about his own story.
Honey, I'll be going now.
- You're leaving?
- Yes.
Why do you keep coughing?
Shouldn't we go to the hospital?
It's okay.
I can deal with a cold.
I can't even take cold medicine anyway.
You should turn this on.
It's not good if the air is dry.
You're not eating well.
What should we do with you?
My mom is coming later.
Don't worry about it and go.
I'd like to go the hospital with you,
but I'm so busy with work.
It's like that everyday. You should go.
Okay, I'll be back soon. Oh yeah!
Baby, your dad will be back soon.
Be good with your mom.
Baby says to get going.
I'll be back!
What is it? Should I buy something
for you when I come home?
Hello? Why aren't you talking?
Honey?
What... what is it? Is something wrong?
Can't breathe... I can't breathe!
Honey! Sun Young!
Sun Young, what is it?
And in just one week...
he said he lost both his wife and baby.
He didn't know it, at the time.
He couldn't have imagined it
was the air purifier humidifier.
I tried my best to tell you all the
details about my daughter and I.
I don't know if it will help you.
It was very helpful.
Thank you for coming out
of your way to talk to us.
Please contact me if you
ever have any questions to ask.
There are more people
like me that I know.
Thank you.
Jung Hye In.
If I...
If, at least, I had helped
that director back then...
And people had found out
about this back then...
maybe Hyun Woo wouldn't
have been kidnapped.
People might not have died.
Don't you think that?
No, no.
Don't speak that way.
Hyun Woo.
I really hope you find him.
Eat some.
You'll be tired if you
get questioned all day today.
What more do you have left to ask?
Shouldn't you know better?
I will be disciplined for what
you've already questioned me about.
Or I'll been cleared of all fault.
The situation has changed.
Your location and movements have been
startling ever since Wanted started.
Right now, you're even being investigated
for kidnapping Song Hyun Woo.
So, why don't we retrace
your past seven years?
Let's stop here for now.
As long as you don't resign,
we'll probably see you soon.
Get to the hospital quickly.
What do you mean?
That kid met the wrong senior.
He learned his job the wrong way.
He tried to catch a group of four
burglars by himself and got hurt.
Where is Lee Young Gwan?
Come this way.
Senior.
Who was it?
Who did this?
Lee Ji Eun...
Have to save her.
Lee Ji Eun.
They took her.
Hello.
Hye In.
It's me.
Where is Hyun Woo?
Where is Hyun Woo, you son of a bitch!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever