It's me.
I'm with Lieutenant Oh Mi Ock.
Soo Hyun... is dead.
SG sent people to kill him.
I think Senior Joon Gu is the kidnapper.
His wife died eight years ago.
She was seven months pregnant
and no one knew the cause.
If this has something do with what
happened seven years ago
it all makes perfect sense.
Lee Ji Eun was able to get
a call out to the kidnapper.
Right after that, Executive Director Choi
disappeared.
Hello? Joon Gu?
Joon Gu just called me.
What did he say?
He said to finish the rest of the show.
He wants you to reveal that SG Group
ordered people to kill Na Soo Hyun.
We have just heard from the kidnapper.
He has asked us to reveal
one thing on this show today.
His accomplice Na Soo Hyun
was stabbed to death today.
It is presumed that SG Group
ordered him to be killed.
Where do you think
Executive Director Choi went?
Executive Choi's mother is dead.
The only older woman who
would help him like this is...
Everything will end tomorrow.
You should pack your things.
Once SG Group finds out and comes,
this thing will end immediately.
This is from Senior Joon Gu's
mother-in-law's house.
He's been preparing for this
for a long time.
Kim Woo Jin, Ha Dong Min, Im Hyung Soon,
Jo Nam Chul, Ko Hyung Joon...
the police commissioner,
and Choi Pil Kyu.
He's been watching them
and keeping track of
what they've done wrong.
He's had them investigated by a
private detective agency since 2009.
We need to know why Joon Gu
wanted to do this show.
And what he planned to do in episode 10.
This is the office for Wanted, right?
Honey! Sun Young!
And in just one week...
he said he lost both his wife and baby.
He didn't know it, at the time.
He couldn't have imagined it was
the air purifier humidifier.
Hello?
Hye In, it's me.
Where is Hyun Woo?
Where is Hyun Woo, you son of a bitch!
[EPISODE 14]
I didn't think you'd come
home until the show ended.
Don't turn on the lights.
Did you come here to hide?
No.
How did you know the entry code?
You're pretty simple with these things.
I tried your birthday and it worked.
What about Hyun Woo?
He's okay.
Can you really say he's okay
just because he's physically safe?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me about your wife
and how the station shut you down?
About all the people dying...
Why didn't you ask to do it together
before doing something so big?
Those people who died...
was it really you who did it?
Yes.
What if I report you? Why are you here?
I thought you would want
to see how this show concludes.
That's why I pulled you into it.
I don't know you at all.
You talk about me like
you know me so well.
- I came here because...
- What are you planning to do?
- I have to finish things.
- Turn yourself in.
Turn yourself in, hand Hyun Woo over,
and as for the show...
I will do what it is that you wanted.
Do you know what I learned
over and over these last eight years?
I was so naive.
Even I had made the show back then...
nothing would have changed.
Then what do we do to change things?
What is it that you want to do?
Here.
What is this?
You'll know once you see it.
This...
If you end up finishing
the show on your own
please make sure to use it.
Lieutenant Oh! Where are you?
I'm sorry I haven't called.
Lee Ji Eun has been taken by SG.
Lieutenant Cha was with internal affairs
and four of them came.
Detective Lee tried to stop them
and he ended up getting injured.
Both the internal affair and
this attack on Young Gwan...
they're going after Lieutenant Cha.
I got a call from Choi Joon Gu.
Where is Lee Ji Eun?
Senior.
Why are you doing this to me?
You need to tell me
where Hyun Woo is first.
SG is looking for you right now.
If they find you before we do,
Hyun Woo will be...
Saying that to me won't change anything.
I wouldn't have started this
to begin with if that mattered.
If you want to get Hyun Woo back
proceed with the show like
you have been up until now.
Also, about Lee Ji Eun...
Bring her to Ohseok Terminal at midnight.
That way...
you will get proof
that Hyun Woo is alive.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep
Lee Ji Eun safe.
I'll be here until Detective Lee's
family arrives.
I can't trust any other police.
I don't know who's
connected to SG and who isn't.
Chief, I have a favor to ask.
Young Gwan and Senior Mi Ock were
hurt and are at the hospital.
Please have police stand patrol
at the hospital.
Two or three at a time, to be safe.
I'll talk to you later.
Where is Hyun Woo?
I told you I don't know.
Even if you don't know right now,
you must know where he'll end up.
I'm not a person with a lot of time.
It would be best for you
to talk while I'm still here.
Once I leave this place,
who knows what these men will do.
You can't go in there.
I told you he's not in.
Who are you?
I told you he's not in!
Who are you anyway?
Call him now.
Tell him Cha Seung In is here
and I'll be waiting for him.
Seriously, what's with you?
Now!
Yes, President.
There's a Cha Seung In here
and he's causing a commotion.
He says he'll wait until you come.
Give him something cold to drink.
I'll be right there.
Lieutenant Cha Seung In?
I've heard a lot about you.
I was hoping to meet you anyhow.
Please sit.
Lee Ji Eun.
Where is she?
Lee Ji Eun?
Why would you ask me about her?
I would think you'd know better.
I'm just checking up
on all possibilities.
My apologies.
That's right, Chief.
Anywhere in a ten minute vicinity from
SG Life that can used to confine someone.
As soon as possible, please.
A place where you could beat someone,
but screams wouldn't be heard outside.
A place with good soundproofing or
set apart from other buildings.
Why are you asking that,
out of the blue?
Is this about Lee Ji Eun, by any chance?
Can you do this without Young Gwan?
I'll call for back-up if
it gets dangerous.
Please just look into it quickly.
I'll tell you all about it later.
Mom, it's me.
How is Jung Eun doing?
Mom, has she been coughing lately?
Oh, really?
I'm going to take her to the hospital
once I'm done with this show.
I want her to get some tests done.
No, I'm just worried about something.
How about you, Mom?
Are you feeling okay?
Okay.
Mom, don't turn on the humidifier
and don't use the air purifier.
They say it's not good for you.
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Yes?
The mission has arrived.
[NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
DO NOT STOP DOING THE SHOW.]
Choi Joon Gu knows us
better than anyone else.
He knows I won't stop
as long as he has Hyun Woo.
I know you feel the same way, Dong Wook.
But, he sent a mission like this anyway.
That means he's planning to do
something big that should not be aired.
We have no story for this episode.
He doesn't want us to know beforehand.
He's saying he'll control it
while the show is airing.
Then what are we supposed to do?
We need to try and figure out
what he's planning to do.
That's the only way we can prepare.
If this show had gone the way
he had originally planned
what do you think the ninth and tenth
missions would've been?
How is Young Gwan doing?
He's seriously injured.
What's Cha Seung In doing
when his kid is hurt like that?
I don't know. Who can stop him?
Tell him not to cause anymore trouble
and to be careful.
And let me know if he needs help.
I'll do that.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Is the mission here?
I'm thinking that Choi Joon Gu
sent an unexpected mission.
By looking at the pattern so far
I think Executive Director Choi has
been achieving two goals at once.
One was to use the
victims and perpetrators
of this air purifier humidifier
and fitting them together
like puzzle pieces to tell this story.
The second was to
punish the perpetrators.
If everything has gone according to plan
what is left for him to do?
Right now, look back at
all the targets of the mission.
Their connection to SG or the air
purifier humidifier has been exposed.
Taking Joon Gu's personality and
his original plans into account
if he had a truth he really
wanted to reveal...
he would've saved it
for the last episode.
The pattern has been to get
the person to admit their crimes.
Then he would proceed to punish them.
The person in charge seven years ago
was President Ham Tae Seob.
He was in charge of SG Chemical
at the time.
That's right.
Ham Tae Seob's crimes.
They are what caused
the deaths of many people.
He killed people just to cover it up.
That was supposed to
be revealed in episode nine.
He may have intended to
punish them in episode ten.
But, his plans have gone awry.
His identity has been revealed.
He didn't send a mission to get
Ham Tae Seob on the show and confess.
He sent a mission to make sure
we proceed with the show.
Then, maybe Senior Hye In is right.
He might kill Ham Tae Seob on air.
There is a chance of that.
President Song sure is busy.
Where could he be
at such a critical time?
Yes, President!
This is Reporter Jang Jin Woong.
We've met before, right?
I had something to tell you,
but you're not here.
I met Executive Choi Joon Gu's
mother-in-law.
She has Hyun Woo right now.
She must feel guilty because she
opened up about everything
after a few questions.
She's coming tonight with
Hyun Woo at 7:00 p.m.
She's supposed to meet
Choi Joon Gu at Haneul Park.
I thought it would look great if
you made an appearance there.
That's why I'm telling you this.
I don't know what the heck I'm doing.
What is he up to?
Go into President Song's office
when he's not there.
Pretend you're talking
to him and just say it.
I heard you met my mother-in-law.
Use that and just say you heard
from my mother-in-law.
Say that my mother-in-law will be meeting
me at 7:00 p.m. in Haneul Park.
No one else can find out about this.
You don't need to know why.
Hi, Detective Park.
What are you doing
in President Song's office?
I went to interview him. What else?
He wasn't around.
You gave me files claiming that you
thought Shin Dong Wook was the culprit.
What are you up to?
You suspected Director Shin too.
I was just trying to help.
What's your relationship
with Choi Joon Gu?
Did you already know him?
Hey, why are you being like this?
Let's talk for a bit.
I... I don't have time.
Should I get a warrant and do
it officially, or should we just talk?
Let's go. Come on.
Just make it quick.
Kwon Kyung Hoon.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Where are you going?
We're going to meet that victim,
Han Ji Yeon.
I want to do a proper interview.
Why are you suddenly doing that?
I understand why Executive Director Choi
felt like he had to do this.
I feel like I could have been his wife.
Na Young Hyun could have been
my daughter or little sister.
So, what are you planning?
It's not like I can make
the dead come back to life.
But, I have to do something.
I'll turn Han Ji Yeon's interview into
a preview and put it up.
He'll see we're putting in an effort to
inform people about what happened.
You never know, he might
have a change of heart.
I'll go with you too.
I am sorry to my daughter, of course.
I was only trying to
do something good for her.
To make things clean.
To make her healthy.
But, it was my fault in the end.
I sent my daughter up to heaven.
Then I ended up with the same illness.
I'm suffering so much from this.
How did that young child...
They found a lung donor for me.
That made me feel crazy.
"Ah, I'm going to live. What a relief."
I thought that to myself.
I wondered to myself, am I even human?
What kind of mother am I?
I kept having those thoughts.
Do you know what I learned
over and over these last eight years?
I was so naive.
Even if I had made the show back then...
nothing would have changed.
Then what do we do to change things?
What is it that you want to do?
Hey. Wake her up.
Put your hands up and get on the ground!
Don't move, you punk!
I thought about it.
This might be uncomfortable for
you to talk about, Hye In.
If you look at everyone that's been
involved with the show so far
they are either victims or perpetrators
of what happened seven years ago.
That's true.
But, you're not directly tied to it.
You're connected because of
your late husband's death.
If you look at it that way,
you could be considered a victim.
But seeing as Hyun Woo was kidnapped,
that could be seen as a punishment.
I don't know what my crime is.
So, stop dragging other people into it
and expose my crime in the next mission.
Do it however you want to.
So that we can reach the conclusion
that you want even faster.
"You requested that
we expose your crime."
"We will grant that request
for the fourth mission."
"Your former husband did
not die in a car accident."
"Find out how he died."
You're right.
It was supposed to be
a mission to expose my crime.
But, he gave me a mission
regarding Tae Young.
He didn't say I had no crime.
Is there anything you're
hiding about that incident?
There's nothing.
I'm not even scared of exposing
anything I've done wrong.
I don't care about anything
as long as I can find Hyun Woo.
Then we need to know why
Executive Director Choi targeted you?
We need to know what he might
consider a crime in his eyes.
Think about it carefully.
If there happens to be an incident
on tonight's show
it could end up being the key in changing
Executive Director Choi's mind.
There hasn't been anyone who has
admitted fault on their own so far.
It has been quite hectic lately.
I was prepared to be stood up.
If I can't stand firm
at a time like this
what would happen to my company?
I suppose you're correct.
No matter how much noise
the ignorant people make
the king must stand firm
so the world can keep turning.
Thank you for saying that.
I'm only doing my job.
- Excuse me for a moment.
- Sure.
Wait out here.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Where is Hyun Woo?
How could you do that, Hye In?
I'll let you deliver Hyun Woo
to Hye In with your own hands.
So, let go of me and let's talk.
You want to know how I
could do that to Hye In?
What about you?
How do you think I found about
Hye In's retirement plans?
And all of those details?
What do you mean?
It was the hidden camera footage that
you sold to her stalkers online.
Park Sae Yong bought one of them.
That's how I found out about those
hidden cameras.
So, you have some responsibility in
Hyun Woo's kidnapping.
That's why I'm giving you a chance to
fix this yourself.
How?
You know President Ham Tae Seob
of SG Life?
He's meeting a congressman
for dinner tonight.
Kidnap him.
What does that have to do with Hyun Woo?
You need to get that done.
Also, don't tell anyone
until the show is over.
Then once the show ends...
I will tell you where Hyun Woo is.
That's when you can take him to Hye In.
How can I trust you?
Even Hye In manipulated me.
She hasn't contacted me even once.
It's your choice whether
or not you trust me.
This is your only chance to fix
your relationship with Jung Hye In.
The VIP guest is gone!
Check the parking lot.
Hey!
Everything on this show is real.
We are doing this show at the request of
the person who has kidnapped my son.
Jung Hye In's Wanted starts now.
[KEEP THIS SHOW ON THE AIR NO MATTER WHAT
IF YOU WANT HYUN WOO TO LIVE.]
We have two more missions left.
This is the ninth mission
sent by the kidnapper.
Do not stop the show.
That was it.
Hello!
Hey!
This is a video feed being sent
to us by the kidnapper
from an unknown location.
There is a person locked in
what looks to be a walk-in fridge.
Who, exactly, is this person?
And why has the kidnapper locked him up?
Is anyone out there?
Hey!
Turn on the sound.
Turn on the monitor.
There is a remote control there.
What is this?
Who are you!
Turn it on.
What do you think Jung Hye In
is feeling, standing there?
It's her son's kidnapper and
the man who murdered her husband.
She has to deal with them both at once.
Ham Tae Seob.
Are you okay?
When this program began,
the police started their search for you.
If you tell us the details
of your kidnapping
I believe it will help with the search.
I was in the restroom of the restaurant.
It was around 8:00 p.m.
I was attacked by a man dressed
in a cleaner's uniform.
Once I woke up, I was in here.
Do you remember his face?
He came up behind me when
I was washing my hands.
I only got a glance through the mirror
and he was wearing a mask
He wasn't that tall.
It happened so fast.
I don't have much more.
We would like to ask the police for help.
We hope that you can find him quickly
using Ham Tae Seob's statement.
I don't think this method
will help me find him in time.
He's using a server in Bangladesh.
I don't think Choi Joon Gu and Hyun Woo
are necessarily at
that refrigeration unit.
We need to find out where Hyun Woo or
Choi Joon Gu are first, not Ham Tae Seob.
The investigation will
focus on Ham Tae Seob.
This man that has been kidnapped and
confined in this video is...
President of SG Life, Ham Tae Seob.
The voice that came over the speakers to
demand Ham Tae Seob turn on the monitor
is the voice of the kidnapper
that took Hyun Woo.
He did not demand anything today,
except to continue on with the show.
Starting now, Ham Tae Seob
will have to tell the truth.
Jung Hye In.
Ask Ham Tae Seob anything
you're curious about.
Ham Tae Seob.
What do you think?
Why do you think the kidnapper has
brought you there and is doing this?
I'm very curious too.
I don't know why he's doing this to me.
Should we ask him about all
the missions starting from the first?
No, I don't think that's
what Joon Gu wants.
Jung Hye In.
Joon Gu didn't give you questions.
Think about why he told you to
ask what you're curious about.
What do you really want
to ask Ham Tae Seob?
We learned on the last episode.
SG hired Jo Nam Chul
to kill Ham Tae Young.
It's our theory that he was killed after
Ham Tae Young secretly met Na Jae Hyun.
Na Jae Hyun was looking into
the cause of his sister's
acute interstitial pneumonia.
He believed that it was the air purifier
humidifier produced by SG Chemical.
These documents show that he
informed Ham Tae Young.
Our team was able to obtain them.
Once Ham Tae Young found out about it
he followed his conscience
and admitted SG Chemical had done wrong.
He wanted a proper investigation
and to apologize.
He planned on compensating
those who were affected.
Now, I will ask Ham Tae Seob a question.
At that time, you were
the President of SG Chemical.
Did you have Ham Tae Young murdered
to cover up what your company did?
Are you saying that I...
You're saying that...
I would kill my little brother
over the company's profit?
That is too awful to even imagine.
How could I do that to my Tae Young?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Today's show isn't going to be easy?
Executive Director Choi wants
Ham Tae Seob to confess his crimes.
How will we get him to do it
if he's acting this way?
He probably knew that Ham Tae Seob
wouldn't admit to it.
Joon Gu must have expected that much.
At this rate...
he's going to do something rash if
Ham Tae Seob keeps denying it.
Let's not worry about Joon Gu
doing something rash.
We need to find a way
to shake up Ham Tae Seob.
We'll find a way to shake him
if we keep questioning him.
Something's been bothering me.
I'm bringing it up in case
you know something.
I saw Reporter Jang Jin Woong going
into President Song's office earlier.
I checked and it was empty.
He was in there too long
to check in on an empty office.
I think Na Soo Hyun and Lee Ji Eun
are Executive Director Choi's
only accomplices.
Even after Na Soo Hyun was exposed
he was the one who
still delivered the missions.
But, it would've been
hard for Choi Joon Gu
to kidnap Ham Tae Seob himself.
He could have used Jang Jin Woong
to get his plan accomplished.
President Song's office?
Did you get anything
from President Song's audio file?
No, there really much.
There's the study, bedroom,
and his office.
Those hidden cameras were
put there by Kwon Kyung Hoon.
- Jung Hye In's manager?
- Yes.
If Jung Hye In can persuade
Kwon Kyung Hoon one more time
then she might be able to find out
what Jang Jin Woong did.
[SG CHEMICAL, AIR PURIFIER HUMIDIFIER,
MURDER, KEEP REPEATING.]
I'll ask you one more thing.
Yesterday, the kidnapper made a demand.
We were told to reveal
that his accomplice Na Soo Hyun
was killed by SG Group.
Na Soo Hyun had a sister Na Young Hyun.
She died from the use of SG's humidifier.
Na Jae Hyun tried to expose this.
It is claimed that he was
killed by SG seven years ago.
That means that all three siblings
were killed due to SG Chemical.
Is this true?
Jung Hye In and the Wanted
team continue to keep this up.
You bring murder and conspiracy to
murder from seven years ago.
These are very serious
criminal accusations.
A child was kidnapped.
Then he held this child hostage
to get a show produced.
This man is a murderer who killed
several people in a matter of days.
Yet, you put his words on air
as if they are established facts?
Furthermore, I've been informed that
Executive Director Choi Joon Gu...
is the kidnapper.
I am very worried about
the adverse effects this show
will have on our society.
Can we really continue doing this show?
You do not verify the things
that the kidnapper tells you.
Then you repeat them on air.
And why did you not tell
people about Choi Joon Gu?
Is there any chance that there is another
accomplice on the broadcast team?
I would like to apologize to the viewers.
Like Ham Tae Seob has told you
we learned right after that show.
We found out the identity
of Hyun Woo's kidnapper.
It was Wanted's Executive Director,
Choi Joon Gu.
He is the kidnapper
who made this show happen.
We're in control of this.
Don't let Ham Tae Seob set the pace.
Make a clean apology and
get the atmosphere calm.
Of course...
I am still in shock from that trauma.
However, I am sure of one thing.
I am standing here
for Hyun Woo and his safety.
What is it?
I need to talk to Jung Hye In.
Okay, you can. Over here.
Jung Hye In, it seems that Jang Jin Woong
helped out Executive Director Choi today.
He went into President Song's office
and did something alone.
I think it was filmed
on the hidden camera
that Kwon Kyung Hoon put in there.
Do you think you can find out
from Kwon Kyung Hoon?
She's saying she's
going contact him, right?
Hold on.
Do we have other footage?
We can't turn off Ham Tae Seob.
- Turn on what we prepared.
- Okay.
I can give you five minutes.
Try to get it done by then.
Put up this caption.
"For the viewers listening to my
conversation with Ham Tae Seob"
"we will show you highlights
from episode one to eight."
Kyung Hoon.
You have important evidence that could
lead me to finding Hyun Woo.
Contact me as soon as possible.
[HYE IN]
You said you needed me last time too,
but you brought cops.
Then you never contacted me again.
I don't trust you anymore.
But, I still did something
very dangerous on your behalf.
I told you I'd bring Hyun Woo
to you, didn't I?
I think I'll be keeping
that promise tonight.
Did Executive Director Choi tell you
he'd give you Hyun Woo tonight?
He's lying. You're being used.
He told me he'd only give me proof
Hyun Woo's alive after the show.
He has no intention of giving Hyun Woo
back until the show ends tomorrow.
Tell me what you did.
Tell me where Executive Director Choi is.
That is how you'd
be finding Hyun Woo for me.
He's starting to get out of control.
Hyun Woo's in a lot of danger
and we have to find him now.
The highlights are ending soon.
Have you heard from him?
You have to go on soon. Get ready.
Let's counterattack.
I'll let you know right away if
Kwon Kyung Hoon makes contact.
Yes, please do.
Hello.
You have just seen highlights of Wanted
from episodes one to eight.
He kidnapped Hyun Woo.
Then Choi Joon Gu demanded
that we create this show.
What could he have wanted from this show?
I think it's time now...
I will ask Ham Tae Seob
the same question I first asked him.
Ham Tae Seob.
Why would the kidnapper
kidnap and confine you?
And then demand that
you tell the truth on live TV?
Why must I make speculations about
what the kidnapper is thinking?
I am a victim.
It is victims who often ask themselves,
"Why did this happen to me?"
They ask themselves that often.
This entire show has been about
the issues related to
SG's air purifier humidifier.
Whether it was talking about
what the victims suffered...
or punishing those who
tried to cover up the crimes.
In the end...
you were president of
SG Chemical at the time.
So, he wants to know how
you were responsible.
Don't you suppose that is
why the kidnapper did all of this?
Do you admit that there was a problem
with the air purifier humidifier?
You have been continuously
using the word victim.
You speak of the kidnapper's
claims as if they are facts.
Our product follows all
national standards and protocols.
It is a safe product.
Even if there are such allegations
we cannot say it is proven true
because of a few claims.
The people making these claims
should prove it scientifically.
Then we will investigate it
again very thoroughly.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Ham Tae Seob.
You claim that there is nothing wrong it.
Then you will be able
to leave this place safely.
What I am now releasing into
the air is in your product.
BHMG.
I am vaporizing it into the air now.
It is at a much stronger concentration
than when in a humidifier.
If there is a problem...
you will die and it will be proven.
But, if you admit
that there is a problem...
I will stop here.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Choi Joon Gu.
You are on live TV. Do you understand?
Many people are watching. Please stop.
Let's talk for now.
Do you think that's real?
It is the most sure way to prove it.
It's also a way to punish him.
Seriously, I wanted to stop
that from happening.
Gosh, what do we do?
I think Executive Director Choi
is there too.
He really intends to kill him.
He probably expected that
Ham Tae Seob wouldn't confess.
So, he would've had a plan B
in case it failed.
He must be nearby.
After he carries out his plan...
I think he might even kill himself.
Choi Joon Gu.
I understand how you feel.
You want to believe in any story
and you need someone to blame.
Those feelings...
those miserable feelings.
You just want to feel better.
After I leave this place
I will investigate that product
thoroughly, one more time.
I promise you that.
But, my nephew...
Our Hyun Woo.
Please let him go.
What has that young child done wrong?
Why would you use him
in a plot like this?
[SEONGSAN-DONG 98-1, BASEMENT]
I'll take care of things here.
Hurry up and go.
Lieutenant Cha, Kwon Kyung Hoo
contacted Hye In.
Stop airing this now.
Please leave.
I think you need to leave, Director Shin.
The police are asking for
cooperation and I agreed to it.
Put on any footage to replace the show.
Director!
Dong Wook, what is it?
What are you doing here
in the middle of your show?
Keep going.
Don't turn on anything else
whatever they send.
Just turn on what's coming from there.
Isn't that a problem?
Tell them that I threatened you.
Just let me finish this episode.
I heard that you have a lot
of debt due to production failures.
If you needed money badly enough
to make an issue out of
your wife and baby's death
Out of consolation...
I can personally help you.
Choi Joon Gu, let's meet.
We need to get him before the show ends.
Open up, Director Shin.
- Open up, Director Shin!
- You can't do this.
What are you planning to do?
Open up, would you?
Dong Wook!
Shouldn't we stop airing this?
Don't you dare stop.
Director Shin, open the door.
- You're going to be fired.
- What are you planning to do?
Hands up!
Put the knife down.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever