Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[EPISODE 15]
If Senior Joon Gu doesn't wake up...
how will we find Hyun Woo?
Bring Lee Ji Eun to the Seoul Express
Bus Terminal at midnight.
That's the only way...
you'll get proof that Hyun Woo is alive.
Lieutenant Cha, we need
to get Lee Ji Eun.
That call was to bring her
to the bus terminal by midnight?
Yes, we don't even have an hour left.
Just tell me where Lee Ji Eun is.
I'll go get her.
We don't have time now,
so we have to split up.
Go to the bus terminal without me.
I'll contact you.
[KIDNAP, IMPRISONMENT, AND MURDER]
Mother-in-law, bring Hyun Woo
to the Seoul Bus Terminal by midnight.
I don't think I'll be able to meet you.
I purposely didn't put a TV in the house,
so don't watch the show.
Just pack a few necessities.
You will have to leave with Lee Ji Eun.
If I don't call you by midnight
I want you to hide and call Jung Hye In.
Aren't you hungry? You're sleepy, right?
Hyun Woo.
I'm not going to take
you somewhere again.
I told you, right?
We're going to meet your mom.
There are lots of bad people,
so we need to meet here in secret.
I'm very sorry for everything.
He probably wanted Lee Ji Eun here
so she could run away
with his mother-in-law.
If that was really his goal,
was he really going to return Hyun Woo?
The proof that Hyun Woo is alive could
be Hyun Woo himself.
There are too many people here for that.
What was he planning to do here?
That's probably why he chose this place.
It's easy to hide here.
Then jump on a bus and run away.
- Yes, Senior.
- I'm here at the bus terminal.
Tell me if you need help and call me.
Okay. Be careful.
Who are you!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
That kid looks very familiar.
Those eyes... those eyes.
I know I've seen them before.
What's a grandma doing hiding
here with a kid at this hour?
Are you running away somewhere?
Wow! I just won the lottery.
No, you can't!
What are you doing?
Hyun Woo, run away!
Go where lots of people are!
Go find help!
Call your mom!
Lieutenant Cha!
Hello?
Jung Hye In?
Where are you?
Where is Hyun Woo?
He ran away on his own.
He ran into the Gyeongbu entry
of the Seoul Express Bus Terminal.
You have to find him now!
A homeless man ran after him.
I'm sorry.
I was going to
return him to you safely.
Hyun Woo!
Help me!
Help me.
Are you by chance... you are, right?
Wow! I just won the lottery.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Wait... wait.
Isn't that Jung Hye In?
Oh! Isn't that Jung Hye In?
It's Jung Hye In! What's going on?
Everyone!
I am Jung Hye In.
It's really Jung Hye In.
My son, Hyun Woo, is here right now.
My son is somewhere in
this building at this very moment.
Everyone, please help me.
The kidnapper was stabbed and
has been taken to the hospital.
His accomplice came to bring me Hyun Woo.
But, she was attacked by someone.
Now, Hyun Woo is all alone and
he's being chased by that person.
I'll go tell them to
make an announcement.
Thank you.
Please find Hyun Woo for me.
Hyun Woo is seven years old.
He's all on his own right now.
Please find Hyun Woo for me.
Please help me search for Hyun Woo.
We'll look for him.
Please search for him, everyone.
Please help me be the one to find him,
not someone else.
Please find him.
This is an announcement for everyone
in the Seoul Express Bus Terminal.
Jung Hye In's son, Song Hyun Woo,
is currently inside the terminal.
If you happen to find Song Hyun Woo
please return him safely to the
information desk immediately.
Neither Jung Hye In
or Lieutenant Cha are picking up.
Do you think the executive director
is okay?
We can go to the hospital.
I'll check to see which
hospital he's been taken to.
I don't know what I'm
supposed to be doing.
First, we should handle today's show.
People saw who the
kidnapper was live on air.
Director, Writer Yeon... look at this.
SG is going to try
to find Hyun Woo first.
We have to stop them. Get your cameras.
The bus terminal?
Yes, I sent our best
people there already.
I've instructed them to find him
and bring him in quietly.
- Song Hyun Woo!
- Hyun Woo!
Those people are from SG.
Keep your eyes on them.
Start filming if something
dangerous happens, can you do it?
I can do it.
They could take out our cameras,
so be careful when you're alone.
Okay.
- Hyun Woo!
We repeat one more time.
If anyone finds Song Hyun Woo,
please bring him to the information area.
Hyun Woo!
Mom!
Lieutenant Cha!
Senior, we found Hyun Woo,
but SG sent their people.
I'm bringing him out now.
Hye In, we need to get out of here.
SG's people are here.
Hyun Woo, can you run?
Jung Hye In!
Back off.
Arrest me, Lieutenant.
Where will you go now?
I should go home for now.
I'll take measures to keep you safe.
I have some work left to do.
Will you be okay with the broadcast team?
Thank you.
You're the one who found him.
Jung Hye In took the child.
The broadcast team
showed up with cameras.
I apologize.
Don't do anything with
the child until I give my orders.
Yes, sir.
What about my father?
He is in the waiting area having a
meeting with your older brother.
Call in the PR team,
SG Chemical Vice President
Ohsung, and the Section Chief
of Strategic Management.
Tell them all to come in here.
- Now.
- Yes, I will.
I should go to the station and
finish things up.
You should rest.
They're all retired cops,
but they'll protect you well.
I would use active police,
but I don't know who works for SG.
These people are trustworthy.
We'll protect this place.
You should go home. Go on in.
Thank you.
Let's go.
You know that you can't.
I'm asking as a favor.
I need to hear what he has left to say.
Wouldn't people who've been
watching need to hear from him too?
We've found Hyun Woo now.
Joon Gu wasn't just a kidnapper either.
You saw it too, Lieutenant Park.
Keep it quick.
I came for the show.
I'm here to film anything
more you have to say.
Did they find him? Did he meet Hye In?
It's all over now.
Forget it. I have nothing more to say.
Anything...
You can say anything.
Anything I have left to say
I should say to Hye In.
Should I call Hye In for you?
Hye In won't want to come.
Do you have any other evidence
beside what you already told us about?
You...
I'm not saying I'll put it on air.
I don't think the show you did today
is what you originally wanted.
I just wanted to confirm that.
There was a doctor that researched,
ran tests, and wrote his own report.
He had other evidence too.
We were supposed to meet three days ago,
but then I didn't hear from him.
He hadn't done anything wrong.
I didn't want to put him in danger.
A doctor?
Today in Bongdam, Hwaseong at 9:00 p.m.
a Mister Kim was
discovered in a reservoir.
What is that?
An area man discovered the body
and called the police.
Police and fire department were able
to recover him.
Is that him?
What the heck is that?
Police believe that he committed suicide
and are looking into the case.
Police also believe that Mister Kim was a
doctor at a hospital seven years ago.
He had disappeared suddenly
and could not be found.
His family has been told of his death.
Dong Wook.
Let me ask you for one last favor.
What is it?
Did you see that tape I gave you?
Here.
What is it?
You'll know when you see it.
This...
When you make a show about this
on your own later on...
please make sure to use this.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I saw it.
I made a mistake.
With what?
I said to you long ago that if I ever
asked you not to air something
I needed you to listen to me just once.
Do you remember that?
I remember.
Don't put that tape on air.
You asked me to put it on air.
I thought that I had to.
I think I was wrong.
Why is that?
People might watch it.
What if they pity my even
just a little bit?
What if they think I...
I don't think it'll be right if people
pardon me for what I've done.
I don't know about anything else.
I shouldn't have done that to Hyun Woo.
What I've done...
So, why?
You won't air that tape, right?
All right.
But, later on...
I might create something of my own.
I might use it then.
This is all I can do for you, Joon Gu.
Thank you.
He wasn't stabbed on purpose.
He was cut while they were fighting.
Then will he be okay?
Yes, he'll need treatment for a few days,
and he'll have to take care of himself.
The issue of Choi Joon Gu's
injuries are very clear-cut.
You will be asked a few questions
as a formality once you are better.
Get it over with as soon as possible.
Yes, I understand.
Come in.
- You can go.
- Okay.
Did that doctor have anything?
According to our investigations,
Kim Bong Joon had a report with proof.
On top of that
he has evidence that SG Chemical
knew tests had to be run
on the the PHMC toxicity.
He was in possession of that, as well.
And?
Where is that evidence now?
Well, that is...
What if the police or broadcast team
get their hands on it first?
Do you think you can fix it?
I will make sure nothing
like that ever happens.
Is this the end?
What about any other
plans or accomplices?
It was about a year ago.
He wouldn't sleep, day or night.
He was holed up in his room saying
he was going to make a bomb.
He ended up with a burn on
his hand and gave up.
What about the bomb Park Sae Yong
was making a year ago?
Is that not connected to this?
Park Sae Yong.
That was when he first met Mister Choi.
He found out that his mom was sick
because of that air purifying humidifier.
He was so angry that he tried
to make a bomb by himself.
But, he failed.
Mister met him and convinced him
with plans of doing this show.
How did you end up
getting involved in this?
Was it after Park Sae Yong kidnapped you?
You looked truly afraid in the video.
Soo Hyun, Mister Choi, and I
had been preparing for a long time.
As for the kidnapping,
I knew all about it.
But, I was so scared when the time came.
I started to doubt Mister
and Park Sae Yong.
I thought to myself...
is this really starting now?
How do you feel now?
Do you regret it?
I'm not really sure.
I'm sorry to Hyun Woo.
And Soo Hyun...
And Mister Choi...
Can you let me see him just once?
That's going to kind of difficult.
Hey, you crazy kid.
What are you doing here so late?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry I didn't do my job properly.
I'll kill you myself if
you go getting beat up again.
Okay.
Executive Director Choi's mother-in-law
got passed off to central headquarter.
The case is over.
There's no reason for us to keep her.
I know.
But, I think Lee Ji Eun
would be safer here.
I'd like to keep an eye on her if we can.
I don't know how much longer we can.
It's getting complicated to explain it.
Watch over her for today, at least.
- I have somewhere to go.
- Where?
I'll go with you, Senior.
It's a personal matter.
Is this by chance about...
Senior Sang Shik?
You can walk there, right?
We just need to run a few tests.
All right.
You can change into this
and come out over there.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I had some questions
for Executive Director Choi.
Isn't the case for
Detective Kim Sang Shik over with?
You should let go of it now.
Take care of yourself
and think about others too.
The changing room doors are locked
and Choi Joon Gu isn't coming back out.
Choi Joon Gu escaped
from the first floor window.
Call for back-up now and search now.
He can't have gone far.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Then we need to know why
Executive Director Choi targeted you?
We need to know what he might
consider a crime in his eyes.
Think about it carefully.
I'm sorry, baby.
Sorry, baby.
[LIEUTENANT CHA SEUNG IN]
Look at your swollen eyes.
Why pick a fight if
you're going cry like that?
You're the one who called
all night pestering me.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Trying to make the swelling go down.
It's so cold.
You have to eat all of this.
You said you have to work all night.
Yes.
- Let's get married.
- Okay.
Huh?
Let's get married already.
Let's not fight all night on the phone.
Let's fight face-to-face.
But...
What kind of proposal is this,
over a meal at this place?
What?
Should we go to a sky lounge, get an
orchestra, get on my knee with a diamond?
Is that what you want?
Yes.
No, I hate that stuff.
Just like we're eating rice here now...
let's live a simple and natural life.
I know it will be hard for either of us
to live in that way.
We both want it more than anyone else.
Finish eating. I'll drive you.
You know, Tae Young.
You have some cheesy lines.
I didn't think you'd be the type.
Jung Hye In.
There's a Han Ji Yeon here to see you.
I need to talk you about something.
I need to talk to you.
Mom.
Come here, Hyun Woo.
Why did you wake up?
You should sleep more.
Because you weren't there.
Is someone here?
No, no. Go back to sleep.
I'll go back in with you. Hold on.
I'm sorry. Please go.
Hyun Woo is still very nervous.
Hyun Woo is my priority right now.
I realize that.
I know how you must be feeling.
I came because I had no choice.
Please see me just once.
Mom.
Hyun Woo.
These are people who helped protect us.
It's okay.
I'll be right in so wait inside.
Choi Joon Gu escaped.
Lieutenant Cha called you right away,
but he couldn't reach you.
I thought you should know.
I'll be right out front.
Call me if you need me.
Thank you.
It was not long ago.
I heard from the man who
was my daughter's doctor.
There was six patients of his
that all shared the same room.
They all had the same symptoms.
Besides me...
everyone else has died.
Han Ji Yeon.
I asked to meet him.
But, he wouldn't tell me where he was.
He seemed very anxious,
like he was being chased.
Then, this morning...
he was discovered dead in a reservoir.
I saw the video of you finding Hyun Woo.
I thought it's all over now.
It was hard for me to find this place,
but I did and I came.
Han Ji Yeon, please listen to me.
For the very last time...
please do one more episode.
You can do it, Hye In.
The people helped you find Hyun Woo.
People who are dying...
People who are in hiding...
People who don't even know
that they are victims...
You can help all those people, Hye In.
I...
I can't do it.
I've only been doing it all this time
because of Hyun Woo.
I'm scared too.
I'm exhausted now and I'm tired.
I'm sorry.
I have to protect Hyun Woo now.
I'm going to leave this place.
Hye In.
I'm sorry.
What has the PR team decided to do?
Choi Joon Gu's escape
works to our advantage.
We're going make a bigger issue
out of Choi Joon Gu.
Delusions of grandeur,
kidnapping, murder.
And he escaped his arrest.
He has a grudge against society.
We plan on focusing on claims that
he is planning a terror attack.
Then the acts he committed last night
will tie-in as acts of terror against SG.
Then in this case,
do not respond to the air purifier.
It would be better to stay silent.
That's correct.
Use this strategy and use
the stations to get it done.
Yes, sir.
Mister Choi, who had this nation in shock
for ten days was arrested yesterday.
However, he managed to escape from the
hospital while receiving treatment.
Police say that he was bitter about his
situation and resentful toward society.
It appears that it was an act of terror
on a top star and the wealthy.
Police also believe that he escaped in
order to commit another act of terror.
They are investigating using
all available methods.
Choi Joon Gu.
Where is he?
What did you two talk about?
What we talked about is on the camera.
I don't know where he is either.
[CHOI ESCAPES FROM HOSPITAL]
I know it's right
that the police catch him.
SG won't let him get away
with it either though.
What is he planning to do?
He's been stabbed and
he needs to get it treated.
That could be a big problem too.
Do you have news
on Executive Director Choi?
No, do you have anything from his files
that he didn't use for the show?
We can figure out why he escaped.
That's the only method.
There's a lot that he didn't use,
but they're all similar.
Most of them are interviews with victims
he wanted to use for his documentary.
There are some whistle blowers
and people who tried to help.
[DETECTIVE KIM SANG SHIK]
Have you seen this tape?
No, we haven't seen that one.
We have so many to go through and
we had covered him in an episode so...
Can I see this now?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Let's be together everyday like this
once we go to France.
- Hye In.
- Yes?
It's nothing.
Wait here.
What is this?
You're in a rush.
This won't fit the baby for a long time.
Also, what if it's a boy?
That's why... tada!
Oh, it's so cute.
You have to put these shoes on our
daughter on her first birthday.
Okay.
Tell her it's the first pair
of shoes that her dad bought.
You have to tell her.
What is this?
You can put them on for her
and tell her yourself.
Right, I can.
And why do you keep saying daughter?
If it's a son, his feelings
might be hurt.
Why do you need to film this?
Move that thing, would you?
I can't focus with that thing around.
I have to keep a record of everything.
If anything were to happen to me,
this is the only way to tell the story.
I'll go and park the car at a distance.
You should leave.
How can I send you there on your own?
Gosh, just don't get in my way.
Those guys... they're scary people.
Ko Hyung Joon said Im Hyung Soon
was an informant.
He didn't go because he didn't
think he should pursue this case?
That's right.
That guy is calculating.
According to what you found out
Im Hyung Soon and Jo Nam Chul
are working together.
There's something called
a hunting website.
It connects people to hit men.
Im Hyung Soon made that site.
I think he made it to con people,
in the beginning.
The money was so good.
So, he got Jo Nam Chul
to really kill people.
They didn't know each other before that?
Yeah.
But, once he actually witnessed it
I think he thought he might
get killed too and got scared.
He wants to run to another country
and become an informant.
You said that SG sent someone
who gave you a warning.
Even if it's not SG,
that stuff is common.
Then this could be a trap.
Even if it is a trap,
I won't be able to catch them otherwise.
That's why I'm going.
Then call up your team members
and go with them.
If Seung In finds out,
it will be a big problem.
That kid will walk through fire.
Suppose they do get caught,
it will still be a long battle.
That kid is just starting out.
I don't want this to
get in the way of his future.
What about you, Detective?
I already found out about it.
Things already worked out this way.
There's nothing I can do now.
I am a detective, after all.
I'm a person whose job
it is to do these things.
Are you planning to go somewhere?
I'm going to the broadcast station.
Something came up that I need to do.
It isn't safe to go anywhere now.
Do you have to go?
This is something that I started.
So, I should finish it.
I'll drive you.
Hyun Woo.
I'm going to step out for a little bit.
You can stay here with
these aunties, right?
Can't I come with you?
I'm sorry.
I'll be back very soon.
But, I'm scared.
Right outside, the policemen that you
like are protecting you too.
Stay here with your aunties for a
little while, okay?
I'll be back very soon.
Yeah, Hyun Woo. I'll stay here with you.
It's okay here. It's safe.
Go on. It won't be long, right?
Of course, not.
I'll just be ten minutes at the cafe.
Thank you.
Hyun Woo.
Hye In.
I'm sorry.
What about Hyun Woo?
Don't even say Hyun Woo's name.
I really am sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
After you kidnapped Hyun Woo
I thought about it
every day for hours.
Why me?
Why my Hyun Woo?
Why did something like this happen to us?
Is it really because
I've done something wrong?
Did I do something even worse than
the people who've been on our show?
I...
I was too severe, but...
I had no other choice.
You were the only one who could do it.
When I continued thinking about it...
I did have a sin.
I did.
Why is this something you have to do?
You made a promise to me.
Once I got pregnant,
we wouldn't tell your family.
We would move to France right away.
You said you didn't want our child
growing up lonely like you did.
You didn't want him growing up
among those monsters.
I'm not the one who said it.
It was you who said those things.
Hye In!
I've been acting since I was seven.
There's no one in this country
who doesn't know me.
That kind of life...
I'm throwing away everything
I've grown accustomed to.
You said you wanted to live a life
that we really want.
You said my entire life has
been fake and it was wrong.
You're the one who made me think it,
so how can you do this now?
We agreed to meet, Ham Tae Young.
Ham Tae Young!
You're all I have, you know that!
You're the only one who can do this.
You're the only one who can
investigate and apologize for this.
You're the one who can rescue people
who don't know anything and are dying.
Please.
Ham Tae Young!
I know you can do it. Please.
You... you promised me you would.
You don't know anything for sure.
Nothing has been confirmed.
You don't know if they're
telling you the truth or not.
You could be getting fooled.
I should be looking into
whether or not that's true!
Hye In... I just need three months.
Everything I promised you...
like going to France and living happily.
We will do all of that.
Then tell me what's going on.
Let's do it together. Help me understand.
No.
This is my task.
I have to be responsible for it.
Make a choice.
Is it me and the baby?
Or those people you don't know?
Okay.
Tae Young.
I'm scared.
I feel like something
bad might happen to you.
Okay.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Back then...
Ham Tae Young had agreed
to be on our side
and help us with everything.
He brought all the files
and came to see me.
He was going to take responsibility.
He was going to do
a proper investigation.
And reveal the truth about it all.
I'm sorry.
I think I made a mistake.
My wife is pregnant.
If something happens to me...
my family who doesn't even treat her
like a human being will take the baby.
They will use the child as a pawn
or take the child away.
It will be one or the other.
Tae Young.
That won't be a problem if
we can do this right.
Also...
you should think about everyone
who lost loved ones so unfairly.
Ham Tae Young, you have a
responsibility for that too.
I know, but still...
I am sorry.
I can't let this happen.
I can't tell my wife about this
or drag her into this.
She is getting so worried.
Ham Tae Young.
I think this is all I can do.
Please tell Na Jae Hyun that I'm sorry.
I didn't know Tae Young did that.
Then he went to meet Na Jae Hyun.
And died.
I didn't even know Tae Young was trying
to expose something like this.
He didn't want you involved in it.
Why?
In order to protect you.
- Are you okay?
- Jung Hye In!
I have something to tell you!
You have to listen, Jung Hye In.
It's about the death of Ham Tae Young!
You're the only one who can do it.
The only person who can help expose this,
the only one who has to do it is you!
You're the only one, Jung Hye In.
Jung Hye In, Jung Hye In!
I need to talk you, please! Jung Hye In!
Driver, please go. I'll miss my flight.
- Yes.
- Jung Hye In!
Please listen to what I have to say.
You're the only one who can do it!
Jung Hye In!
Jung Hye In, Jung Hye In!
That person was...
Na Soo Hyun?
I may realize what I did wrong.
You...
have suffered more than enough, Hye In.
I was much too severe.
It wasn't just about what you did.
I needed you.
The work that Ham Tae Young started...
I wanted you to do it.
I have no intention
of apologizing to you.
I'm not looking for redemption either.
When I think about what
you did to my Hyun Woo...
I can't forgive you. even if I die.
Senior.
You need to pay for your crimes now.
As for me...
I'm going to do what I can.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
We have to do the tenth episode.
Getting Ham Tae Seob on
the show will be impossible.
Help me with today's show.
You know Ham Tae Seob's weakness.
Tell me.
Let me interview Hyun Woo about what
happened during that week.
We came to see if we
could be of any help.
Won't SG have to admit
the truth if we use this?
Stop the broadcast using any
necessary measures.
Even if we have to throw away UCN.
Executive Director Choi!
Let's do our best. It's our last episode.
Jung Hye In's Wanted is starting now.