Subtitles by DramaFever
I have no intention
of apologizing to you.
I'm not looking for redemption either.
When I think about what
you did to my Hyun Woo...
I can't forgive you even if I die.
Senior.
You need to pay for your crimes now.
As for me...
I'm going to do what I can.
Suppose they do get caught,
it will still be a long battle.
That kid is just starting out.
I don't want this to get
in the way of his future.
What about you, Detective?
I already found out about it.
Things already worked out this way.
There's nothing I can do now.
I am a detective, after all.
I'm a person whose job it is
to do these things.
Wait, wait. Hye In.
I... what do I do?
I never meant to hurt
people in the beginning.
There is one last thing I have to do.
It can't end like this.
Lieutenant Cha.
You have to catch
Executive Director Choi.
You have to.
You can do that, right?
I will.
If Senior is trying to do
one last thing...
I hope that he can do it.
What he was originally planning to do...
I hope he can achieve that.
I should finish things off too.
That's why I'm going
to do the tenth episode.
Where are you now?
Let's meet and talk in person.
I'll come up to the waiting room.
Hye In.
This moment right now...
please do not make me regret it.
[Final Episode]
Will you be okay?
It won't be easy going back on TV.
Honestly, I'm scared.
You don't have to do it.
No.
I have to do it.
It's not your fault, Hye In.
When I was pregnant with Hyun Woo...
When my husband passed away...
When I felt like Hyun Woo
and I would be in danger
and I announced my retirement.
I was always running away.
I can't run away now.
If I run now...
I'm not sure I can ever escape this.
There are some things you can't
escape without getting hurt.
I will catch Choi Joon Gu.
Tell me if you need help with anything.
I heard from a victim of
the air purifier humidifier.
Not long ago...
I heard from the man who
was my daughter's doctor.
Then, this morning...
he was discovered dead in a reservoir.
Can you look into that doctor?
I was wondering if SG killed him.
It's a recent event so it could
be quite harmful to them.
I'll do that.
I came for the show.
I'm here to film anything
more you have to say.
Forget it. I have nothing more to say.
I'm not saying I'll put it on air.
I don't think the show you did today
is what you originally wanted.
I just wanted to confirm that.
There was a doctor that researched,
ran tests, and wrote his own report.
He had other evidence too.
We were supposed to meet three days ago,
but then I didn't hear from him.
He hadn't done anything wrong.
I didn't want to put him in danger.
A local resident discovered
the body and called the police.
What the heck is that?
Is there anything else you didn't film?
Did he know where
that doctor was staying?
No.
Tell me the truth.
If he escaped to find that evidence
he could be in danger of SG Group.
Han Ji Yeon's daughter's doctor was
also Choi Joon Gu's wife's doctor.
He had evidence to use against
the air purifier humidifier.
But, he's been missing
for over seven years.
He died only a few days ago.
He's been on the run from SG Group.
He saw Wanted and agreed to give
the evidence over to Choi Joon Gu.
He's also been contacting victims
like Han Ji Yeon.
He was looking into the current situation
and got exposed somehow.
This is from the time Han Ji Yeon's
daughter was getting treated.
This is the family contact information
for his patients with similar symptoms.
Let's meet them all one at a time.
I called them all and they
don't want to meet with us.
They don't believe that
the doctor committed suicide.
They're afraid.
They've already been through a lot.
It's too much to handle.
This person.
He's the only one who's willing to meet.
[Kim Tae Kyung]
Let's do episode 10.
Why do you want to do it?
Because of Executive Director Choi?
I can't say that's not why.
But, that's not the entire reason why...
We should do it.
I don't think we should
end it like this either.
I don't agree with his methods
But, the issue of
the air purifier humidifier...
It's been covered up all this time.
If we don't let people know now,
it will be covered up again.
I think we have that responsibility too.
We showed such harsh things
on the air all this time.
If we stop now because we found Hyun Woo
then we really were just
manipulating them for the show.
But...
do you think Senior Hye In would do it?
She's found Hyun Woo now and
it's been so hard on her.
We need to a tenth episode.
We just made that decision too.
Let's get Ham Tae Seob on the show.
Let's prove that he conspired to murder.
We need to get him to admit the issue
with the air purifier humidifier too.
It won't be easy.
That's why the executive director
made the choices he did.
We can't use the same tactics as before.
This time we're not following
anyone's orders.
We're doing it on our own.
Have you thought about what kind
of show you want to make?
Connect this to the TV.
Are... are you okay?
I have to film this.
This is the only thing I can think of.
There's nothing else I can do.
I... I...
I'll make sure to find out
why this is happening to you.
Why this is suddenly happening to you...
You have oxygen
so why can't you breathe?
Is there something wrong with this
hospital or is it something else?
I'm going find out.
Just hold on a little longer.
I will find out for you.
You and our baby...
I'll save you both.
Hold on a little longer.
She went into premature labor.
The baby died right away
of the same illness.
His wife died right away too.
I wasn't saying we should do the last
episode to tell Senior Joon Gu's story.
Neither was I.
This won't go on the air.
It will be different than
the rest of our episodes.
What Joon Gu wanted people to know...
the murders committed by SG and
the air purifier humidifier.
I'll tell it the way Joon Gu would.
The way he wanted to tell it originally.
I'll do it like that.
No, that won't be enough.
I need your style, Dong Wook.
I still do.
She's not wrong.
To educate people,
you have to get their interest first.
We can't give Ham Tae Seob
a way out either.
It needs to be completely unexpected,
just like what we've done so far.
Hello?
The phone has been cloned.
[Myungjin Hospice Lee Jung Hee]
Thanks.
Executive Director Choi, don't do this.
Turn yourself in.
You're putting yourself in danger.
I don't have anything left to protect.
Why does it matter if I'm in danger?
What is that?
Take care of yourself.
We're going to do the show.
Even Lieutenant Cha agreed to help out.
You don't need to go to these lengths.
I should finish what I started.
All this time...
I've put you all in so much danger.
I'm sorry.
I should get going now.
- Director Shin will be looking for me.
- Okay.
It will be almost impossible to get
Ham Tae Seob on our show.
He was kidnapped and nearly murdered.
It will come out as self-defense,
but he did stab a man on live TV.
Also, it's obvious that he'll get
attacked if he comes on our show.
If Joon Gu hadn't done that yesterday,
we would have a chance.
I don't think it's completely impossible.
Yesterday, I think Ham Tae Seob
believed he knew the public very well.
He believes he can control
them however he wants to.
From what I've seen
while married to Tae Young
he's good at hiding his emotions.
He's all about maintaining his image.
He's never failed at
anything in his life.
Then you have to use
that confidence against him.
You can get him to appear
if you hurt his image a lot.
He won't be able to handle
his image being destroyed.
He'll want to resolve it himself and
he believes that he can resolve it.
Still, how can we come up
with an issue that big?
Theories or claims are not good enough.
I have something.
It won't do any good as legal evidence.
I have something good enough
to stir up the public.
Maybe Tae Young was worried that
something would happen to him.
He left an audio file of a conversation
he had with Ham Tae Seob.
I found it yesterday.
[June 2009, Real conversation between
Ham Tae Seob and Ham Tae Young]
You have to do a proper investigation!
Do you know how many people
rely on SG to make a living?
You don't know anything for sure.
Yet, you want to start investigating,
give money, and compensate?
It won't be just that product.
All of SG's products will suffer.
People have died!
More people can die
if they continue to use it.
Ham Tae Young! Tae Young...
You're my little brother.
I know you better than anyone.
You grew up like a fine prince.
Suddenly, you're all about justice
and playing hero.
Sure, I can overlook
that as a cute thing.
So, I won't do a thing to you.
What?
However, others will get hurt if you
continue to keep this up.
That boy you met, Na Jae Hyun?
He's still young.
The air purifier is just
one way a person can die.
If that boy ends up dying,
it's all because of your actions.
Do not... touch him.
Don't tell me what I can and cannot do!
I... am Ham Tae Seob.
Before I am your brother,
I am the successor to SG Group.
You are the one who
take orders from me.
[Wanted Preview!!! Exclusive Conversation
Between Ham Tae Seob and Ham Tae Young]
He killed a person over the air purifier?
Does that make sense?
- Is he crazy?
- Is this for real?
I'm speechless. I'm speechless.
He's a total criminal.
[We are not even in people in his eyes.]
[I guess Ham Tae Young was killed by SG.]
SG has released an official statement
regarding Wanted.
They had no other choice
to find Song Hyun Woo.
The show was used for a personal matter.
They were forced by the kidnapper to air
a show that was destructive to society.
They would like to
apologize to the nation.
Now that Song Hyun Woo has been found,
they will no longer be airing the show.
Bring him out, bring him out!
Bring Ham Tae Seob out here!
Compensate the victims!
Compensate, compensate!
Murderer, leave this place.
Leave, leave!
Police should investigate immediately!
Investigate, investigate!
Bring Ham Tae Seob out here!
Kim Tae Kyung?
I'm Lieutenant Cha Seung In
from the Gangnam station.
Did you contact anyone after hearing
from Doctor Kim Bong Joon?
I got a little angry at the doctor.
I said why does it matter
when they're already dead.
That's how our call ended.
I got a call from someone
named Lee Jung Hee.
What did she say?
She said she lost her family too.
She said we should do something now
while the issue was on TV.
She asked if I would help her
if she took action first.
Did you meet her?
No.
Do you know her contact info?
I was more afraid because I didn't know
who she was so we stopped speaking.
When she introduced herself,
she said she worked at Myungjin Hospice.
Until we say so...
no one can leave this place.
Look through the list of all
the employees and patients.
Why... why are you doing this?
We're going to call the police.
Go ahead.
We're working with the police right now.
Stop right there!
Get her!
Is there an employee named Lee Jung Hee?
Yes.
Those men just chased her off.
Back off. Let her go.
Move.
Where is it?
I don't know.
How do you know what I'm talking
about to even say no? Huh?
Stop!
Lee Jung Hee!
Lee Jung Hee.
We lost her.
The evidence is either
with her or Choi Joon Gu.
Are you positive this
evidence even exists?
Seeing as how Choi Joon Gu and that
detective both came to that place...
I am sure of it.
Watch over the broadcast team
to see if they get their hands on it.
Do whatever you have to do
to stop that show.
Even if we must discard UCN.
I understand.
I'm Reporter Jang Jin Woong,
I called you.
- Hello.
- Sorry for being late.
I'm going to start with
some basic questions.
Seven years ago...
you suddenly quit your job as
Ham Tae Seob's driver.
- Yes.
- Why did you quit?
I hear it's a great job.
Ham Tae Seob is known for
being good to his employees.
It's hard for me to talk to you about it.
I signed a confidentiality agreement.
Even though I no longer work there,
I'm not supposed to talk about it.
Hey, why are you being that way?
You came to meet me, didn't you?
So why be like this?
Do you want something from me?
Should I give you something
in return for the interview?
I think I made a mistake.
You gave up and left seven years ago.
Then something happened back then.
You saw something, right?
Hi! You must be Hyun Woo.
Do you want to talk to me?
Get out.
Let me interview Hyun Woo about
what happened during that week.
He's the only one who knows what
went on with the kidnappers.
Get lost.
I'm not asking to do it for nothing.
Is Ham Tae Seob coming on the show?
You just revealed that preview,
so now what are you going to do?
Aren't you bringing him on the show
hoping to get more solid evidence?
I don't need your help so get lost.
Oh, okay.
I'll leave.
Maybe I should tell SG first then.
Don't ever mess with Hyun Woo.
One hour once this show is over.
An exclusive interview.
What I have is...
Dong Wook.
You know the reports that
Doctor Kim Bong Joon made?
There's a person who has them.
She's a woman named Lee Jung Hee.
She's a victims family member.
She got stabbed by people from SG.
I dropped her off at Jinsung Hospital.
Get over here now.
Writer Yeon, I think I can get evidence.
There's a witness at
Jinsung Hospital's ER.
Call the police.
Tell them she was passed out
by the ER with a stab wound.
It could create problems
for us if we don't report it.
Yes, okay.
Squad Car 390. Get to the hospital.
We'll be right there.
Yes, Lieutenant Choi.
We've found Lee Jung Hee.
She was admitted to the ER
at Jinsung Hospital.
They called in a stab wound patient.
The patrol unit are going there now.
Take care of it properly.
Lee Jung Hee.
I know Executive Director Choi.
- The evidence from Kim Bong Joon...
- Are you her guardian?
I am.
What's your relationship to her?
I'm her friend.
We got a call about a victim of a crime.
We have a few questions to ask.
Can you give us some time alone with her?
Why don't you let her get treated first
and then ask your questions?
There are procedures to follow.
Don't get in the way of our jobs.
And which procedures would
you be speaking of?
What brings you here, Lieutenant Choi?
This is an investigation
for a local police unit.
What is Violent Crimes Unit doing here?
Someone called in a favor.
Hey! Put the camera down.
It seems like some important
things might be said.
Cha Seung In, what are you doing here?
She's an important witness
in one of my cases.
I'll handle the investigation,
so you can leave.
You shouldn't fight against
just anyone like that.
Stay out of it. We'll handle it.
Why don't you two stay out of it?
What!
I'm not going to treat you differently
because you're my seniors.
I'll put in an investigation request to
find out how you ended up on this case.
Unless you think SG will have
your backs on that...
you should back off now.
I told you to stop filming!
How did you know to come here?
Writer Yeon called me.
You know when Ham Tae Seob
took you and spoke to you?
Tell me everything in great detail.
Do you think you can do that?
Yes.
Doctor Kim Bong Joon is an expert in
disease control and epidemiology.
While working in disease control,
he consulted Ha Dong Min for help.
Ha Dong Min denied the truth and said the
cause of death was something else.
He is pretty amazing.
He was alone and on the run from SG.
Yet, he was working with researchers
from foreign countries.
And he was running tests on his own.
It refutes Professor Kim Woo Jin's paper.
Isn't this enough to make
SG admit the truth?
SG won't admit it.
They will do whatever they can
to get out of it.
Still, we can use this to fight back.
I want you to use this
to write your script.
Since he can't be a witness,
stay on point but give out information.
Okay.
We wondered if we could help,
so we came here.
So, you've been sick for over two years.
You never knew why?
That's right. I had no idea.
The insurance company said they
would come and look into it.
I left it to them.
They only came up with a few
possibilities for what it could be.
I only found out
after I saw this TV show.
I have a favor to ask all of you.
Something besides the interview?
Yes, if you agree to it.
Let's get a divorce.
We should have done it a long time ago.
I haven't done anything right either.
All I have done is use you, Jung Ho.
But...
But, what?
For one last time,
let's use each other.
Help me with today's show.
You know Ham Tae Seob's weakness.
Give it to me.
What can you give me?
This station is about to
be destroyed because of you.
All of my UCN stock.
I'll give you all of them.
Are you confident you'll win?
I don't know.
If you've picked a fight,
make sure to destroy them completely.
Don't do a half-hearted job and
make me suffer too.
I'll give it a try.
Okay.
This is the best ending we can have.
Our show will be starting soon.
We all started it for a different reason.
And we're all doing this last tenth
episode for different reasons too.
That's why...
I'll do whatever I need in order
to find Hyun Woo.
Whatever your reason is,
just make this show happen.
I'm curious.
Is a TV show like this really possible?
This show pays a lot of money
and I really need that money.
Yes, I will be very responsible.
I will work very hard so that
we find Hyun Woo for sure!
The reason I want to do
this episode is still the same.
How will this show influence people,
and how far can we go?
I still want to test that.
Director.
Now that we've found Hyun Woo...
we have one thing left with this show.
The people who've lost
their family so painfully.
They went so far as to kidnap and murder
in order to tell people the truth.
People died because of
an air purifier humidifier.
Some people are sick and dying without
even knowing the reason why.
Ham Tae Seob needs to come on the show.
Once we do the show the way we want,
how will people react?
How much strength can a TV show have?
I'm curious about that.
Will we each get what
we want out of this?
Let's all do our very best.
Because, it is our last episode.
I'll forgive you if you read this to me.
- This part.
- Again?
How many times is it now?
You must've memorized it by now.
"Edmund walked by his side
and said to Peter."
"Everything will be okay."
"Peter, we'll be able to knock
Miraz down in one blow, right?"
"Peter replied to him calmly."
"I'm fighting in order to find that out."
You just need to wait a little longer.
Are you okay?
You've waited a long time, right?
Wait just a little longer.
Right now...
they're looking through the house
where Choi Joon Gu lived with his wife.
Also, his mother-in-law's home
and the charnel house.
It's these three places.
It could be one those three places.
Still, I want you to look around.
- Yes, okay.
- Okay.
Everything on this show is real.
We have been doing this show at the
request of the kidnapper who took my son.
However, we plan on revealing
a shocking truth to the viewers today.
That is why we are doing this show today.
Jung Hye In's Wanted is starting now.
Yesterday night...
I finally...
found my son, Hyun Woo.
Ham Tae Seob will be going on soon.
Guests will be going in and out quickly,
so be on your toes.
Yes, Lieutenant Oh. It's starting.
Please come on in.
We played an audio file for you
as our preview.
It is a conversation that my late husband
Ham Tae Young had with Ham Tae Seob.
After the preview was released
Ham Tae Seob let us know that he
wanted to explain the situation himself.
How could he do that?
He's putting on a show.
After making us this way?
First, regarding Song Hyun Woo...
No, I mean Ham Hyun Woo
and the issue of the birth father
I apologize to everyone for
the inconvenience it has caused.
At SG, we used all means possible
and wanted to find out the truth.
Jung Hye In, don't try to get the truth
or refute anything he says.
We're going create a situation
that Ham Tae Seob can control.
Therefore, I will take measures so
that my honor is not destroyed.
We have heard Ham Tae Seob's
side of the story.
Regarding the accusation of conspiring
to murder Na Jae Hyun and Ham Tae Young
I take that to mean you deny it.
We have a witness in
the studio to testify
she was kidnapped by Ham Tae Seob.
What are you...
He seemed to have a fear of germs.
Replay that scene
of Ham Tae Seob's reaction.
Viewers know he's pretending to
be weak because of the audio preview.
But, it's still fun for them to see it.
Okay.
Only question Lee Ji Eun.
She has to cut him off
before he counterattacks with
the accusation that we saved Lee Ji Eun.
If he realizes that we're running
the show, he'll squirm in his seat.
Okay.
Only question Lee Ji Eun.
Lee Ji Eun.
Two nights ago...
you were attacked by some men
and locked in a basement?
Yes.
What does that have to do with me?
The next morning...
a man came into the basement and
demanded to know where Hyun Woo was.
I didn't answer him and he ordered
the other men to beat me.
Is it this man sitting here?
It is.
Are you willing to testify that
in a court or to the police?
Yes.
This show has not changed at all.
You said a shocking truth
would be revealed.
You have not confirmed facts
and there is no evidence.
You come to conclusions using
the claims of a criminal.
Your evidence has arrived!
I thought I should keep my
mouth shut forever and live.
I saw the show yesterday.
Then I was watching my daughter sleep.
I thought this isn't right.
Use it for something good.
I did something good, huh?
Let me ask you one thing.
Ask.
This would be a huge exclusive article
if you wrote it and put it up.
Why would you bring it to me?
Gosh, you still don't know me.
Here.
That's Executive Director Choi's chapter.
I'm going to get an exclusive
and write it.
Check the very back. Look.
You see my chapter, right?
The critical piece of evidence I bring,
how will it affect the show?
How will it help catch Ham Tae Seob?
That is the highlight of this book!
Lee Ji Eun is currently under arrest.
The police will do a thorough
investigation of Lee Ji Eun's crimes.
At the same time...
we will also start an investigation
in the kidnapping
and confinement of Lee Ji Eun.
Once the investigation starts
and we have the results
we will make an announcement as well.
I will pay for the crimes
I have committed.
I'll be atoning for it my whole life.
That, alone, makes me
a better person than you.
Turn on the video.
Why did you change your mind?
You told Director Choi that
you wouldn't be doing it.
If I don't do it, no one will.
My company will never admit to it.
It will turn into a long fight.
The victims will just keep getting hurt.
What about your wife and baby?
Ham Tae Seob is shaken up right now.
Jung Hye In, listen to me
and don't think about anything.
We've informed everyone about
everything to do with this now.
We've exposed who Ham Tae Seob is too.
That's what it's been about so far.
Don't forget the goal of this show.
It's important to make Ham Tae Seob
admit it in front of the viewers.
That's the only way to make him admit
he was covering up the humidifier issue.
Ham Tae Seob.
Seven years ago, Ham Tae Young
wanted to expose the truth.
You wanted to cover up the truth
about the issue with the humidifiers.
Did you hire people to kill
Ham Tae Young and Na Jae Hyun?
No, I did not.
You only have speculation
and no evidence.
How can you even prove that the voices
in that video are their voices?
People like us get two
or three levels of insurance.
For example, something like this.
President Ham Tae Seob.
We know you're our client.
It's not going to work for us if you
stay hidden while we do dangerous work.
You only let us talk to your employees.
I thought I'd give you a report of
what happened myself.
Get to the point.
I took care of Na Jae Hyun.
I was only going to scare
Ham Tae Young like you said.
He ran in there to save Na Jae Hyun.
I had no choice.
He saw our faces too.
Too bad. Look here, Ham Tae Seob.
Are you listening?
I'll send someone.
Make it look like an accident.
And don't ever call here again.
This is like a noose you can use
to get Ham Tae Seob.
How much will you give me for it?
What will you do if I call the police?
You think I can't get out of that after
being in this line of work this long?
I hear you collect weaknesses
of people in high places.
You know Ham Tae Seob's weakness.
Give it to me.
Stop this show right now if
you don't want to get fired.
No matter how much I think about it,
I have nothing to replace this show.
If there's a show with ratings this high,
I'll put that on.
Take a look.
I think it's going to
get really good now.
The audio file you just heard was of
Ham Tae Seob and Jo Nam Chul.
This evidence, alone, is enough for
Ham Tae Seob to get arrested.
Before we do that...
he went so far as to hire killers
in order to cover this up.
The issue of SG Chemical's
air purifier humidifiers.
We will bring out his victims.
And give him an opportunity to admit
he was wrong and apologize.
I'm bringing them in.
You can all come in now.
Family members can come in too.
Here in the studio, we have people
who have used the SG humidifier.
These victims are suffering
from a lung disease.
Also, their families have
joined them here today.
Ham Tae Seob.
Will you sincerely apologize to
these people in front of you?
You have gone out of your way...
to fabricate this evidence against me.
You are lying to the viewers.
You attack the integrity of SG Group.
You defame my name and honor.
For what reason?
I really do not know why.
Are you even a human being!
What kind of nonsense is that?
- How could you...
- You're not human.
You should be apologizing!
Oh my goodness!
You call yourself a human being?
Choi Joon Gu must be
watching this right now.
We have to catch him before this ends.
Once this show ends
he'll think it's all over
and kill himself.
Where do you think he is?
They're all at the places he could be at.
If it were me...
I would want to be here.
The broadcast team is doing the show
that he originally wanted to do.
You should go to the studio.
Senior, you should do it.
It's okay. Go.
Executive Director Choi!
Lieutenant Cha.
Executive Director Choi, don't do that.
Come down from there.
In the end, this is how it turned out.
Nothing worked, no matter what I did.
I killed all those people.
I did things to people I shouldn't have.
I did an awful thing to a little child.
Executive Director Choi,
come down and talk.
I...
I was planning to go
once I finished everything.
To my baby...
and to where my wife is buried.
If I knew I wouldn't be seeing them,
I should've visited earlier.
What am I supposed to say to them
now if I meet them later?
I left them there, all lonely.
You should go. You can even go now.
I'm sorry, but...
I'll go to hell and pay for my crimes.
Ham Tae Seob.
You're under arrest for conspiracy to
murder Na Jae Hyun and Ham Tae Young.
You have the to remain silent
and a right to an attorney.
What's wrong with your face?
You're just a young man.
You're arresting me in
front of the entire country.
Do you think you can handle it once
the investigation results come out?
How can someone be so brazen?
He needs to go to prison
to get his head on straight!
What kind of a person behaves that way?
Rot in prison.
Stay in prison forever!
For a long time,
I wondered why my son was kidnapped.
Why was it me chosen to do this show?
He did not let me know.
He never gave a mission
to reveal my own crimes.
However...
I had definitely done something wrong.
Back when it happened seven years ago
my husband did not tell me the specifics.
I knew that SG Chemical
had done something wrong.
And that people were
getting hurt or dying.
I also knew that SG
was trying to cover it up.
But, I was more concerned about
my husband getting hurt.
I thought of myself and my baby.
I worried my family would be in danger.
So, I objected to my husband
taking part in this work.
I told him to choose
between doing it or me.
I pushed him to leave for France with me.
My husband was going to
give up on it because of me.
That was my crime.
I want to use this opportunity...
to apologize to all of you.
I only thought of my baby
and family as precious.
In order to protect that
I thought it was okay to turn my back
on the pains of others.
I did not even try to know
about people who were in pain.
You were wronged.
And you were in severe situations.
For that, I am so sorry.
I am very sorry.
Don't die.
Don't run away.
Just live.
Don't go to hell.
Pay for what you've done here.
It's not like nothing has changed.
People know now.
Stay alive, whether it's
in prison or wherever.
Watch over SG Group to see
what they end up doing.
Open your eyes and watch them.
Also, watch over those victims.
Watch how they stand back up again.
Watch to see what choices people
unrelated to this end up making.
You have to see it.
And people like Senior Sang Shik...
who sacrificed their lives to help you.
And Na Soo Hyun, though he
went about it wrong...
He wanted to see that end.
You have a responsibility to them.
You have to be here.
At this point...
we will tell you everything we know
about SG's air purifier humidifier.
We will start from the beginning.
Are you all right?
I feel strange.
The perpetrator is being punished.
The whole country knows now.
I thought I'd feel good
once this happened.
Do you think anything will change now?
Will we get a proper apology?
Ham Tae Seob will probably escape
legal punishment somehow.
SG will not admit to any wrongdoing.
Still...
we will keep doing what we can.
What we must do.
Even at this very moment
it could you or your loved ones
who are in pain without knowing why.
I would estimate that there are
millions of these potential victims.
It's finally the end.
I'm not going to work with you again.
You don't know what
I'm going to work on next.
Whatever you do,
we don't suit each other.
More than doing well,
I care about doing things right.
I want to work with
you again, Writer Yeon.
I want try something different now.
You're not talking about...
Director, you're not really going to
do a new show on this, are you?
Are you really not going to work with me?
I'll see how today's show goes first.
SG must be held responsible.
Victims must receive an apology
and compensation.
The government still has
a lot of work left to do.
After you watch the conclusion
to this broadcast
If you have any symptoms from
the air purifier humidifier
It does not matter if you have
used the humidifiers for a long time.
If you do not have any symptoms yet
please call into our station.
Subtitles by DramaFever