[Wanted]
There's something that I wish
to tell all of you today.
This movie will be my last,
and I will be retiring.
Mommy, are you mad that I
came here without telling you?
Is that why you said that
you're not working anymore?
No. It's because I want
to be with you every day.
Hi!
You said that you wanted to see
how fake blood is made, right?
- Right now?
- That's okay with you, right?
Please take good
care of him.
Hyun Woo!
Hyun Woo, let's go.
Hyun Woo isn't here?
Hyun Woo!
[IF YOU DON'T WANT YOUR CHILD
TO GET HURT, WATCH THIS ALONE.]
Who are you?
[MAKE A REAL-TIME REALITY TV SHOW,
WITH JUNG HYE IN AS THE LEAD.]
Stop!
[THERE WILL BE A MISSION SENT TO
YOU AT 10 P.M. EVERY NIGHT]
[FOR A SHOW WITH 10 EPISODES.]
Wait!
[IF JUNG HYE IN COMPLETES THE
MISSIONS WITHOUT A HITCH]
[SHE WILL BE SENT EVIDENCE
SHOWING THAT HYUN WOO IS SAFE.]
[IF SHE MANAGES TO GET
THROUGH ALL TEN EPISODES]
[HYUN WOO WILL BE
SENT BACK TO HER SAFELY.]
Mommy!
Hye In.
You have to report
this to the police.
I can't. They're watching
my every move.
There's only one person
who could do this, but...
This is what happened to Hyun Woo.
Then, they sent me this.
You should've reported
this to the police.
Why are you bringing this to me?
Only you can do this,
Dong Wook.
Find someone else.
Please, save
my Hyun Woo!
The only network that we
can work with is UCN.
Tell me why I should spend
any money on this show.
The fact that you're Hyun Woo's father
isn't a good enough reason?
This program will
definitely make you money.
I'm sure that the viewers will wonder
whether or not we can find the child
and about what the next
mission may be about.
I'm sure that the ratings
will only get higher and higher.
I'm sure you can take care of a lot of
UCN's money problems with this...
Okay. We'll start airing it on Saturday,
and it'll be on at 10 p.m. every week.
I'll give you a time slot
as a special program.
What?
Okay.
Ms. Hye In, you suddenly announced
your retirement not too long ago.
So what brings you
on the show today?
I heard that this program
had the best ratings.
I guess you weren't really retiring.
You were just switching to variety shows!
Ms. Jung Hye In?
To be honest...
I came here because there
was something I wanted to say
to everyone about the day
I announced my retirement.
On that day...
my son, Hyun Woo,
was kidnapped.
Right now, a team of content creators
are working their hardest
on a program focused on
finding Hyun Woo again.
I just hope that my
Hyun Woo is safe.
The first episode will air on
UCN on Saturday, at 10 p.m.
If she keeps talking, it may become an
issue so try and make the viewers cry!
Use the story about the kid
to make people get emotional!
If all of you who are watching
this could forgive me
and sympathize with a mother
who wishes to find her child
please, help me!
I'm begging you!
Please watch the show,
and help us find Hyun Woo.
Did you know
about this, PD?
No. Not at all.
Why didn't I think of that?
That's amazing.
It definitely makes an
impact, for sure.
Look.
[TRENDING: 1. JANG HYE IN
2. KISS AND TALK JANG HYE IN]
She's all over the
top searches on the web.
Oh my gosh!
What do we do?
Even when she's like this,
it all seems like an act.
She doesn't have 20 years of
experience in the industry for nothing.
She sure is incredible.
That's how you get people
emotionally invested
so they'll watch the show
and have it get
more popular.
Where are you going?
I have to record some
footage for the show
and check on some things.
Bo Yeon, you work with Director Choi and
monitor the online comments about this.
Check how many people have checked
our program's homepage.
And change the copy, Director,
so it's more dramatic.
- Update the site as soon as it's ready.
- Yes, sir.
What's this?
It's been a while since I've seen you,
so I didn't want to come empty-handed.
No. What's more embarrassing
would be me leaving with a gift
after having dined with you for the
first time in a while, as Commissioner.
- I knew you'd react that way.
- So why did you bring it, then?
I think it's about time you've
started preparing yourself
to retire from being a Commissioner,
and become an Assemblyman.
What are you
trying to pull, here?
Do you want me to cut
ties with you forever?
Make me a tiny little template.
Divide this among some people who
you trust and tell them to deposit it.
I'll give you even more
money after that.
This is something that you must do if you
are going to go and do great things.
Don't just take any old offer
that's shoved into your face
and accept mine,
which you know is trustworthy.
Yes.
All right.
I'll call you again.
Was this because of the issue
regarding your son?
It's just that my plans
have been pulled forward a bit.
This is something that I've been
preparing before that happened.
What do you need?
Just 10 days.
Make sure that the program
won't be negatively affected
due to an investigation or
something, for ten days.
Oh, Writer Yeon!
What brings you here?
You must be happy, PD Jo.
Your ratings were
already great, but, wow.
How do you feel now,
now that they've skyrocketed?
What are you
talking about?
How could this possibly be a good thing?
A child was kidnapped!
What are you talking about?
When Ms. Hye In collapsed... wow.
Wow, you did a great job
evoking emotion.
Seeing that, I...
But seriously, what's going on?
Is this why you suddenly quit?
For that show?
You should've told me sooner!
Then we would've
canceled Mr. Kim's appearance
and would've made an episode
focusing solely on Jung Hye In!
She went and did that on her own.
We didn't even knew she'd be doing that.
How could such a spectacle happen
if everything had been pre-planned?
But, um, is this
really happening?
Poor Jung Hye In.
Did anything strange come up
or did a strange person
come by after the show?
No.
The criminal may contact you guys,
so please keep an ear to the ground.
Don't try to profit off
this as an exclusive
and let us know right away!
Why would they contact us here?
Wouldn't they just contact Ms. Jung?
And also, it's not like
that's up to me, you know.
If the higher-ups tell me to reveal it,
I'll have no choice but to do it!
You've already got yourself a cash cow,
so don't toy with a child's life, too.
- I'll be going, then.
- Why, that little...
Stop doing that.
There are reporters outside.
It wasn't bad. And it's not like I don't
understand how you must feel.
But, you know, something about
this puts me in a bad mood.
I don't want to put an end to everything
just because you did as you pleased.
Did you speak to them?
I'm sure you didn't have
the time to do that yet.
All you needed to do is
make a single phone call.
At the very least, we need to
be filled in on what's going on.
And what if you told me
that I couldn't do it?
Then, you shouldn't
have done it.
This is a program that I'm
risking my reputation on.
You can't make any huge
decisions without my approval.
If something like this
happens again, I'm out.
Let me ask you
just one thing.
Do you have any intention of wanting
to find Hyun Woo through this show?
Of course we must find him.
And he must be safe.
That's the only way this will
all end with a happy ending.
That way, we can justify the premise
of the show, and it'll also become a hit.
Why are you even curious about
how I feel toward all this?
All you have to do is
find Hyun Woo, anyway.
You're right.
That's true.
- It's Ms. Jung Hye In!
- She's out!
Take on the Jung Hye In case.
And pass the Lee Ji Eun
incident over to Officer Shin.
I don't want to.
Can't you be good just once
and just do as I say?
Why do I have to do that?
Because you're
freakishly talented
when it comes to kidnapping
and missing persons cases!
And you have the highest
recovery rate of victims, too!
Lee Ji Eun is also a
victim of kidnapping.
But the circumstances
are different, man!
This is a case that was pretty much
announced to the entire country!
So I'm sure that they'll
find the kid even faster.
And since it's an incident
involving an influential figure
the higher-ups will
do all they can, too.
Use a unit of 10 or
20 people to find the kid.
Just ignore the fact that I
exist until I find Lee Ji Eun.
Wow, look at Mr. Hotshot over here,
picking and choosing what he takes on.
Is that why your
record is so good?
Find someone else for this case.
I don't want to work with him, either.
Seeing how things have gotten this bad,
it's clear that I'm completely unskilled.
Go, you sons of bitches!
Do whatever the hell you want, and
don't even bother reporting back to me!
Assholes.
I'll go and wash up.
Anyone who was watching Kiss and Talk,
a live talk show, must've been shocked.
Actress Jung Hye In went on
the show as a surprise guest.
However, she made the shocking
announcement that her son was kidnapped
while live on the air, and has sent
shock waves throughout the nation.
Ms. Jung stated the criminal ordered
her to create a live reality TV show
in which she completes missions
sent to her by the captor.
Currently, the police is conducting a
press conference regarding this case.
Let's head over there now.
Regarding "Wanted," the show that will
be airing on UCN on Saturday at 10 p.m.
It is one way that we will be conducting
investigations regarding this case.
We wish for the safe return
of Song Hyun Woo
as much as his mother does
and we have been forced
to make this decision.
We will be making thorough preparations,
and treat this matter seriously.
We will also be working with the TV
team to do our best to find the child.
I can only give you two weeks.
Find the kid before then.
If this drags on any longer,
we're all dead. Got that?
Yes, I understand,
sir. Yes.
Easier said than done,
man! Sheesh.
We've already lost three days.
Get your heads on straight.
If you don't want to
be working 24/7
make sure you monitor all other media
outlets other than the show itself.
Don't you dare sleep until we find
the kid, and eat while you're working!
- Got that? Hurry and go!
- Yes, sir!
There hasn't been any
word from the criminals.
I thought we were supposed
to air the show tonight.
That's why you should have just
reported this when it first happened!
There's so much time you've lost by
fooling around and trusting the criminal!
Sir, sir, sir! What good would
speculating about that do?
Three days is long enough
for a child to have already died!
Nothing good will come of
playing along with these mind games.
Mommy!
Do all victims always come back alive
because the crime is reported to cops?
- Do you have a child, Officer?
- I have a daughter.
How do you think you would've
reacted if you were in my shoes?
Well, um, yes. What's most important
right now is actually finding the child.
Let's not cry over spilled
milk here, and...
Is there anyone who would've had
any malicious intent toward you two?
No. I can't think of
anyone like that.
There's nobody that you've gotten
especially close to recently
or had a falling-out with due
to work, all of the sudden?
No, there isn't.
There are some employees
who are suing his company.
And those employees are
having their wages held, too.
No, that's nothing major.
All she's ever done is act,
so she knows nothing about business
and she's making a
big deal over nothing.
We'll be the judge of that.
If you've gotten any threats,
please let us know about them.
Even if it's nothing major,
you must tell us about it in detail.
No, there haven't been
any instances like that.
I'll take care of this, so you
head in and get some rest.
You're quite sensitive right now.
It's been all right for the past month
or so, but I have stalkers.
There have also been times
where I've sued people for libel online.
And there have been instances when this
man had been seeing some other women.
I don't think their relationships
lasted very long, but you never know.
Oh. How about we talk over there?
Don't worry.
We respect your privacy.
We will ensure that details regarding the
case will not be leaked to the press.
It's not like it'll be that big
of a deal even if it is leaked.
I've been with her for a while,
so you know how it can be.
The longer you stay with each other,
the larger your doubts grow.
At any rate, I'll tell you
everything. Let us go.
Are you out of your damn mind?
Do you think I could honestly
be sane right now?
Do you think that the
company will be okay
after the police question the
people suing the company?
I have no interest in your life.
If you want to find Hyun Woo,
it'd be best if you were.
If you'd just told me from the beginning,
things wouldn't have become like this.
I have quite a bit of
influence, you see.
Then do what you can now
even though you're a bit
late to the game.
No matter what anyone says, you've lived
as Hyun Woo's father for seven years.
I'm back!
- Jang Jin Woong!
- Yes?
Get over here.
Damn it, why is she
targeting me?
- Why are you lounging around here?
- Well, this is where I work.
Where else should I be?
Don't you know that we have an
urgent situation on our hands?
Also, you're the one in
charge of Jung Hye In!
Shouldn't we leave kidnapping incidents
to be handled by the public?
Why should the entertainment
section cover that?
A top star's child has been abducted!
It's obviously a total exclusive!
And you weren't at the meeting yesterday.
Why are you so carefree lately?
It's not like it was about
anything important.
Get your head in the game,
Jang Jin Woong!
Don't you hear the sound of
everyone scrambling around?
Everyone's desperate to get their
hands on any juicy information!
Great, then we'll just do
what we always do.
After another outlet works their
butt off to get an article out
we can gauge people's reactions,
and rewrite the article for our site!
Hey... get the hell out, right now.
Do whatever it takes to get an in with
UCN or Jang Hye In, and get an exclusive!
Go find out what Jang Hye In
is eating in this time of distress
by digging in her trash bin or something,
you piece of human trash!
Wow, you'll shatter
the lens at that rate.
How is it that your voice
only gets louder and louder?
You lazy bastard!
Dig through her trash, eh?
How could she tell me to do that?
I did think that you were
quite extraordinary
I'm not just extraordinary.
I'm revolutionary.
Someone who deserves to
be written about in history books.
Everyone and their dog has an
opinion about the ongoing case
but it's different when an extremely
detailed account of the case is released.
When everything is said and done
and I release this book
it'll totally be a hit!
Have you really finished talking
things over with Ms. Jung's people?
I'm telling you, yes!
I've been working as a celebrity
reporter for ten years now.
You don't just write things
based off internet comments
or just based on gut feeling!
That's just not right!
There aren't many hardworking
reporters like us anymore!
And there are even fewer people
who are as great as I am.
Jung Hye In and
Song Jung Ho are no problem!
Do you know how many
scandals I've uncovered?
Well, then, I'll read it over
and give you a call.
I'm allowing you to be the first one
to read it, so to reject this is...
This is something that needs
careful consideration.
Well, fine, then.
It's not a bad idea for me
to weigh my options later
after I'm done polishing
up this work, after all.
Geez, that annoying
fly-like bastard.
[WITNESS AFFIDAVIT]
That night, I went to a dinner with
the movie crew, and drank quite a lot.
I checked into a nearby motel, and
I woke up around 12 p.m. the next day.
So why didn't you go
straight home that day?
As soon as I woke up, I felt so
apologetic toward Hye In and called her
and she didn't pick up the
first couple of times I called her.
Then, I got a single text.
It said, "go rest at your parents'
house for a couple of days."
I thought that there may have
been some issues between
her and her husband because of
her retirement announcement.
And you've been with your
parents since then, huh?
Yes.
Um, we're finished here, then, right?
Today's the premiere of the show,
so I need to be by Hye In's side.
If you want to prove what you just
said is true, you need to stay here.
We found a hidden camera
inside Ms. Hye In's car.
You're the one who takes
care of her car, correct?
[MAKING A LIVE TV SHOW OUT OF A CRIME?]
[WE WILL NOT WATCH UCN'S SHOWS]
Stop making excuses,
and pay us!
- Pay us!
The criminal requested that
a reality TV show be made.
This is certainly a first.
Could this show really help
the investigation?
- What do you think?
- Well...
It seems to me that the criminal has a
strong desire to make himself known.
Above all else,
they seek attention.
It is a dangerous situation, but it may
be good to listen to their demands
and buy some time.
Hyun Woo is...
It's dangerous to listen to
a criminal's demands.
There is a possibility that there may
be others who try to copy this criminal.
We cannot trust a criminal,
no matter the circumstances.
Could the show really help
with the investigation, or not?
We're out here in Yeouido
to gauge the public opinion.
It definitely pains me to see this.
And as a mother,
I know how she must feel.
I am a bit excited to see a live TV
show that is trying to catch a criminal.
I also want to watch the show and
potentially help with the case.
I do worry that someone else
may try to emulate this criminal
or that someone else may
try to do this again, for fame.
I cried while I was watching
Kiss and Talk yesterday.
And Hyun Woo is such a handsome child,
which makes it even sadder.
I'll definitely be
watching the show.
[1. THE FIRST EPISODE WILL AIR TWO
DAYS FROM TODAY, ON SATURDAY.]
[4. IF THE VIEWERSHIP RATING FALLS BELOW
20 PERCENT, HYUN WOO WILL GET HURT.]
[- THE CRIMINAL SUCKS]
[- HOW COULD YOU MAKE A SHOW LIKE THIS?]
The show is supposed to air tonight,
but there's no mission.
Maybe the criminal never intended
to go through with a TV show.
Maybe they changed their plans
because something happened...
No, seeing as how they
requested the show be live
they're trying to give us very little
time to make sound judgments
and may be trying to fulfill
another objective by doing so.
We just have to wait and see.
Let's try and make a plan
beforehand, too.
We have to give the viewers an impression
that we're working to help the case.
What if that makes
the criminal angry?
That's not that bad, either.
If they act irrationally
based on their emotions
they may do something to
expose themselves.
Hyun Woo is with them, though!
We can't put him in danger!
No, doing that isn't going against
what the criminal told us to do, per se.
The mission, the ratings,
and you being the star...
we just have to meet
those conditions.
Delivery!
Let's eat first.
Hye In. Let's eat, okay?
Eat, and regain some
of your strength.
- Hye In!
- If you don't want to eat, don't.
Don't eat, or sleep,
or anything else.
I'm sure that the criminal will see that
and return Hyun Woo, for sure.
I can quit working on this
at any time, you know.
If you're not in the state
to be working with me
I have no intention of
bending over backwards for you.
Just clench your teeth and bear it.
Get a good night's rest, and eat up.
Keep yourself in
tip-top shape.
Sir, do you really not have any
interest in the Jung Hye In case?
Yeah.
I thought about it, and I think
all of this has been orchestrated.
Why?
Jung Hye In's husband is the
president of the network.
They said before that they were going
to make a reality TV show with her.
But then, she suddenly
announced her retirement
and her child just so happened
to be there that day.
And that's where her
child was kidnapped.
- Seeing that...
- Stop watching dramas.
- Where are you going?
- Aren't you going to work?
Wait for me, sir!
[MEMBERS BANNED FROM COCONUT TV]
I saw this video, too,
but I'm telling you.
This wasn't a kidnapping.
This was just an act.
Seriously, isn't she a bit of a
psycho for agreeing to do this?
So you're saying that you received
an offer to do something like that
a month ago,
from Orson Welles?
Yes. All the people who broadcast
on this channel know about him.
He's generous, and gives one
or two thousand star balloons to people.
But if he feels like you remember him,
he gets all clingy and weird.
And he emails creepy videos.
- Did you meet him in person to talk?
- Yes.
Is it this person,
by any chance?
Oh... oh, yes! Yes!
Yes, it's him!
He kept sending me
creepy videos and photos
so I told him I'd report him to the
police, then he told me he loved me
and even came to
my front door!
So why didn't you report him?
Don't be like that. It's a
hassle to report people to the police.
And most people back off once
you threaten to report them.
I ran into him while I was
out with my boyfriend
and he told me that he had a
business plan, or something.
- It was kind of weird.
- A business plan?
You know, kidnapping people
while they're broadcasting.
He kept telling me that it would totally
blow up if he did something like that
and that he had a plan.
But I had no idea what
he was talking about.
He got all worked up by himself.
Obviously, he was a psycho.
- Anyway, can I head back in now?
- Oh, yes.
If you remember
anything else, call me.
- Thank you!
Thank you.
This is Cha Seung In of the
Gangnam Police Department.
Oh, you confirmed it?
Yeah.
Send the details to me over email.
I'll confirm it on the way there.
Turn the car around.
- Is it correct?
- We'll know when we get there.
They've been in twice, but were
released due to lack of evidence.
Go to Yeonnamdong.
- Shouldn't we report this...
- We have to find the kid!
We have no time!
Let's arrest him first and
worry about a warrant later.
Yes, sir.
Yes?
This came for you.
[TO THE "WANTED" TEAM]
Who dropped this off?
A guy from a delivery service
we work with frequently.
Where's the person
who brought this here?
Over there.
- Wait!
- What are you doing?
- Stop it!
- Who the hell are you?
- What are you doing?
You have something on you,
don't you? Get the hell off!
No! No!
[FIRST MISSION: I WONDER WHAT'S
INSIDE THE TRUNK OF THIS CAR?]
[PLEASE SHOW IT TO THE
WORLD ON THE SHOW.]
Spill it, punk!
They told me they'd
give me 1 million won
so I just did this errand for them.
And I gave that girl
a ride last time, too.
I really didn't know
what was going on, either!
I saw the news this morning, and debated
whether or not I should say something.
But I was scared that something would
happen to me if I didn't do this!
- I was scared.
- Who ordered you to do this?
His name is Park Sae Yong.
I went to high school with them.
They told me to take my license
plate off when running errands.
What about that girl
from last time?
Where did you
drop her off?
Yeonnamdong. Someone came to
pick her up at the subway station.
You have to be completely
honest with us.
If you don't, you'll be
tried as an accomplice.
An accomplice?
All I did was deliver this!
I didn't even know what I was doing!
What did that person tell you?
That I couldn't tell anyone
what I was doing.
And that, if I did,
they'd kill everyone.
That bastard was a total psychopath
when we went to school together, too.
If he finds out that
I told you guys all this
I don't know what'll happen to me!
He knows where I live,
and what my family look like!
I have a package for you!
Mr. Park Sae Yong!
Ma'am! Hurry!
- Is Mr. Park Sae Yong here?
- No.
Just give it to me, please.
I can't. I was told that I had
to deliver it to him directly.
- He's not home?
- No, he's not!
Why are you acting like this?
I'll call the police!
We are the police.
May we come in for a bit?
You've come to the wrong place.
That person doesn't live here!
We're not going to take him away.
We just need to ask
a couple of questions.
I told you, that person
doesn't live here!
- Sae Yong! No! You can't!
- Hold her back!
- Sae Yong!
- Open the door!
- No!
- Please, ma'am!
Hey, untie him!
Sir!
Hold him!
- Call an ambulance, and the precinct.
- Yes, sir.
Park Sae Yong.
Park Sae Yong!
Yes, hello. We have someone who
attempted to commit suicide here!
The address is...
- Yeonnamdong, 2-
- Sae Yong!
- Ma'am! Please!
- Sae Yong! Sae Yong!
Ma'am!
Sir, shouldn't we
secure the premises?
Lee Ji Eun isn't here.
Seeing as he tried to commit suicide,
he may have already killed...
Then go find the damn
corpse, bastard!
["THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT."]
We don't have much time left.
First, send the photos to the police.
I'm sure they'll be able
to find it quickly.
Let's send the photos
to the breaking news team.
We can use our network's
news channel, but not others'.
This is ultimately a personal
matter, after all.
It may be faster to do it
over social media.
We can use Facebook,
Twitter, and Instagram.
I've made accounts for
our show on all of those.
Really? Then, I'll go and
meet with the police.
It's crucial that we help them
with their investigation.
Hye In. I got a call
from the police.
You dropped your
phone before, so...
Yes, this is Jung Hye In.
I'm Cha Seung In from the
Gangnam Police Department.
Have you ever gotten threatened
or harassed by someone lately?
Or, do you have someone who's
been stalking you for a long time?
Yes, there are a couple of them.
I'll send you a photo, so can
you tell me if they look familiar?
Hi!
You said you wanted to see
how fake blood is made, right?
Please take good care of him.
I'd like it if you could
come to the scene
and confirm a few things for us.
Hye In. Where are you going?
I'll drive you there.
You should've stayed with him.
You should've been with him!
- What?
- You should've stayed with Hyun Woo!
The person who took Hyun Woo
apparently committed suicide!
If something happened to Hyun Woo,
I'll never forgive you.
So you're basically asking the police
to help clean up after your mess?
Is that what you're
saying right now?
But even so, it's great that you kept
the motorcyclist from leaving, yes.
Well, from now on, please call us
if anything like this happens again!
Kidnappings are like
a race against time!
Yes, I understand.
You did this on purpose, right?
What?
You did it in order to raise
the ratings of this show.
Aren't you kind of hoping that
the criminal will not be caught?
- What are you saying?
- Mr. Choi Joon Gu.
You got in hot water for creating a show
without your network's involvement.
So how did you get
back in here, anyway?
I guess the president is more
generous that I thought.
Are you investigating
me right now?
No, I'm just curious, is all.
You can investigate me or
interrogate me whenever you want.
But right now, shouldn't our first
priority be finding Hyun Woo?
We'll continue to work alongside
you for the sake of this case.
Let's find Hyun Woo
as soon as possible.
I beg of you.
- I guess he's dead.
- Well, that was sudden!
- It's Jung Hye In!
- Oh my gosh, Jung Hye In!
What are you doing?
Stop that!
Hyun Woo!
Get out of the way!
- Hyun Woo! Hyun Woo!
- You mustn't go in!
- You can't go in!
- No!
It's all right.
Let her go.
[ALWAYS GREAT GAS STATION]
I'm Cha Seung In,
the one who called you.
- Where's my Hyun Woo?
- You son is not here.
I'm sorry, but there are a couple
things I'd like to have you confirm.
Have you ever seen this woman?
- Yes. I've seen her.
- Where?
She brought the script to my house
the day Hyun Woo was taken.
Did you get a good look at her face?
Are you sure it's her?
I only saw her for a few moments,
but I'm positive.
Is she here?
She's an accomplice.
- She's not an accomplice.
- What are you saying?
- On that day...
- She's a victim.
She was also kidnapped,
just like your son was.
I don't know this man.
I did see him on the last few
days of the shoot for my movie.
But he lied about his identity,
and nobody knew him.
Have you ever run into him in front
of your home, or somewhere else?
Has your son ever said that a
strange man approached him?
No.
But... is this because of me?
Is he trying to prevent me from
retiring by making me do this TV show
like it says here?
Then he would've continued with that,
instead of committing suicide.
And if he'd changed his mind
and decided to commit suicide
I'm sure he would've left a note
saying what must be done now.
I'm sure that someone else
is the true mastermind.
They may have used the fact that Mr. Park
was a huge fan of yours as an advantage.
Mommy...
Hyun Woo!
Hyun Woo, it's Mom!
- Anything?
- I'm not sure.
Yes, it's me. We've found
the owner of the car
but it was stolen 3 days ago.
But the car was bought under
another person's name
so the owner didn't
bother reporting it.
Yes. And I have a
solid alibi, too.
[FOOTAGE OF YEONAN PIER'S
CARGO TERMINAL]
[COMPILATION OF
FOOTAGE FROM PORTS]
I knew that you
were skilled, PD Shin.
And that's why I gave you
the okay yesterday.
So I thought that you'd be suited
to work for my network.
If this isn't anything urgent,
I'll hear you out after the show today.
I finally understand
why people say that
you shouldn't work with
people past their prime.
Have you lost your touch?
Jung Hye In is the one
who made the preview
and all you have is a photo to work with,
even though the show is in 2 hours.
Well, do you have any
back-up plans, at least?
No.
What are you doing to do, then?
If we can't find it,
that's what will be shown on TV.
Are you trying to
get my son killed?
That may end up happening
if you keep wasting my time
with drivel like this.
- Mommy... save me!
- Hyun Woo, it's Mom!
- It's Mom, Hyun Woo!
- Mom... my...
- Hurry over here, Mommy!
- Where are you, Hyun Woo?
Are you in any sort of pain?
Are you hurt anywhere?
- I'm scared, Mommy...
- Hyun Woo!
It's so dark!
Hyun Woo, Mommy will be there soon.
I'll be there soon, okay?
- Mommy!
- Where are you?
- You have to let me know where you are!
- Mommy!
Hyun Woo. Hyun Woo!
Hyun Woo!
- Here are the materials you requested.
- Thanks.
How did things go?
All right?
I'm not sure if we can
find the car in time.
- And even if we do...
- Can we get a helicopter?
A helicopter? Okay.
We'll have to do that, then.
No, it might not
be able to find it in time.
What about Jung Hye In?
Still not picking up?
Yes. I kept trying to call her.
And her manager
wouldn't pick up, either.
What have you been doing this whole time?
Make sure she's here in thirty minutes!
Yes, sir.
Damn it. I'm sure that she'll be here
since we need her most. Let's wait.
We still haven't even
found the car yet.
Sheesh.
Please, pick up!
The person you are trying to
reach is unavailable at this time...
I found it.
I knew I felt like I'd
seen it somewhere.
I once did some investigative
work there three years ago.
We'll be short on time,
even if we head there now.
You sure about this?
Here, here, and here.
And the most decisive piece
of evidence is this graffiti.
Let's hurry and report
this to the police.
Did you forget? The criminal told us
that the show is supposed to be live.
We might end up filming something
that shouldn't be on TV.
If the police gets there before us,
they might get in our way.
If it's that bad, we should come
up with a contingency plan!
No contingency plan will work.
We just have to shoot everything as is.
That's what we agreed to do.
And even if the
criminal falls for it
do you think the viewers will continue
watching if it doesn't seem genuine?
Getting a 20 percent rating
is already a herculean task.
I'll send Hye In to the studio
when she's found.
You work on prompts for the show.
Okay, okay.
Hurry and go.
Oh, and let me know what's in
the trunk before the show if you can
by sending me a
photo or calling me.
I'll take care of the rest here.
- Writer Yeon. If the director...
- I know. Go, already.
- Young Gwan.
- Yes?
Find a port in Incheon that
smaller freight ships visit.
And look for places where the
train tracks are close to the beach.
There's a railroad crossing, and
a train passed by it at 8:40 p.m.
Call for some backup and
find it as soon as you can.
Did you find Ji Eun?
Jung Hye In got a call from her son.
I'll head over to Incheon right now
so call me as soon as
you find the place.
Yes, sir.
Due to this customer's request,
we are unable to complete your call.
Let's get it together.
Get it together, Jung Hye In.
I'm sure that someone else
is the true mastermind.
[WANTED]
- Mommy... Mommy!
- Hyun Woo!
It's so dark!
Mommy!
Please wait at home, and I'll...
I might get another
call from Hyun Woo.
Let's go together.
What are you
doing right now?
Um, we're not completely
sure where it is, either.
We're just going to
try heading out first
so please give us a
call when you find the car.
Tell me where the
hell you're going!
But, um, why are you
talking so informally?
It's pissing me off.
Park Bo Yeon, you haven't
found where Hye In is yet?
No. It keeps saying that she's
in the middle of another call.
Call the authorities
and ask them to find her!
I did, but they said that they can
only do that in emergency situations...
Then put on an act, punk!
Our program might go under
and a kid may die
,
so what the hell are you doing?
Yes, sir.
Who the hell are you?
Hey! Hey, you! Hey!
He's not a staff member
of yours, right?
Take it easy, please!
I'm not a weirdo, I promise!
I'm a reporter!
Ow!
I'm just here doing my job!
Wait, sir! Ow!
Wait, please!
Where did you say that you saw
those large pieces of cargo, again?
- Here, here, and...
- Here it is.
Thank you.
They said that the kid
might be in Incheon
so check every nook and cranny!
Did you find it? Hey, are you going to
take responsibility if the kid dies?
I found it!
Sir, I found it!
All right. I'll be right there.
We found the place where
the call was made from.
There are others looking
for him, too, so...
Can we find him within
thirty minutes?
- Yes, it's me.
- Where are you right now?
What the hell are
you doing right now?
Did you find the car?
Go to the studio right now.
We're on our way to the scene.
Where are you heading?
The north port in Incheon.
It's a warehouse.
Is there a railroad
crossing near that?
How did you know that?
I got a call from Hyun Woo
and it's from the same location.
Hyun Woo and the criminal
may be near there, too.
Hello?
I'll do the show.
I'll be right there.
I think I'll be there a bit after 10.
Text me your exact address.
Then, we'll use what Writer Yeon wrote...
No, I have to open the show.
They'll have doubts
if we stall for time.
You can broadcast a video that
I send you with my phone, right?
Get ready to begin.
Five, four, three, two, one.
I'm all sweaty.
Please.
[FIRST MISSION: WHAT COULD
BE INSIDE THIS TRUNK?]
- Is Hye In ready?
- Yes.
We'll be going in
in 10 seconds.
Right now, we're on our way to
find a car at a pier in Incheon.
Before today's show is over, we will
show everyone what is in the trunk
to complete the mission.
You have to put a light here, and
some more over there, too!
Camera.
Film them!
Follow her!
Turn the feed back to
what's going on in the studio
and turn it back when
things have settled down.
Switch to 5. Hurry.
- Stop filming.
- Get the camera here.
- No!
- Move!
A child was discovered in the trunk.
They are in critical condition.
- They are being taken to a hospital.
- You can't record here.
If Ms. Jung Hye In's son ends up
dying because of this hospital's policy
you'll have to close
down, won't you?
Everything was going
fine up until now
but it's definitely
not at 20 percent yet.
As to be expected of
Jung Hye In. You did great.
Don't ever joke like this again.
It's seriously creeping me out.
Hyun Woo may get hurt if
we hesitate for even a second.
So I'm going to do
whatever I must.
Subtitles by DramaFever