Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
Hyun Woo, let's go now.
Did Hyun Woo go somewhere?
Hyun Woo!
[IF YOU DON'T WANT YOUR CHILD TO
GET HURT, WATCH THIS VIDEO ALONE]
[JUNG HYE IN WILL HAVE TO STAR
IN LIVE REALITY SHOW.]
[A MISSION WILL BE GIVEN]
[AND THE SHOW WILL AIR
AT NIGHT FOR TEN EPISODES.]
[IF JUNG HYE IN COMPLETES THE MISSION,
SHE WILL RECEIVE PROOF HYUN WOO IS SAFE.]
[ONCE THE TEN EPISODES ARE OVER,
HYUN WOO WILL BE SENT HOME.]
Mom, Mom!
Mom!
Hyun Woo has been kidnapped.
The kidnapper sent this to me.
You're the only person who
can do this, Dong Wook.
Find someone else.
Please help me save Hyun Woo's life.
My son Hyun Woo was kidnapped.
Please help me.
This was just delivered.
[WHAT'S INSIDE THIS CAR'S TRUNK?]
I'm Lieutenant Cha Seung In.
I need you to come
to a crime scene for me.
Where is Hyun Woo?
Your son is not here.
Mom.
- Hyun Woo!
- Mom...
Hyun Woo!
- I'll be there soon.
- It's so dark.
I'll be there soon, Hyun Woo.
Where are you?
We're heading over in the broadcast van.
Is Hye In ready?
We're going on air in 10 seconds.
Camera! Get the camera!
[EPISODE 3]
Go! Stay with her.
We need to get the studio ready to go.
Get number five ready now!
Don't film that.
Bring the camera in.
Stay back.
Over here!
Go with her.
Check all the CCTVs in this area.
We arrived at the car that
the culprit specified.
An unidentified child was
discovered inside the trunk.
He is in critical condition.
Critical condition.
He is on his way to the hospital.
Hey, Hyun Woo's call came from this area.
Then shouldn't she stay there
instead of going to the hospital?
The police will stay there and
they will investigate.
They footage was shaky earlier.
We didn't do a good job
showing what happened.
Give Hye In the earpiece and
get a close-up of the child's face.
Hye In.
How can anyone recognize him like this?
Let's take that oxygen mask off for
a few seconds.
We can't do that.
It's a matter of life or death.
Film his clothes, shoes,
and hands in detail.
His parents are looking for him,
they'll recognize those.
Okay.
Okay, Hye In.
This is the child we found in the trunk
of the car the culprit sent us to.
If anyone knows this child,
please contact the station.
We hope that the parents who lost this
boy are watching this right now.
We are currently heading to
Dongwoon Hospital in Incheon.
Look into any missing children reports
between the ages of six to ten.
Look into Seoul and Incheon for now.
Has his face been broadcast on TV?
Keep in touch with Senior Park's team.
I'll head to the hospital for now.
He's a boy, age seven to eight.
He's in hypothermic shock,
his blood pressure is 80 over 50.
His saturation level is at 94 percent,
so we've given him saline.
You cannot film in here.
Only a guardian can come in.
I said, no filming!
That child will either die or wake up
and tell us about the kidnapper.
That's what we need,
or it's not going to work.
We can't fill the rest of the show
arguing with the hospital.
Getting 20 percent ratings is no joke.
Once the commercials end,
we'll put up a screen for a tip line.
We have, at most, five minutes.
I'll try to figure something out.
I wonder if President Song has
any connections at this hospital.
Is Jung Hye In with the child?
Yes, we convinced the hospital to allow
her to stay until a guardian comes.
- Stay in here and watch over this.
- What?
Don't do anything unless me
or Writer Yeon tells you to.
Don't make any decisions on your own.
Okay.
The other patients in the ER
are very sensitive, as well.
It will disrupt their treatment and
you didn't get permission in advance.
We can't reach the director because
he's at a seminar out of the country.
That's what I'm saying.
The director is away at a seminar.
You're just an intern making a decision.
Suppose the hospital
won't let us broadcast
and Jung Hye In's son dies.
Wouldn't this hospital
have to close down?
It would be better to say we were able
to film with the hospital's cooperation.
You won't even be able to get
product placement on this show.
Don't film anywhere else!
Only film inside that room.
Of course.
When this hospital gets very popular...
I will say it's all thanks to you,
Doctor Han Kyu Won.
[WE ARE LOOKING FOR THE GUARDIANS.]
Make yourself decent in five minutes
and come outside.
You said Hyun Woo called
before the show aired?
The call was traced.
It showed that the call came from
around where the car was found.
So, why did you come to the hospital
instead of looking for Hyun Woo?
[20 PERCENT RATINGS]
[FOSTER GOODWILL AND
EXPLAIN THE SHOW'S MORAL DUTY]
A child was dying in front of me.
I had no time to think of anything else.
I thought to myself...
"Just save this child."
"He's a child like my Hyun Woo."
Mom...
Are you awake?
Do you know where you are?
What is your name?
Han Sol.
Hyun Woo!
Hello?
Hyun Woo?
Speaker phone.
Mom... save me.
Hyun Woo, it's your mom.
Yes, Chief.
The call was made within
this 500-meter radius.
We called ahead and found out
that a man came in with a boy.
He hasn't checked out.
Yes, sir.
Hyun Woo, it's Mom.
I'm hungry.
Hyun Woo, you need to help me
so I can find you.
I'm thirsty.
Come quickly, Mom.
Hyun Woo, calm down.
Hurry.
Hyun Woo, where are you?
It's so dark.
Hyun Woo.
Mom!
[NO TRAINS RUN AFTER 9:00 P.M.]
Who are you?
It's a recording.
This isn't Hyun Woo calling.
This is the same call from before.
It's a recording.
I was just checking.
To see if you are preparing the show
like I instructed.
Or to see if you were trying
to play me to find Hyun Woo.
I was checking on you.
Be careful.
If you don't follow orders next time,
things will become a bit difficult.
Don't pull something like this again.
If I lose my trust in you...
So, if I stop believing that
Hyun Woo is safe...
you won't get what you want either.
You must have wanted something too when
you made me go live on air with missions.
I'll do it all.
Whatever it is you want, I'll do it.
Cut the feed.
Okay.
We're live right now.
Don't you know how dangerous it is to
say you'll do whatever he wants?
Do you plan to stop after today?
I have no other way of talking
to the culprit!
You're an actress.
If you have a message to get across,
why don't you act?
Move the viewers and earn their empathy.
You're working right now.
Control your emotions
and take a deep breath.
We're going back in.
We're coming back in.
Okay. Let's go to camera three.
Okay.
Sir, are you in there?
What is this?
I'm hungry.
I'm thirsty.
Come quickly, Mom.
Leave that to the local precinct
and come back in.
Tell them investigate the area
very thoroughly.
Senior, it's me.
They say they cannot track that call.
It's being traced to a call in Jamaica.
Excuse me, I'm the father
of the child on TV.
- I'll call you back.
- Come this way.
I'm with the police.
- Are you the parents of that child?
- Yes.
Can you tell me when
and where your son went missing?
First, I need to see if my son is safe.
Come with me.
Han Sol! Han Sol!
Han Sol! My precious child.
Let me take a look at you.
Are you hurt at all?
We carried out the mission and
the wrong child nearly died.
The culprit called and
a child was united with his parents.
So far, it's not too bad.
But, it's still a little lacking
to hit 20 percent.
Han Sol, are you all right?
Get rid of the cameras.
Are you using my son to find your son?
There's a situation on scene.
Buy us some time.
Please calm down.
We did help find your son.
Didn't he get kidnapped because
of this TV show?
I'll be taking my son now.
Let's go, Han Sol.
Come here. Let's go.
Come here. It's okay.
There's something up with this family.
We can use this for the remaining time,
so keep watch and go on air.
Okay.
Han Sol, come here.
Come here.
How did you hurt your hand?
Ah... I hurt it while exercising.
Is that what's important right now?
My son is in shock right now
and he's shaking.
Come here.
Did you hit your son and his mother?
What do you think you're saying...
Tell us if you need help. It's all right.
No... he's just worked up
because of our son.
Please just leave us alone and let us go.
Let's go on air now and
put the camera on me first.
Do you think you can handle this?
Do you even know who I am?
Look at me.
You have to think of your son.
I am sorry.
I'll sue all of you.
Turn the camera off now!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
Ah, did you see the show?
It's a bit odd to enjoy a situation
like this, isn't it?
You don't have to
be sorry either, President.
We'll have to see the ratings tomorrow.
Honestly...
I was trying to run away yesterday.
His father had gone on
a trip out of the city.
But... I didn't know where to go.
So, I went to a sauna.
I lost him there.
Please.
Just save us.
Please, help us escape him.
[JUNG HYE IN'S WANTED]
That wasn't too bad, though it
unfolded in an unexpected way.
We need proof that Hyun Woo is alive.
We won't know the ratings until tomorrow.
This isn't easy.
There he is!
Did you abuse your son?
Give us a comment!
I'm sorry.
Let me ask you one thing.
Did you rip that woman's shirt because
you really wanted to help her?
You didn't have to do it that way.
Or did you use her to get ratings?
Think whatever you want.
Answer me.
What if I did use her?
I don't even have time to cry.
Sometimes I feel like I'm going insane
because I can't
remember Hyun Woo's face.
I can only think of one thing.
It's ten days.
For those ten days,
I'm willing to do anything.
If I hesitate for even one moment,
I could lose Hyun Woo.
If lose the audience's interest
for even a moment...
Hyun Woo could get hurt.
Yes, I know.
Still... shouldn't you avoid
hurting other people?
You can never escape some
relationships without getting hurt.
That child's mother would never have
told the truth on her own.
Her mask had to be cracked
for her to gain courage too.
Was there anyone you got close with
recently before Han Sol was kidnapped?
No.
Unless we were with his father,
we didn't really leave the house.
Did anyone know about you and Han Sol?
Someone who knew about your suffering...
I believe the kidnapper knew
and took Han Sol for this show.
I don't really know.
My parents both passed away.
I have no sisters or brothers.
My husband made me cut off contact
with all my friends after we married.
Why didn't you ever report
it to the police!
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay. It's okay.
I was so stupid.
I should have made sure to protect
Han Sol from him.
Where will you go now?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Seriously, I don't know.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I don't know a thing.
I don't know anything...
[THE CHRONICLES OF NARNIA]
It's strange to have you home.
I'm sorry I've been so busy.
I'll forgive you if you read this to me.
This part.
Again?
How many times is that now?
Haven't you memorized
it by now, Hyun Woo?
All right.
"Edmund walked alongside Peter
and spoke to Peter."
"Everything will be alright."
"Peter, will we be able to take down
Miraz with one blow?"
"Peter replied calmly."
"I am fighting in order to find out."
Mom, why do you like this part so much?
Because I want you to grow up
to be courageous like this too.
I'm fine. I'm going to head in.
When did you get in?
I said I'd pick you up.
Is it still that...
you can't forgive me yet?
No, it's not that.
Just because.
I don't think you need to do this.
You stayed by my side for two years
without sleeping for 24 hours.
You suffered a lot.
No, Hye In.
I'm going to stick with you...
I was going to retire anyway.
Star Entertainment isn't going wait long
with a section chief job for you.
It's a good opportunity.
You can't be on sets all your life.
I saw Chae Eun Yi act
and she was very good.
I met her before and she has
a good personality, as well.
You should go with her.
Succeed together.
I already told her that I can't
and that I was sorry.
- Why did you do that?
- This show...
No one knows what's going to happen.
You can't do this on your own.
You're not in a situation
to hire someone new.
The only thing that I can do is this.
I...
cared a lot for Hyun Woo too.
It's making me go crazy.
I'm determined to find him.
You don't have to do this.
We're... family.
This is what's right.
You're right.
Thanks.
[HUB OF CONTROVERSY! JUNG HYE IN'S HOME.]
Hye In, go in and rest.
You too.
Good work today.
I'm tired. Can you leave?
Jung Hye In is really something.
You're good when your heart is in it.
I was good?
At what?
I thought you always ran when
your back was against the wall.
But, today you were very good.
Yes.
Should I thank you for your compliments?
What were you doing?
Were you sitting around,
watching it on TV?
Of course, I should watch.
You disgust me.
Let's not exert our energy on each other.
We have a long way to go.
You knew very well that I wasn't going
to go running over there.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I'll be sleeping at the police station,
so don't worry and sleep.
Also, you'll need to come to
the police station tomorrow.
Get some rest.
I'm so sorry for being
a burden like this.
Don't worry about it.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Don't ever think that.
It's the adults that were bad.
I'll apologize to you on
behalf of all the adults.
Sorry.
Eat this.
You're going to ruin your body if you
drink coffee on an empty stomach.
So what if I do?
You said you'll pay me a lot.
I'll make rounds at all the hospitals
after we're done with this.
Did I do enough work today
to get a meal?
Should I be honest?
Both the first episode and preview...
we wouldn't have had
an answer without Jung Hye In.
Wow, I guess it's true,
but I feel a little upset by that.
You always do good work, Writer Yeon.
Well, I don't worry about you Director.
However, we will have to continue making
decisions by the minute or second.
I worry about Executive Director Choi.
He's going to act like an ethics teacher
in every circumstance.
Isn't it a waste of our energy?
I need that.
I'm not going to think about whether
something right or wrong.
It's nice to have someone else
think about it for me.
For me, you're my accelerator
and he's my brake.
Wow, that makes me sound like
the worst person here.
Once we're done with this
you should look at his stuff
he made as a director.
If you look at the Legend broadcast,
he did some things I could never do.
A policeman's vacation days
are determined by criminals.
But, when are there
ever days with no criminals?
So, don't think about resting
like anyone else.
Why don't you do you job properly?
Come on, Seung In!
Not in front of the kid.
Senior, you're older?
Hey, what about it?
My face has been like
this since junior high.
The Chief is coming.
The four of you are now in
charge of the TV show case.
The culprit is going to keep contacting
them with his missions or whatever.
Cha Seung In, do you have
a problem with it?
In order to find Lee Ji Eun
we need to find
Song Hyun Woo's kidnapper.
All right.
Try not to get in the way
of the broadcast team.
Cooperate with them the best you can,
but follow them wherever they go.
Chief, will we be held responsible for
anything that goes wrong on air?
The higher-up's have guaranteed that
you will not be held responsible.
Just focus on catching the kidnapper.
Didn't they guarantee anything else?
Shouldn't they promote us if
we catch the criminal this time?
It's one of the hardest cases.
Fine, just catch the guy.
Even if I get passed over,
I'll get you promoted, okay?
- What about back-up?
- You'll get whatever you need.
Just report to me if something happens.
Hey, Cha Seung In.
If you're hanging around the show,
our investigation can get exposed.
If you break procedure like usual and
end up pulling our team down
I won't let it go.
Give it a rest, both of you.
You two are both so greedy.
I'm going to go organize the
Park Se Young murder case.
I'm not done talking yet.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
I lost my way.
It's my first time in the police station.
- You're still here?
- Who is he?
A reporter.
He got caught in the broadcast relay van.
You're Lieutenant Cha Seung In, right?
I'm Jang Jin Woong from Starlight.
- Have you checked his alibi?
- Yes.
Wow, you're colder than I heard.
We'll be seeing each other often.
I'm doing this story.
I think it's best not to meet again.
Next time, I won't be seeing you
as a reporter but as a suspect.
That's not a bad thing either.
You're an important character too.
This case could make you a star or
your life could spiral out of control.
Leave.
See you again.
Here is your order.
Did you see "Wanted" yesterday?
It was crazy.
Didn't Jung Hye In go too far?
I thought she was cool.
They didn't have much air time left,
so weren't they trying to expose him?
Why is the kidnapper trying to expose
that man?
Do you think Jung Hye In's son is
abused too?
What would you like to order?
Six iced americanos for take-out.
Can I have three shots in one of them?
Take UCN off the air!
Off the air, off the air!
The creators of "Wanted"
must be punished.
Punished, punished!
It was number one in ratings.
- It was number one?
- It's all real.
[PROFESSOR KIM WOO JIN
INVESTIGATED FOR ABUSE]
- Seriously...
- Do you see that?
Maybe we should do a show like that.
[JUNG HYE IN'S WANTED - 20.3 PERCENT]
Here you go.
Oh, thank you so much.
- Iced americano.
- You're welcome.
Hello.
You brought the newspapers.
Where's Jung Hye In?
She's not here yet?
Yeah, I told her to come later.
The reporters are squatting
in front of her place.
She should rest a bit if we're going
to broadcast today.
Park Bo Yeon, you should stay
in touch with her.
- Don't lose her like yesterday.
- Okay.
Missions are one thing
but getting over 20 percent
is the problem.
We barely made it over last night.
Still, people will start talking today
and I think tonight will be okay.
I don't think that's enough.
I feel like last night was too rushed.
We don't even know what the mission is.
Do you have a good idea?
What gets over 20 percent rating?
Nothing gets that much even
on the public networks.
Our show has to be like a drama
that people can follow.
Though we can't plan the story,
we need a clear-cut concept.
Jung Hye In and the culprit are the
stars of this story.
So, we need to characterize this culprit.
Hello, hello...
Where should I sit? Oh, thank you.
Oh my. This is a good chair.
What is it?
We don't have to hide anything now.
We're on the same team.
If you want to be at the meetings,
please be on time.
We don't have time to repeat ourselves.
What's a good nickname for the culprit?
If we watch today's show,
we'll know what he's trying to achieve.
It's more important to let people
understand the situation.
We could just call him
"Hyun Woo's kidnapper."
I'm not sure we should make it up.
It might be better to see what people
come up with naturally on the internet.
Hey, you.
Come here.
Why are you here again?
I'm here to see you, Lieutenant Park.
I had a proposal for you.
It's win-win for both of us.
Honestly, isn't this a good
opportunity for you too?
If you get a lead before others
and catch the kidnapper
you'll get promoted, right?
Isn't it time for you to be chief?
Wait, is it way past time to be a chief?
Go if you're going to say nonsense.
Let's be completely
honest with each other.
I have this case completely in my grasp.
Gossip reporter? I'm so sick of that.
I'm going write an article
about this show.
I even have a contract.
I'm going to publish a book.
If you can get me in on this show,
I can write about all your achievements.
I can give you useful tips too.
I'll think about it.
I don't care about your book
or my achievements.
If you can give me tips and info,
you might be useful.
- Is Hye In still not in contact?
- No, not yet.
If we get proof Hyun Woo is alive,
we need to put that on air.
That's one of our show's obligations.
I understand.
I think we should continue looking into
the reason behind the missions.
Why did he want Han Sol on the show?
I don't think it was just coincidence
that it was an abused child.
If so...
did he want us to
expose that on the show?
This is why you need
to work with us on this.
Ah, yes.
So, do you have any information
on Han Sol's case?
Before the incident, you packed your bags
and fell asleep at the sauna.
- That's when Han Sol was taken?
- Yes.
Did you happen to see these people
at the sauna that day?
Or meet them before that day?
No, I don't know them at all.
I didn't see them that day either.
This girl.
Have you seen her before?
She told me that my dad
was almost at the sauna.
She said I had to run away
quickly on my own.
She said that was the only way
my mom could get away too.
That we would get caught
if were together.
She said we could meet up later.
She took my hand and I followed her.
What happened after that?
I don't know.
She gave me some banana milk.
I drank it, fell asleep, and woke up.
And I was alone in that car.
In that car trunk where
that lady found you?
Han Sol, you're really smart.
Thank you for helping me.
About Han Sol's father, Professor Kim...
he's been released.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
Thank you for your help.
Until everything is take care of,
you shouldn't go home.
Do you have a place to stay?
Until you find a place to live,
you can stay at my place.
I live at the police station anyhow
and my home will be safe.
Oh no, you really don't need to.
Someone once opened their home
to me and my mother.
I'm returning that favor,
so don't feel burdened by it.
Well, then.
Bye, Han Sol.
Well, it was definitely suicide.
There is almost no chance
it was murder.
His toxicology came back okay.
This wasn't the direct cause of death.
But, he had a large amount of pills
in his stomach.
I think he took them before dying.
What kind of pills?
It's for seizures.
It's an anti-epileptic drug.
Taking large amounts
when you don't need it
can cause you to become addicted.
There are side effects like hallucination
and loss of memory.
His medical records don't show
that he ever had seizures.
He'd never been prescribed it.
You've come to the wrong place.
No one like that lives here.
Look into Park Sae Yong's
mother's medical records.
Okay.
Also, he's a cancer patient.
- Cancer?
- Intestinal cancer.
It had spread to his whole body.
You see the surgery scar?
It's recent.
His medical records show that they cut
him open and just closed him up.
Even if he didn't commit suicide,
he wouldn't have lived much longer.
Do you think it was guilt?
No.
The live TV, the Coconut TV kidnapping,
and this suicide...
I think it's all been planned
down to every detail.
He was just able to make the decision
to commit suicide because of cancer.
For what purpose?
John Lennon was killed
by a stalker, right?
Jodie Foster's stalker attempted
to kill President Reagan.
This woman...
I happened to look into that.
That woman with the guitar is an actress
name Rebecca Schaeffer.
Her stalker shot her with a gun
for filming a scene in bed.
I'm going meet Jung Hye In
once she arrives at the station.
I want you to meet her manager
and look into her stalkers.
Okay.
You should've rested more.
Did you get some sleep?
This is better than being home.
I think I have to do something to live.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Should I go buy something?
No, I'm alright.
Hye In, you're going to pass out
at this rate.
I can wear anything from here?
Yes.
- What's this?
- Oh?
That wasn't there at the shop.
[MISSION ONE: SUCCESS]
[HYUN WOO IS ALIVE.]
I left the car door open for a moment
in the parking lot.
I had a phone call.
That was the only time.
I'll call the police and check the CCTV.
Think back carefully.
Did Park Sae Yong ever contact you
or approach you in the past?
Have you ever met Lee Ji Eun before?
No.
I've thought about it hundreds of times.
Why are they doing this to me
and why to Hyun Woo?
Did I do something wrong?
There's nothing.
I've never even met these people.
The true culprit is hiding his identity
in order to kidnap Hyun Woo.
He used Park Sae Yong's
obsession with you.
Park Sae Yong knew that he had cancer
and would be dying soon.
He was taking drugs that could cause
hallucinations and memory loss.
What about this girl?
I believe Lee Ji Eun is being
manipulated as well.
He sent a picture of them together means
he will continue to use Lee Ji Eun.
After that, she may commit suicide
like Park Sae Yong.
Or she may be murdered.
Then... the real kidnapper?
Is it someone near these two people?
There's a higher chance
it's someone close to you.
When you just heard me say this,
who was the first person you thought of?
A mother's instinct can be correct.
I can use Hyun Woo more if I need to.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
There's a meeting with advertisers.
Drop in and say hello.
I'm Cha Seung In, the detective
working on the case.
Oh, yes. Thank you for your work.
Get changed.
This one's nice.
What's this?
You can handle meeting's
with advertisers.
Do I have to do things like that?
I need to talk to her regarding the case.
You need to come, at least, once.
Don't forget what you promised me.
Thank you then.
Do you...
trust your husband?
She announced her retirement
without even letting us know.
I wondered what to do with the contract
that had six months left.
The company was leaning toward suing.
You wouldn't have had to sue.
We would have paid the breach
of contract penalty.
Still, Jung Hye In's been
with us a long time.
It's not right to do that
when people are in trouble.
That's why we made this decision.
Oh, thank you.
This show is getting
the most attention right now.
I'm sure you saw last night,
but you don't know what to expect.
Commercials in the middle of the show
will do very well.
I got so many offers today,
but I left it empty for you.
I'm relieved that I'm able
to return your goodwill.
The CCTV where you parked your car
broke a few days ago.
They haven't fixed it yet.
- Why did it have to be there?
- Yes, why?
Why did you happen to park there?
- What?
- It's strange.
It was the car you drove where
the hidden camera was found.
It was the clothes you brought where
the picture of Hyun Woo was found.
You say you don't know anything,
but we can't confirm it.
That's because I'm always with Hye In.
Don't go anywhere for the time being.
You need to stay where we can find you.
Okay.
I'm really okay even if you suspect me.
I just don't want you to lose the real
culprit while focusing on me...
We'll handle that.
I heard that Jung Hye In
had some stalkers.
Do you handle them all?
Yes, Hye In doesn't like to make
a fuss about it.
We don't report it to the police.
I have a blacklist.
Has she ever been attacked
at a fan meeting or in a busy place?
No, nothing like that.
They usually come to her house
or send weird gifts.
Was Park Sae Yong on that list?
No.
He never did anything to her
for me to know his face or name.
I don't know him at all.
Can I get that blacklist
and a list of her fan club members?
I'll email it to you right away.
I'll contact you soon.
What is it? Why are you here?
Did you get fired?
Who'd catch the criminals if I get fired?
You grew up. You're showing off now.
Why are you here?
I came to see you, Mi Ock.
Forget it. Tell me what you want.
I need help with something.
I'm resting for a year.
I have to see only
nice things for a year.
You told me to do that.
It takes ten days.
Take it with you.
Ask the department for help.
Why are you bothering me?
I don't want to do it either,
but I'm in a rush.
If you help me this once,
I'll be loyal to you forever.
I want to do everything that I can.
"It wasn't your fault.
There was nothing you could do."
I don't want to hear
anything like that again.
Take it with you.
Call me.
[MI OCK]
Yes, Mi Ock.
We're having a meeting with
the investigative team.
I'll be right there.
Did you hear from the kidnapper?
I'd probably send proof of Hyun Woo
being alive to you and not the station.
No, not yet.
You're not a good liar.
It's been years since I've seen you.
Don't pretend to know me.
Come to the meeting.
[WANTED'S SECOND MISSION
HAS BEEN EMAILED TO YOU.]
[READ IT ALONE.]
[WANTED - SECOND MISSION]
Jung Hye In,
this is Wanted's second mission.
Let's end this show.
Someone died because of it.
Hyun Woo will die.
They're not just scaring us.
They will really kill someone.
Who was it that told you to do it?
Lee Ji Eun, you're under arrest
as an accomplice for
Song Hyun Woo's kidnapping.
I'm sorry for everything.
Tell me where Hyun Woo is.
Tell me where the place in the photo is.
Even if you go there,
there won't be anything left.
Everything that's happening
on this show is real.
Jung Hye In's Wanted is starting now.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever