Subtitles by DramaFever
[Wanted's second mission
has been emailed to you.]
[Read it alone.]
[Wanted: Second Mission]
Jung Hye In, this is
Wanted's second mission.
This person is a murderer.
But no one knows about his crimes.
I want you to prove that he
is a murderer on today's show.
If you fail...
Hyun Woo will die.
[Episode 4]
Who is that man?
He looks familiar.
I think I've seen him somewhere.
Ha Dong Min.
He's been Hyun Woo's pediatrician
since he was a baby.
[Ha Dong Min]
She's right. Ha Dong Min.
Chief of the Pediatrics Department
at Soojung Hospital.
I read an article about him recently.
He's the Korean Albert Schweitzer.
He started the social welfare program
at Soojung Hospital.
He provided free health care to children
with cancer who couldn't afford it.
A person like that doesn't
sound like a murderer.
Are there articles about
medical treatment issues?
No, there was nothing like that.
There are only good things.
He's our nation's expert in
the field of pediatrics.
Especially in the field of cancer.
I made a request before
he became Chief
so he specially made time
to see Hyun Woo.
He's someone that's trustworthy.
He's been that way for
the past seven years.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
Usually, people would say
he's a skilled doctor.
Unless you're sharing secrets with him
it's odd to use the term trustworthy.
I'm only saying that he's a good person.
That's all I meant.
Oh! She started broadcasting again.
By the way,
you were great on the last show.
That child and woman
were being horribly abused.
You saved them, Jung Hye In.
What is that?
Also, the person who committed
the crime has been punished.
What... what are we going to do?
Our show...
A person died because of us.
We need to end this show.
Wait! Let's think about this.
Think about it?
There's nothing to even think about.
Yesterday, that person was exposed
as a wife and child abuser.
Right after that...
he got murdered.
A person died because of our show.
That kind of footage
can easily be produced.
He could be alive.
He might be doing this to capture
our interest and manipulate us.
What if he's really dead?
What if another person dies?
Even so...
That means we should go through
with the show even more!
- Hye In.
- Hyun Woo will die!
He's not just making threats anymore.
He is really killing people.
A person like that is with
Hyun Woo right now.
Hye In is right.
If we end this right now,
we won't be able to find Hyun Woo.
A person will have died for no reason.
Park Bo Yeon!
I'll talk to her.
I... want to quit.
I can't do it anymore.
All right, then.
You should quit if you can't do it.
It's not like I don't
understand how you feel.
- Are you okay with this, Writer Yeon?
- No.
But this is my job.
I work hard to make my money and
I'm good enough to deserve it.
This show pays a lot
and I really need that money.
What about you?
Why did you start working for this show?
I...
Should I take a guess?
You couldn't find another job
with that resume.
You wanted to grab onto this opportunity.
Still, I didn't think
it would be like this.
Someone has died so how
can all you be like this?
Whatever the reason is,
if something big has happened
you have to see it through to the end.
That's what it means
to take responsibility.
No matter what the result is.
I really don't understand it.
Forget about all the others,
but what about Hye In?
How can she be so cold?
This is all happening because of her.
That looked cold to you?
That was desperation.
She's willing to commit any sin
to get her son back.
Detective Lee, I just emailed
you the blacklist.
I will do anything. Please let me help.
Hye In, something suddenly came up.
Is it okay if I head out?
I'm sorry, at a time like this.
No, you don't need to worry about it.
I'll leave the car here and be back
before the show ends.
Call me if something comes up.
Leave immediately if
you're going to quit.
I won't hold you back.
No, I'm sorry.
Let's let the investigative team
know about this situation.
They need to find Han Sol's father's body
and look for evidence.
We should do that.
We only have seven hours left.
We have to do everything we can.
We'll need help from the police.
Are you sure you don't need to put
in an official request?
Then they will send me someone else.
I'll have to report in
about every little thing.
I wouldn't have come to you
if I wanted to do that.
So you needed someone to bother.
What if you get me fired?
I'll take care of you.
That works for me.
But, I think your job
might be in danger too.
I thought you were on vacation.
Did the head office send you?
We can't let the culprit have
his way for all ten episodes.
We needed a consultant,
so I asked her to come.
Why don't you mind your own business
and stick to your own task?
Aren't you in charge of Lee Ji Eun?
She killed someone.
You should've contacted us right away
once you heard from the culprit.
You continue to keep us out of the loop.
I'm sorry. We won't do it again.
Can we trust you on that?
Excuse me?
Director, your goal is this show
and not catching the kidnapper.
Well, I am a person in broadcasting.
I am only doing what I do best.
The criminal should be caught
by all of you.
I've traced the IP.
It's Han Sol's home.
Let's go.
Did you really do it?
You didn't, right?
A person your size can't control
a grown man and tie him up.
If you had stabbed him deeply
that many times
a beginner like you
would've hurt your hands.
Who told you to do this?
Lee Ji Eun.
You're under arrest for the murder
of Kim Woo Jin
and as an accomplice in the kidnap
of Song Hyun Woo.
You have the right to remain silent
and the right to legal counsel.
There are two possibilities.
One is that Ha Dong Min paid
someone to kill or did it himself.
The other is that is it was
a medical action that caused death.
We're going to have a hard time
getting proof for either.
We don't have time.
Park Bo Yeon, why don't you
show us your skills?
Okay.
What?
Is it possible to hack Ha Dong Min's
personal email or cell phone?
Well, I'm a white hacker.
I don't do things like that.
You don't do it or can't do it?
- Well, I can do it...
- Then do it.
Why do you think I chose you?
This show is more important
than your conscience.
What is your choice?
Do you want to stand by and watch people
die because you don't want to do this?
We have no time for this.
I just don't think I can do that.
Instead, I promise I'll
get it another way.
I'll be back.
Hey!
[Situation Report]
Can we get 500 million won
to spend on tonight's show?
500 million won?
What is it for?
We're going to use it as reward money.
It's for the person who's going to
prove that Ha Dong Min is a murderer.
It's the price for Ha Dong Min's life.
It's also the price for ratings,
500 million won.
Do it.
[The conclusive report on
Ha Dong Min's murder case]
Say what you want.
What?
You're here because you heard about
the preview from President Song.
Why aren't you saying anything?
You want to tell me not to do it.
If I told you not to, would you listen?
No, I wouldn't.
Dong Wook.
What?
We started this to find Hyun Woo.
Let's not lose him, at least.
Let's make sure to find Hyun Woo.
Why are you making me nervous?
I agreed to do this show too.
I can't try to stop it without giving
an alternate solution.
I'll take care of things,
so just do your work.
If I really feel like something
shouldn't go on air...
listen to me that one time.
Okay.
[Wanted Ha Dong Min]
[Wow! Wanted has a reward
of 500 million won.]
[Looking for tips on
Ha Dong Min, murderer]
[Wanted's reward is 500 million won]
Hey, Kim Dong Wan.
Are you happy now that you don't
have to see my face anymore?
You still have to see me
once a month, you know.
Ma'am, you really suffered
a lot all this time.
Please take care of this.
Don't leave a trace of anything behind.
Where is my Hyun Woo?
Tell me now!
Hye In, let's talk outside.
Let go of me.
She was with Hyun Woo.
She knows where Hyun Woo is
and who the kidnapper is.
Get up.
Please.
I'm begging you like this.
I was wrong for everything.
Just tell me where my Hyun Woo is.
If you tell me where Hyun Woo is
I'll do whatever I can
to keep you from being punished.
You'll do that, right?
You'll help me Lieutenant, right?
I'll use all the money I have.
I will do my best for you.
I'll put my life on the line.
I'll do everything!
So... so please.
Just tell me where Hyun Woo is.
Hyun Woo is innocent and hasn't
done anything wrong, please...
Where are you going? What did she say?
Promise me one thing.
I will go in first.
Keep that promise.
No one is in here.
Let's try to solve this again.
What is the culprit's motive?
Why did he target Ha Dong Min this time?
I'm from the criminal intelligence team.
My name is Oh Mi Ock.
Lieutenant Cha unofficially asked
me to consult on this case.
You can take a seat there.
Ha Dong Min is Hyun Woo's
pediatrician, isn't he?
Isn't this some sort of revenge
against Jung Hye In then?
The culprit had a hidden camera on her
and was around her for a long time.
Park Sae Yong took part in
the kidnapping, and he was a stalker.
What about Han Sol's family?
There is no connection to that family.
The culprit's goal could be this show.
Jung Hye In and Hyun Woo could merely
be pawns to get that accomplished.
Do you have evidence of that?
Don't make up a story.
Please continue.
Jung Hye In is an actress that
everyone in this country knows.
Her husband is the president
of a broadcast station.
Kidnapping her child
getting the public's attention
and getting a show on air.
She's the most suitable candidate.
The accomplices were people who would not
expose him and were easy to manipulate.
Why would he want to do this show?
You heard Lee Ji Eun before.
She said this about Han Sol's father.
"The person who committed the crime
has been punished."
That's what she said.
That's right.
It's not enough to call it a pattern.
He is using this show.
He wants to expose hidden wrongs
and then personally punish them.
The first episode led to Han Sol
and his mother's abuse being exposed.
Han Sol's father was revealed on air.
They made it clear that it was punishment
and murdered him.
And the second episode...
They want us to show proof that a
supposedly good doctor is a murderer.
There's one more link.
The children.
Hyun Woo was kidnapped.
Han Sol was a boy that was being abused.
Ha Dong Min is a pediatrician.
If I am correct...
the culprit isn't choosing people
to punish at random.
I think there's a chance that he believes
he has a duty to save these kids.
Has anything strange happened
with Doctor Ha Dong Min lately?
Has he fought with anyone
or had any sudden changes in behavior?
Nothing like that.
Oh, right.
About a month ago
there was a nurse
that quit very suddenly.
Are you sure you can go on your own?
This is something I have to do.
You have to go to Lee Ji Eun, don't you?
Don't expect too much
from Lee Ji Eun for now.
Still, she's the only thing
I can hold onto.
She planned to turn herself in.
We will only end up running
around like we did today.
Even if we run around...
I'm sure we'll end up one step closer.
I'm at Soojung Hospital.
Ha Dong Min will come on
the show tonight.
I'll bring him.
It's a good idea, but will he come?
Okay, I'll prepare for it then.
What happened with Lee Ji Eun?
[Pediatrics Department]
You want me to go on that show?
I'm asking as a favor?
What do you want me to do on that show?
You can address
the allegations of murder...
Murder?
Jung Hye In.
Look here, Hyun Woo's mother.
You've left your son in
my care for seven years.
I've kept your secret
for all those seven years!
Is this how you repay me?
You're going to falsely accuse me
of murder in front of the entire nation.
Then make a spectacle of me?
I have always been grateful.
That's why I'm giving you this chance.
What? Chance?
[New message]
I don't think calling you a murderer
is necessarily a false accusation.
What is this?
Why are you showing me this?
You know her, Nurse Kim Sang Mi.
We found her corpse in a house today.
And we have evidence that
you paid someone to kill her.
Get out.
It's getting hard to listen
to this nonsense.
Whether you're a murderer or not,
it has nothing to do with me.
The kidnapper told me to prove it on TV.
If I can't do that, Hyun Woo is
in danger and that's what matters.
I will put these photos
and the evidence on the show tonight.
Are you crazy?
Do you think you'll be safe?
There's only one way to stop this.
You need to come on the show, yourself.
I don't care which crime you confess to.
It can be a small crime that you
can avoid legal punishment for.
If you can do that...
I will keep this quiet.
Just like you have
always kept my secret, Doctor.
Hey!
Hang up.
Stop airing Wanted!
UCN must apologize!
Violation of human rights.
Destroying honor.
Apologize and compensate!
How are these people connected
to Ha Dong Min?
What?
Ah, I'm a reporter.
You could do this for a hundred days.
It won't work.
Tell me if you have a story.
I'll write an article.
Is it good? Give some to me too.
- Oh, that's good.
- So...
Your child got free cancer treatment
thanks to Doctor Ha Dong Min?
Yes, that's right.
I had stopped working
because my child was so sick.
My husband is disabled, as well.
I had been borrowing money
since the first surgery.
When the cancer relapsed...
we had pretty much given up.
Then you heard from
the welfare department?
What were the conditions?
They looked at the medical treatment
we'd received and our income bracket.
Things like that.
I just had to submit
a few documents as proof.
The paperwork was done
by the welfare department.
Later, we got the first examination
from Doctor Ha Dong Min.
That's when we signed a consent form.
A consent form?
You know how you sign one
when you get surgery?
These are kids who relapse or
don't respond well to chemotherapy.
It had a list of all the drugs
they would be using.
I think it was in case the results of the
treatment were not good.
They were concerned problems would
arise even though they trying to do good.
Basically, it was a form absolving them
of responsibility of the results.
Something like that.
If you wouldn't sign it,
would they not treat your child?
But... who wouldn't sign it?
They're willing to grasp any straw.
Is your child all better now?
No.
My child was getting much better
during the first month.
Then things suddenly got bad.
Breathing became very difficult...
He said we started treatment too late.
If we had only started the treatment
a little earlier.
It would have worked.
Still, it was because of that welfare
program that she got in the hospital.
My Ji Won didn't suffer when she died.
Reporter Jang.
Please write a nice article.
Doctor Ha Dong Min
is a really good person.
My daughter left so quickly like that.
He saved so many sick children
from poor families.
Please make sure to fix this mistake.
People need to know
that he's a good person.
Everything that happens
on this show is reality.
We are following the demands of the
person who kidnapped my son, Hyun Woo.
That is why we are
doing this show tonight.
Jung Hye In's Wanted starts now.
Where's Ha Dong Min? He's not here yet?
Hold on. A car is coming in now.
He's here. I'll be right up with him.
When I saw the previews...
I felt very wronged and angry, of course.
I was scared too.
Then, I recalled a case that had
bothered me for many years.
If someone is accusing me
of being a murderer...
I thought it must be about that incident.
Are you saying you have
killed someone before?
No, it's not like that.
I was a first year resident.
A patient that I was treating died.
It was a seven year old
with leukemia.
I gave that patient injections of
Cytarabine and Vincristine all at once.
You cannot differentiate these two
drugs just by looking at them.
Cytarabine is injected into the spine.
Vincristine is injected into the vein.
If Vincristine is injected into the spine
the central nervous system
becomes severely damaged.
You become paralyzed.
Then you die.
So, you made an error
and mixed up the two medications.
And a seven-year-old leukemia patient
ended up dying?
That's what the patient's
parent's claimed.
The hospital and I claimed
that we had not made an error.
We claimed that it was
an adverse reaction to the Cytarabine.
It the trial, the hospital won.
The symptoms were similar.
What's the truth?
It is true that I made a mistake.
I am very sorry to
the parents of that patient.
I wanted to tell the truth now.
I will personally pay for what I've done.
Wow, he's smart.
Isn't that a big crime?
It's clearly his fault
that the patient died.
But, he won't get punished legally.
If he was a first year resident,
it's been over 15 years.
Those parents can't even sue him.
Let's put up the kid's pictures.
Let's get started.
Talk about the children.
Take a sip of water when you're ready.
Thank you to Doctor Ha Dong Min
for your courage.
However, there was no intent and it was
a medical accident.
It has been more than 15 years.
Can we really call Doctor Ha Dong Min
a murderer for that?
These children are a part of the program
led by Doctor Ha Dong Min.
Through a social welfare program for
children with leukemia
they are children who have been
receiving free treatment.
Over  150 children have
received free treatment
for leukemia in the past 3 years.
We're coming now.
If that doctor manages to run away,
you're all dead tomorrow.
- Stay alert and keep watch.
- Yes, sir.
Park Ji Won, Jung So Yeon,
Jang Young Min.
Han Jae Woo, Kim Min Sung, Choi Eun Ho.
These six children that you can no longer
see on the screen
are children that died while receiving
this treatment.
All of them improved very quickly,
in the beginning.
Later, they experienced difficulty
breathing and swelling of the head.
They died of severe organ failure.
Gosh, please.
[Consent Form for Cancer Treatment]
Thank you! Thank you so much.
This is the consent form that had to be
signed in order to receive treatment.
They had to agree to
a new drug called NLC136.
It was a drug developed by an American
company three years ago.
It has currently been recalled
due to adverse side effects.
It has gone back into re-development.
I realize your situation that you have
to do what the kidnapper says.
Isn't this going too far?
It is you who has gone too far, Doctor.
To poor children and orphans,
sick ones, at that.
Under the guise of treating them
you ran illegal experiments
using humans.
Why are you people doing this to me?
Do you have proof?
They're just test subjects.
Have you seen an experiment end
just because one rat dies?
Children who are sick and suffering
with leukemia...
are nothing but lab rats to you?
Because of your illegal human tests,
six people have died.
- Do you admit it?
- No.
That's not my voice!
I've never said such things.
What do you think is in this bag?
No, no!
How long are you going to live
just looking after patients?
Check your account tomorrow.
If you're satisfied,
then don't come to work tomorrow.
I'll take care of your resignation.
Today...
Kim Sang Mi was a nurse
at Soojung Hospital
and disappeared last month.
Today, she was found
in a home in this state.
Who and why did someone
try to kill Kim Sang Mi?
We will now introduce the person who
gave us the answer to this question.
How are you...
How am I still alive?
When the man you sent was choking me,
I thought I was going to die too.
If Jung Hye In had arrived any later,
I would be dead now.
Kim Sang Mi.
In the recording we just heard,
was Ha Dong Min trying to bribe you?
Yes, he was.
I told him to stop the tests.
That I would tell the parents of the
children who died and authorities.
Then I noticed money had
been deposited into my account.
He said I was now an accomplice too.
He threatened me.
So, you tried to put a stop
to these horrible experiments.
But, you were too afraid.
Yes.
I should have been more courageous
and told the world.
I'm sorry.
A burglar came into my home and
took everything in my computer.
He told me he'd kill me
if I didn't leave the country.
I was very conflicted.
I was more scared of that
than being named an accomplice.
You...
You promised me!
You made a promise to those kids too.
To save their lives...
Your secret will no longer
remain a secret.
Wait and see.
If you have something to say,
just say it.
I'm sorry for not mentioning
Kim Sang Mi beforehand...
The secret that the doctor's referring to
is about Hyun Woo, isn't it?
He's actually your ex-husband's son.
His bloodline is of the SG Group.
That has nothing to do with the show.
The culprit happened to focus on
Hyun Woo's doctor.
Ha Dong Min knows that
and is now threatening you.
That has nothing to do with the show?
You had to spill your secrets to me
because of this show.
If Ha Dong Min tells everyone
there will be more interest
in that than in the show.
SG won't let it go either.
Ha Dong Min, President Song,
Joon Gu, and me.
Who else knows about this?
That's it.
All right, I'll take care of this.
Things might get difficult for you.
You should be prepared.
What are you planning to do?
Let me try to see if it's possible first.
Let's talk tomorrow.
We haven't heard about Hyun Woo yet?
Gosh! Oh, Writer Yeon.
Put a cop on Kim Sang Mi
or check on her yourself.
She went through all that
and still came on the show.
We should protect her to the end.
Of course.
- Executive Director.
- Yes?
Check your account tomorrow.
If you're satisfied,
then don't come to work tomorrow.
I'll take care of your resignation.
What if I'm not satisfied?
What?
I'll have to quit my job.
If this gets exposed,
I could be named an accomplice.
We could end this cleanly
if I leave the country.
Hey, was this your goal
from the beginning?
Just tell right here and now.
How much are you giving me?
It's me.
Why didn't you tell me that Kim Sang Mi
threatened Ha Dong Mi?
It's not really important.
Why does the truth matter?
What matters is what
the viewers want to see.
You did a good job.
By the way, Writer Yeon.
Before the show, Jung Hye In told me that
the 500 million won reward was mine.
That's why I came at all.
That money is really mine, right?
Yes, of course.
There's a procedure to it and everything.
I'll let you know.
Bringing up money at a time like this...
I must seem no different than
that trash, Ha Dong Min.
No, you don't need to explain to me.
There was a medical accident that
occurred at the first place I worked at.
I took responsibility and testified
for the patient.
The hospital won the case though.
I ended up fired because
I was a whistle-blower.
After that, it became very hard to find
a job for a long time.
Even if you expose the truth,
the world doesn't change.
Only my life changes.
Here he comes!
Move out of the way! Move!
Doctor!
Do you admit you committed a crime?
Bring back my Ji Won!
Bring my Ji Won back to me!
Bring my Ji Won back!
You bring her back!
My Ji Won... my Ji Won...
My Ji Won.
My Ji Won...
You weren't forced to do it.
You did it of your own volition.
Okay.
Other people...
were either crazy.
Or they deserved to die.
Let's say that you believed
that they could've been saved.
What about Song Hyun Woo?
Why did you do it?
He's only seven years old.
The age where kids cry if they don't
see their moms for a night.
He's too young for you to leave him
with some punk playing with his life!
Tell me.
At least, tell me where
that place in the picture is.
Even if you go there...
there's nothing there.
Wow, how long did it take
for them to start talking?
It hasn't even been two hours yet.
I told him to stick around
after the show.
Why is he here?
Why is he even bothering?
He really doesn't listen well.
Are you still expecting him to?
Who can control him?
Look at me.
I haven't had time off in years
and I got dragged into this.
You've been mixed up with
that idiot since he was a rookie
and now you're suffering.
You're not even getting paid right now.
No kidding.
Well, you know
I had a senior like that too.
[Hye In, sorry I'm still
taking care of something.]
[Sorry, I can't drive you.]
You too.
You punk!
You shouldn't have.
Tell me, tell me.
[UCN Wanted team]
[People connected to missions.]
This is Oh Mi Ock.
Thank you for letting me know.
Yes, bye.
Did you get anything?
No, she won't talk.
I think you can get rid of these two.
Kim Sang Mi was involved because she was
trying to extort money from Ha Dong Min.
I investigated him
and he's not connected at all.
Besides the fact that he was paid money
and hired to kill Kim Sang Mi.
Is something wrong?
Seung In.
Jo Nam Chul has been released on parole.
What did you say?
I wasn't going to tell you.
I'm telling you now so that you don't
cause trouble if you find out later.
Focus on the case.
It's over with anyway.
What do you mean it's over!
[Mister Policeman, thank you.
From, Han Sol.]
[Lieutenant Cha Seung In.]
This is Cha Seung In.
The kidnapper sent an address.
He says to come to that address to see
proof that Hyun Woo is alive.
I'll be right there.
Don't go on your own and wait there.
[Research and Development]
Subtitles by DramaFever