Jung Hye In,
this is Wanted's second mission.
He is a murderer.
You need to prove he is
a murderer on today's show.
If you fail to do so, Hyun Woo will die.
You are under arrest for murder and
accomplice to the kidnap Song Hyun Woo.
I understand how you must feel,
but aren't you going too far?
Doctor, you are the one
who committed atrocious acts.
To children of poor families and orphans,
sick ones, at that...
You promised to treat them
but used them as subjects
in illegal clinical tests.
Your secret will no longer
remain a secret.
Look forward to it.
The kidnapper sent an address.
He wants me to come to that address
for proof that Hyun Woo is alive.
You can't film this.
This is a murder crime scene
and you cannot film it.
Tell us who the suspect is.
If we can't do the mission now,
Hyun Woo will be in danger.
After the show last night...
we were given proof
that Hyun Woo is alive.
However, a body was
discovered at that location.
The third mission was also found
at that same location.
We will now put out a public wanted
notice for the murder suspect.
Don't come any closer!
Jo Nam Chul!
The murderer Jo Nam Chul
has been arrested.
You think you're so great, don't you?
[Episode 6]
[FIGHTING WITH HUSBAND]
[SHOWER]
[SLEEPING HYE IN]
What are you doing in here?
Kyung Hoon.
Hye In, you have to understand.
I love you. You know that, right?
You liked having me by your side too.
You trusted me more
than you trusted Jung Ho.
Yes, I understand how
you feel Kyung Hoon.
Why don't we go outside and talk?
Can you let me go first? It hurts.
I'm determined to find Hyun Woo for you.
The detectives keep
bringing up the stalkers.
Besides the one who died
I think they have
something to do with it.
Yesterday, I went after all of them
and questioned them.
Oh... my stomach.
- My stomach hurts.
- What is it?
Kyung Hoon.
You know where my medicine is.
Can you bring it to me?
I must be in shock.
Oh, my stomach...
[LIEUTENANT CHA SEUNG IN]
[JUNG HYE IN]
- Are you awake now?
- What about Young Gwan?
He got a little more injured than you.
He's getting treated over there.
Is he very injured?
No, he got a CT,
but they didn't find anything.
And Jo Nam Chul?
What happened to him?
He escaped.
Hey! Seung In!
Hey, why are you here?
What about the car that hit us?
It was a hit and run.
Do you know what kind of car it was?
There was no CCTV or black box
footage from the other cars.
There are no witnesses either.
We'll keep looking into it.
What about Kim Yang Hee's house?
Lieutenant Park and Detective Yoo
are over there now.
There's nothing there.
Hey, kid! Take a deep breath.
It was a pretty big accident.
Make sure you're not hurt anywhere.
Is that what's important right now?
Jo Nam Chul's face was
seen across the country.
He won't last long.
[MISSED CALLS - JUNG HYE IN]
The customer is not available
to take your call...
Chief, who's with the broadcast team now?
No one's there right now.
They're supposed to call once they get
the next mission.
How can you not have anyone there?
[JUNG HYE IN'S MANAGER]
The customer is not available
to take your call...
No, we can't get in
touch with her either.
President Song says she didn't
come home last night either.
Jung Hye In!
Jung Hye In.
I found a hidden camera in my home
like the one that was in my car.
Do you think it was your husband?
That's what I thought at first,
but my manager...
[SLEEPING HYE IN]
[PUTTING ON MAKEUP]
I told you to always know
where Jung Hye In is!
I'm sorry.
This isn't the first time Jung Hye In
has acted on her own.
She doesn't contact you
when she has a problem.
Doesn't that mean you're
no good as a director?
[HYEIN0331]
This is Senior Hye In's email.
There are no emails from the kidnapper.
Is there a possibility that
the manager kidnapped Hyun Woo?
We can't be sure of anything yet.
He could be an accomplice
like Lee Ji Eun.
He could be acting on his own.
If the kidnapper didn't take
Hye In as a part of his plan
you will receive a mission today.
Because we won't be able to do the show
unless we find Hye In by 10:00 p.m.
Hyun Woo could be in danger.
We need to let the kidnapper know
that Hye In is missing.
Don't take any action until
we contact you.
We need to come up with a plan too.
We need to buy some time.
Jung Hye In's safety comes first.
We can't provoke the kidnapper.
We must minimize the risk of having
an incident come from this.
Chief, the manager went home for
his belongings this morning and left.
We checked the CCTV
and he didn't take
Jung Hye In's car.
Even though you fooled me,
I understand, Hye In.
I'm sure you were taken aback.
You just don't understand
your own feelings yet.
You're probably confused
by your emotions right now.
I will find Hyun Woo
and bring him back myself.
When I do, you will see that
I'm the one you need the most.
All right, keep looking and report to me.
What did he say?
The manager definitely ran.
If he took Jung Hye In,
he probably hid her somewhere or...
We've found Jung Hye In's car.
Where? What about Jung Hye In?
You've been parked here since last night?
Yes, it's been here since
around 9:00 p.m. last night.
- I'll take a look at the video.
- Sure.
[JUNG HYE IN: CURRENTLY MISSING]
[JUNG HYE IN]
Jung Hye In, where are you?
Director Shin Dong Wook?
Who are you?
What is it that you want?
I need to go on air and say something.
On air?
About Im Hyung Soon and the detective
from seven years ago...
I didn't kill him by myself.
I was hired to do it.
Why didn't you tell anyone that
seven years ago?
Do you know what kind of people they are?
Even the prosecutors ignored
what I said
and covered it up.
Now that you've stirred things up again,
those people are trying to kill me.
Whether I get caught by the police
or go on the run...
I will be killed by them.
They were the ones who
caused the car accident last night.
I want to go on your show and
tell people everything I know.
I want everyone to be watching them.
Even if I have to live in jail forever,
at least I'll be alive.
And if I do end up dying,
I get to hurt them.
I'll do it.
I'll do it but you
have to let Hye In go.
How can I trust you?
How can I trust that Hye In is alive?
There's nothing you can do
even if you don't trust me.
Fine. Consider her dead.
Jung Hye In is locked up
and dying in a place nobody knows about.
You may find her later on.
But if she can't do her show at 10:00,
her son will die.
Sounds fun.
How do I know you'll let
Hye In go once I put you on air?
You have no choice in that matter.
You have to trust me.
That's not true.
I could put you away now and the police
could find Jung Hye In.
Jung Hye In is not alone right now.
Jung Hye In will be dead before
the police even get there.
Who was Jo Nam Chul's closest friend
while he was in prison?
If he were to go to anyone for help,
it would be Park Gwang Hyung.
Park Gwang Hyung, as in
a member of the Snow gang?
Welcome.
Park Gwang Hyun is inside, right?
Who are you?
I need to talk to him so move.
He's not here right now. Please leave.
Hey, get him!
You punk!
Who are you?
What's going on?
All of you, get out.
I didn't come here to see you.
I want to talk quietly.
Don't get yourself into trouble
for no reason.
It's been a long time.
Where's Jo Nam Chul?
Get out.
Go on now.
I don't know where he is either.
When's the last time you heard from him?
I heard from him about a week ago,
saying that he was getting out.
He asked me for
Im Hyung Soon's number
so I helped him out.
I didn't think he'd kill him.
He didn't say anything in prison about
Im Hyun Soon or anyone else?
We did go in together seven years ago.
He found out I was a gang member
and gave me a lot of prison money.
So, I asked him what it was for.
He said he had a favor to ask of me.
He wanted me to get
rid of a body for him.
A body?
It was hidden at
a deserted airport in Incheon.
He wasn't able to finish
that job before coming in.
He said the person who hired him
would throw a fit.
Was it Jo Nam Chul
who killed that person?
I don't know and I didn't ask.
Get your act together.
You have to find Jung Hye In,
she has been kidnapped.
If you can't find her today,
Hyun Woo will be in danger too.
What are you trying to say?
About Senior Sang Shik's case
and Jo Nam Chul's parole...
We may have a new lead,
but that's for later.
Don't lose focus.
Jo Nam Chul was the mission.
Jo Nam Chul and Im Hyung Soon.
Both of them, the unknown body,
and Hyun Woo may all be connected.
You're right about that.
You're thinking that the body
has something to do
with Senior Sang Shik's case, right?
I'll look into that.
Right now, just focus
on finding Jung Hye In.
You got it... okay?
[DRESSING ROOM A]
I will put you on air
and help reduce your sentence.
Only if you tell me
where Hye In is right now.
After you put me on air
and reduce my sentence
I'll tell you where Jung Hye In is.
Do you know what I hate
more than anything else?
When someone damages what's mine.
When someone steals what's mine.
Even if you succeed in getting on air
if you hurt even one finger,
I will kill you myself.
I'll give you the 7:00 p.m. news slot.
Do a special live show.
Okay.
You have to stay where
I can see you before the show.
You told us to prepare a show for you.
How can we do that
if you hold us hostage?
Then one person has to stay here with me.
The moment the cops get involved,
you can consider that person dead.
You.
I can't make a show without a writer.
I'll stay behind.
Go on, get the show ready.
You have to save Hyun Woo.
Your coffee's ready.
- Do you need a carry-out container?
- Yes.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Don't forget to take your coffee.
Right, thank you.
Are you... alright?
Excuse me?
It seemed like something was wrong.
No, I'm fine.
[LIEUTENANT CHA SEUNG IN]
What are you doing?
That will put Hye In in danger.
I'm doing this because she's in danger.
We can't leave things like this.
We don't know if he's telling the truth.
It's because we don't know...
He could be telling the truth,
and that's why.
What?
- Is it because you want high ratings?
- Writer Yeon!
We already hit 30 percent
with our show last night.
No matter what,
our show will be legendary.
But, now you got this extra add-on?
Do you think broadcasting is
like a blog or something?
What's the problem?
Your show is inflammatory and
it puts lives on the line.
Now, we have to skip the news for a day?
Does that make any sense?
How are you any different
than the criminals?
The mission has arrived.
I connected my phone so that I could
see Hye In's emails and messages.
It came in through email.
"I enjoyed yesterday's show."
"You requested that
we expose your crime."
"We will grant that request
for the fourth mission."
"Your former husband
did not die in a car accident."
"Find out how he died."
Mom.
- Mom, it's so dark.
- Hyun Woo!
Hyun Woo.
Jung Hye In?
Who are you?
You're alive.
I'll be back.
Wait! Wait, don't leave.
Open the door for me.
I have to get out of here.
Please help me!
[JO NAM CHUL]
[IM HYUNG SOON, KIM YANG HEE,
PARK GWANG HYUNG]
[BODY REMOVAL?]
Senior...
Kim Yang Hee has disappeared.
Have you tracked her phone?
Her phone is off.
Get her phone records
and credit card records as well.
Yes, I just got back from
the cyber investigations team.
Once Jo Nam Chul disappeared
they took her hard drive
and went through emails.
There was nothing about
a hiding place or future plans.
There were no pictures of
any locations either.
- Okay.
- Here are the records.
There's nothing in
her email or hard drive.
There's no other phone
in her house either.
Then they didn't contact
each another after his escape.
There could a place they decided on
when she saw him in prison.
It could be a place they prepared in
advance before he was paroled.
They could've agreed to meet there
if anything happened.
Perhaps, she went there after
seeing the news of the escape.
She used her credit card in Incheon
a lot in the past six months.
- Taxi and bus fares.
- Incheon?
We'll head over to Incheon and
check out wherever she used her card.
You're not even in good shape.
Why don't you just back off here?
I'm fine.
[HAM TAE YOUNG CAR ACCIDENT]
Please.
Please let me find something suspicious.
What's wrong with you today?
I thought you were a good worker
who didn't get emotional.
Don't worry about it.
You're acting strange too, Director.
Isn't it more normal to be abnormal
in a situation like this?
We need to finish this show
within 30 minutes.
Writer Yeon, call the police as
soon as the live show starts.
I understand.
I'll take care of the broadcast,
so focus on getting Hye In back safely.
Joon Gu's not picking up the phone.
I'm going to go get Jo Nam Chul.
Jo Nam Chul.
Jo Nam Chul?
Joon Gu!
Joon Gu...
Joon Gu.
Joon Gu!
Are you okay?
I'm very hurt.
The bleeding won't stop.
I can't move either.
Really?
Yes.
Were you the one who brought me here?
No, it was my boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
As long as the broadcast station
does what he asks...
he said he will let you go.
I will do whatever you want.
Anything you want.
I can get you whatever you need.
The people at the station
will listen to me.
I'm sorry...
Once he got on air safely,
he was really going to let you go.
It's past 7:00 p.m.
and he's still not on.
I think something went wrong.
Just open the door, for now.
Come inside and talk to me. I won't run.
Let's talk. Let's just talk.
Put the knife down.
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
I won't run away.
I can't even move.
I'm sorry. I really am sorry.
I'm just...
My boyfriend was framed
and he was framed
seven years ago too.
He went to prison for murder.
He said they framed him again.
He said no one would listen to him.
Not the prosecutor,
and not even his own lawyer.
By any chance...
are you talking about Jo Nam Chul?
There was a secret place
that only we knew about.
He left a letter for me there.
He said he would go on TV
and tell his side of the story.
That's why he brought you here.
The broadcast station must
not have done it for him.
I... I will look into it.
I will look into it and tell
them to do what you want.
You have me hostage right now.
You have a knife too.
I can't even move.
All I need to do is make one phone call.
I won't tell them where I am.
You said you were going to let me go
after the show anyway.
Killing me is not the goal.
What's important is rectifying
this wrong against Jo Nam Chul.
2100.
6572.
This is Jung Hye In.
Where are you? Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm all right.
Is Jo Nam Chul going on air
as he requested?
Keep talking. I'm in Incheon now.
Do you know where you are?
Is it the place where
we found Han Sol?
Yes, it is.
Yes, Incheon South Pier.
It's where we found the boy
in the trunk.
We'll go in first.
Please send back-up quickly.
Hands up!
Police! Drop the knife.
Have you received proof
that Hyun Woo is alive?
There has to be a reason
why the kidnapper was near
this container for the first mission.
Jo Nam Chul was someone we found
through the kidnapper's mission too.
Jo Nam Chul.
Jo Nam Chul committed murder.
Then kept the personal effects
of the people he killed.
It's evidence, so why?
It could be like a trophy.
Or if someone else is involved...
it would be insurance.
[HAM TAE YOUNG]
[JUNG HYE IN]
You say these belong to the people
Jo Nam Chul murdered?
That's not possible.
My husband was in a car accident...
The kidnapper has been choosing people
even before the show started.
He may have targeted them beforehand.
What is the common thread
between the three of you?
You need to think about that for us.
[DETECTIVE LEE YOUNG CHUL]
Hello, I have a few questions to ask you.
I heard that you were the lead on
a car accident seven years ago.
I wanted to know what the scene
of the accident was like.
How is Executive Director Choi?
How is he doing?
He wasn't hurt too badly.
He's in shock so he's not awake.
The police are waiting to take his
statement.
If he got stabbed like that,
there must have been a fight.
Then he must have seen the killer.
He may have.
I think they could catch
the killer faster than we think.
Today's show is the problem.
Hye In will just barely make it here
in time for her live show.
Even right after the accident
and over the past seven years
there has never been any suspicion.
I looked everywhere
and there's not even a rumor.
What about Bo Yeon?
She talked to the detective on the case.
He said the same thing.
We don't have enough time.
Hye In asked for him to expose her crime
and this is the mission he gave.
Hye In might have the key
to solving this mission.
We have five seconds to go.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Everything on this show is real.
We are doing this show at the request of
the person who has kidnapped my son.
Jung Hye In's Wanted is starting now.
You may all be wondering why I'm standing
in front of the camera in this state.
I will explain that in a moment.
The kidnapper made one promise
when he demanded we make this show.
He was to provide proof
of Hyun Woo's life
every time we completed a mission.
However...
Upon completion of yesterday's show,
I have not received any proof.
I cannot continue on
with this show in this situation.
I am demanding the
promise be kept, immediately.
Do you think this will work?
She has to try.
If Hyun Woo is dead...
there is no reason to do this show.
If he is alive,
the kidnapper will make a move.
It was the right move to start
today's show like this.
We need to confirm that we are
communicating with the kidnapper.
Mom.
Sing that song for your mom.
The flower petals move my heart.
The flower petals brings
tears to my eyes.
Beautiful memories.
Blue skies.
I am taking it all in.
I kept my promise.
Show Hyun Woo to the camera.
The viewers need to know.
Child, do not be weak.
Don't carry your sadness alone in life.
Dad, where are you going?
Live with a heart like yours.
The biggest star...
The kidnapper didn't alter his voice.
I'm not sure if Jung Hye In's
provocations from yesterday are working.
Or if it was intentional.
I'm going to the station.
I want to see the crime scene
for Jo Nam Chul.
Seung In.
Other detectives are
already investigating.
Trust them.
Rest even though it's hard to rest.
At this rate, you'll pass out
before you catch the culprit.
I'm okay.
I'm not okay with it!
You're acting just like Senior Sang Shik
was back then.
All right.
Stay here.
Now... I will reveal today's mission.
[JUNG HYE IN'S FORMER HUSBAND
DID NOT DIE IN A CAR ACCIDENT.]
[FIND OUT HOW HE DIED.]
Many of you already know.
After my first marriage
my husband died in a car accident
within our first year of marriage.
I met my current husband
afterward and got married.
For today's mission...
I must reveal that my former husband's
cause of death was not a car accident.
Are you watching it?
I want the PR and legal teams
gathered within the hour.
Yesterday night...
Jo Nam Chul kidnapped
and held me hostage.
He made a demand to the broadcast station
asking for a special live show.
He was hired seven years ago
to murder the detective.
He confessed that to the authorities.
He claimed that the prosecutors
covered it up.
Im Hyung Soon was said to have
received the same job offer.
Unexpectedly, our show brought
attention to that old case.
Jo Nam Chul claimed that the person
who hired him was trying to kill him.
He wanted to reveal the truth
to the entire country.
We didn't have any
decent footage for today.
If viewers can't handle it,
they can change the channel.
We can see the results tomorrow.
If you do this, the threshold for what
viewers expect just goes up.
How do you plan on handling that?
Worry about tomorrow when it comes.
We have to succeed today.
You're going too far!
If you continue down this path,
people won't be curious about Hyun Woo.
They will only tune in to this show
to watch something outrageous.
I'm thinking of only three things.
Mission complete, 20 percent ratings,
and a happy ending.
I don't care why they're watching.
What?
You said I didn't have any expectations
from you as a human being.
That's why we work well, right?
What about it?
I was wrong. Now, I see clearly.
If you work with people
who have no humanity...
I could be held hostage or
the Executive Director could be stabbed.
It all becomes good footage.
We're not people to you.
We're just like tools, right?
Right before the live show,
Jo Nam Chul was found murdered.
At that same time...
I was captured and did not know
what the mission was.
Inside the storage unit
Jo Nam Chul locked me in
I discovered an important clue
in solving the mission.
These flight tickets are something only
my husband and I knew about.
At the time of that accident,
I was...
I was five weeks pregnant.
My former husband said to me...
He wanted to have our son,
leave everything behind
and live in France.
He was a second generation billionaire.
He didn't want Hyun Woo to grow up
lonely and empty like he had.
So, why?
These were not found anywhere
in his belongings.
These tickets were not found in our home.
Why were they found in
Jo Nam Chul's storage unit?
First mission's location, Jo Nam Chul,
and Hye In are all connected.
Leaving that body in a similar position
as Senior Sang Shik was planned too.
What's the one thing
that connects all of that?
That unknown body that
the gangster boss took care of...
We should look into that first.
Jo Nam Chul is dead now.
This is everything I know, so far.
Just like Hyun Woo's kidnapper has said.
I do not think that my ex-husband's death
was just a car accident.
Jo Nam Chul may have murdered him.
There could be another
explanation as well.
In order to find solid evidence,
we will need a little more time.
If that is what
Hyun Woo's kidnapper wants...
I will... discover the truth.
These are the other items that
were found in the storage unit.
We need to find out how these items are
connected to Jo Nam Chul.
Please call in if you have information
on these items.
Why did you do it?
When you were being taken from the room,
you were really being kidnapped.
Your body wouldn't be frozen
with terror if it were acting.
You must have realized out that it was
Park Sae Yong who kidnapped you.
When you met the person who got
Park Sae Yong to kidnap you...
what did he say to you?
How is it?
Are you able to manage?
It's probably harder than you thought.
Being in there.
Did your mother come by?
It doesn't matter.
So, she didn't.
We did speak to her.
You were on TV too.
I told you that it doesn't matter.
Do you hate your mother?
Or do you hate someone else for making
you and your mom live that way?
Before your dad passed away...
I noticed that he received treatment
for depression and alcoholism.
Did he hit you and your mother,
by any chance?
Is that why you said people
like Han Sol's dad should die?
Is that why you tried
to help them escape?
Don't talk about what
you know nothing about!
My dad?
My dad is not that kind of person.
My dad.
My dad was the only person
who believed me.
The world made my dad that way!
Can you tell me what happened?
Do you know who this person is?
Is he an employee here?
This guy!
He works at the cafe across the street.
I go there often.
Have you ever spoken to him?
Just to say hello to each other.
We heard he works here.
Oh, it's him.
If you have his resume,
can we take a look at it?
Yes, sure.
He hasn't even been here very long
and he suddenly quit on me.
I guess he caused trouble.
Hold on.
Here you go.
Na Soo Hyun.
Sorry. Excuse me for a moment.
This is because you stole my stuff
and used it on your show.
Then totally ignored me.
It's all Director Shin Dong Wook's
fault, so just know that.
Are you feeling all right?
I'm all right.
You should go home and rest.
Don't worry about me.
Why don't you go home and rest?
If you go anywhere or if the kidnapper
contacts you, call me first.
Even if nothing is wrong,
contact me every hour.
Okay.
I don't want to spend time looking
for you every time we do our show.
Okay... that's enough.
Today's mission...
Do you think we succeeded?
It has to be.
My Hyun Woo has to be safe.
He didn't say to provide evidence.
This could have been extent
of the kidnapper's intent.
My Hyun Woo.
When I was trying to stop
Ha Dong Min's lawyer...
I agreed to give him up to SG Group.
If I knew I was going to expose it today,
I wouldn't have made that agreement.
I would have protected him
until the very end.
Saving his life was the priority.
You did what you had to do.
Hyun Woo.
[UNKNOWN CALLER]
Mom. It's me, Hyun Woo.
Subtitles by DramaFever