Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 7]
Hyun Woo.
Mom. It's me, Hyun Woo.
Are you listening to me?
That man might find me soon.
Come find me.
The battery is running out.
I only have five percent left.
Hyun Woo.
Mom will come for you.
Just get out of there.
Get out of there for now.
The doors are locked.
The front doors are chained up.
Is someone there with you?
How many people are there?
One person. He comes every night.
Where is that person?
Are you hiding now?
Hyun Woo, hide that phone now.
But don't hang up.
Hyun Woo.
It's okay. Just come out.
What is it? What's wrong?
[Hyun Woo escaped. On the phone.]
Mom, I'm on the second floor and
there's a really big swimming pool.
There's no water.
There's garbage piled everywhere.
What else? What else do you see?
[Through the window]
Are there windows?
Look for some windows
you can go out of.
They're too high up. I can't reach them.
Hyun Woo, you have to find a window
that you can leave from.
If it's locked, break it.
Get out, find an adult, and ask for help.
[Jeongneung Blue Swim Club]
Hyun Woo, what happened?
Mom, there's a sign here that says
Jeongneung Blue Swim Club.
Hyun Woo!
Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo managed to escape and call.
He's still locked inside a building
with the kidnapper.
It seems to be the Jeongneung Blue
Sports Center.
We're going to head there now.
I'll do it.
Go on in.
I can't see.
The pool on the second floor.
- Hyun Woo!
- Song Hyun Woo!
Hyun Woo!
Look somewhere else. Let's split up.
- Will you be okay on your own?
- Yes, go.
I'm going down to the basement.
Call me if anything happens.
Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo, Hyun Woo!
Hyun Woo!
- Young Gwan.
- Okay.
Jung Hye In, where are you?
Are you alone?
Leave your phone on.
If anything happens,
shout and let me know where you are.
Hyun Woo!
I'm across the third floor stairwell.
I hear something.
Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo!
Mom!
Let me take a look at you, Hyun Woo.
Are you hurt at all?
Are you in pain?
Mom, Mom!
Mom!
Mom, Mom, Mom...
Mom, Mom!
Mom!
Jung Hye In, Jung Hye In.
Young Gwan.
He escaped through the third floor window
opposite the stairwell with Hyun Woo.
Jung Hye In has been hurt.
Tell back-up what happened and
block off all escape routes.
Jung Hye In, Jung Hye In...
Jung Hye In!
Are you awake now?
My Hyun Woo went that way...
The police are looking for him.
They can't have gotten very far.
[Blocked Number]
Jung Hye In, you have completed
your fourth mission.
I assume you've confirmed
that Hyun Woo is alive.
Go back now and wait for
your next mission.
No!
Na Soo Hyun, 29 years old.
Just before Jo Nam Chul's estimated time
of death at 6:40 p.m.
he was caught on UCN's CCTV.
The kidnapper that Jung Hye In
saw during Hyun Woo's escape
was confirmed to be him.
We found the person that has Hyun Woo.
Na Soo Hyun.
I see it wasn't in the plans for
Na Soo Hyun to be exposed now.
Na Soo Hyun was the one who killed
Han Sol's father, wasn't it?
You, Na Soo Hyun, and Park Sae Yong...
how are you three connected?
You started meeting Park Sae Yong
one month before Hyun Woo was kidnapped.
Na Soo Hyun started working at the cafe
by UCN two months before the kidnapping.
When was this entire plan made?
Has his place of residence been found?
His place of residence was unknown,
so his resident registry was canceled.
What about his family?
He currently has no family.
Both his parents died in an accident when
he was 16 years old.
Nine years before he entered the army,
his six year old sister died of illness.
He has a brother four years older.
But, he was reported missing
seven years ago.
His case is still unsolved.
I'm sorry.
If only I had caught him,
Jo Nam Chul could've made his statement.
And Hyun Woo...
Is it okay for you to be
discharged so quickly?
I'm fine.
I only needed to get some stitches.
I just need to be careful moving around.
I don't understand how could that be.
What?
Na Soo Hyun went after
Jo Nam Chul to kill him.
If you had tried to stop him
and you were there...
how could you be so unharmed and
come out with minor injuries?
- Jung Hye In.
- No, no.
I understand Hye In's point of view.
It all happened so quickly, so...
Na Soo Hyun had no reason
to kill Joon Gu.
He was just someone getting in
the way of killing Jo Nam Chul.
I am sorry.
Get some rest today for the show later.
We'll be getting prepared for it.
Take your time coming out.
There's no need for that.
Let's head out together.
He told me to wait for the next mission.
He usually sends you
the mission directly.
Don't do anything on your own,
and call us right away.
Yes, Director Shin.
I think I need to head out because of
a tip we got about the silver ring.
I think there might be something there.
It could be nothing but I need to check.
I'll film everything we discuss
and give you a call.
Sorry I couldn't tell you beforehand.
Okay.
This used to be my store.
I wasn't much of a businessman.
I'm an old local in this neighborhood.
Now, there are many young people here.
The old ways won't do anymore.
My son over there changed
everything in here.
Oh, I see.
What about the silver ring
you called to tell me about?
You'll see when I show you.
They wanted to buy Young Hyun
a gift for her fifth birthday.
Her older brothers came here
to ask me to make something.
Young Hyun?
Yes.
She was a girl who lived
in this neighborhood.
She had two brothers that
were a lot older than her.
I have a picture.
Here it is. This is the picture.
They were good kids.
They didn't have parents.
Two guys were raising this little girl.
When they would go out to work,
Young Hyun would come here to play.
Do you happen to know the names
of those brothers?
Yes, their last name is Na.
The older one is Jae Hyun.
The younger one is Soo Hyun.
That's right.
- Na Soo Hyun?
- Yes.
Thank you. I'm going to make a call.
Oh, okay.
Oh, excuse me.
Our tip lead to some
useful information, right?
Yes, thank you so much.
- Then how much do we get?
- Excuse me?
Last time, there was a reward
of 500 million won.
Ah, well I can't really
make those decisions.
There's nothing?
Even the police pay you something
if you call in with a tip.
She's doing a show to find her son and
she didn't even think of reward money?
Thank you for the information.
I'll look into what you're asking
about and let you know.
I found the owner of the silver ring
that we had on our show.
Na Soo Hyun and his brother got it
made for their sister's birthday.
The J is for Na Jae Hyun.
The S is for Na Soo Hyun.
The Y is for the sister Na Young Hyun.
The bracelet belongs to the youngest.
Then the ring from Jo Nam Chul's
storage unit belongs to...
Na Jae Hyun was reported missing
so it's very likely that
it belongs to him.
Suppose that Jo Nam Chul
killed Na Jae Hyun.
What if Na Soo Hyun killed Jo Nam Chul
to get revenge for his brother?
So, is this helpful
to your investigation?
Of course. Thank you.
But, why did you bring it to us first
instead of the broadcast team?
I wanted to get your permission first
to see if this was okay to air.
If you think it might be better not
to air in order to capture him...
I won't tell the broadcast team about it.
Why is that?
Our show...
it's staring to scare me more and more.
I try to think to myself that we have
no choice in order to save Hyun Woo.
People keep dying and our team
gets put in danger, as well.
Yet, everything continues trying to make
things more provocative.
I'm just worried.
Yes, this Yeon Woo Jin.
You're the writer for Wanted, right?
Yes, I am.
You murderers.
You are all murderers.
I'm going to hang up now.
You continue to make
a show to get ratings
even though a person has died?
If you don't put a stop to this show now,
I'll kill all of you myself!
This is Shin Dong Wook from UCN.
How could you make a show like this?
You knew a person died because of
your show and you still continued?
Isn't that a crime?
What are you talking about?
It's in the article. It's all online.
The kidnapper showed a murder
when he sent you a mission.
But, you hid that.
Hello?
Yes, this is Wanted...
[Wanted Promoting Murder]
What is this?
[The Wanted crew knew about the murder,
but continued with the broadcast...]
By the way, you were
great on the last show.
That woman and child
were being horribly abused.
You saved them, Jung Hye In.
"Wanted team knew the kidnapper would
follow the logic of punishing by death."
"They knew people would be murdered"
"but continued to push
for the show to air."
Who wrote this?
Jang Jin Woong from Starlife.
Wow, Director Shin finally called me.
Didn't I tell you that I would?
Well, you used all my information
I gathered on Lieutenant Cha Seung In.
Then I didn't hear from you.
I took that to mean
I could do things my way.
What about the video?
Where did you get it?
I can't give you my sources.
By the way, you were
great on the last show.
That child and woman were
being horribly abused.
You saved them, Jung Hye In.
Why don't you join
our team starting today?
How can I join your team when
I wrote an article like this?
It's not like I have
multiple personalities.
Write an article amending it.
Get people to turn their attention
elsewhere so that we can do our show.
How can I change facts?
You can change the reason
for why it was done.
We will say the police made the decision,
to keep Hyun Woo safe.
We'll supplement that with
an interview from within our team.
And?
Let's get people's interest turned
away from our morals
and back to the kidnapper.
Let's focus on what's been exposed.
There is the girl in the video,
Lee Ji Eun.
You're really something, aren't you?
Reporter Jang, wasn't this
your goal to begin with?
No matter what happened in the end,
there was no loss for me.
So, I took a gamble.
If you were going to ask a favor,
you shouldn't have caused trouble.
How could you let this happen?
I apologize.
Help me just this once.
Tell people that the video of the murder
wasn't released due to investigation.
- Let us announce...
- You want us to take the blame!
It would look better for the police
to make that statement.
We need an explanation for
our knowledge of that video.
We will handle things on our side.
Police Commissioner!
Attention, everyone.
This is an order directly
from the commissioner.
Starting now, we will no longer
be working with the broadcast team.
Chief!
Because we were in charge of this case,
I will be responsible for what happened.
It was a mistake.
Why should you?
They're cutting tail.
When was it that they were telling
us to cooperate with the show?
Then what will happen to us?
I'm going to have be off
the case completely.
All of you will join the new team that's
been formed at national headquarters.
You will be investigating
the "Wanted" murders.
That means the broadcast team
are all suspects too.
That's good. I'm fine with that.
This is the way it should be.
A kidnapping case has turned
into a murder case.
It's not right for the police to be
manipulated by the culprit like this.
I don't want to be a part of it.
I don't want to be in the new team.
Come out. Talk to me outside.
Let me do what I've been doing and
stay with the broadcast team.
Why?
You're all after the same culprit.
The person you're after
is the same person
they're trying to catch.
- I know, but...
- But, what?
Hyun Woo will die if they fail
even one mission.
They can't do it without help
from the police.
What else?
Jung Hye In is in isolation right now.
She can't trust her husband,
the team, or anyone.
She got kidnapped herself
and got Hyun Woo
snatched away from her again.
She's dealing with that all by herself.
Officially, I can't allow this.
- I clearly said no.
- Chief!
If you're going to join the team,
take care of the old, backed up cases.
You have so much paperwork backed up.
Are you saying...
No, I'm not doing this
to give you more time.
I can't cover for you if you go to
national police headquarters.
I'm letting you out because you might
go and cause trouble there.
Yes, sir!
I might get suspended for a bit or
get some sort of punishment.
But, let me know if you need anything.
I will.
What do you want?
What did you decide to do?
I decided to let him stay because
he might go and cause trouble.
What?
Then what about me?
You should join the new team, of course.
Chief...
Really?
Gosh, how can I send off this
little kid without his senior?
Why don't you take this opportunity
to teach him well?
Okay.
We've taken care of
the article issue somewhat.
Why isn't the mission coming?
Let's do what we can before that.
This might be better for the preview
than anything related to the mission.
It gives people a reason to watch.
Jung Hye In, you have
completed your fourth mission.
I assume you've confirmed
that Hyun Woo is alive.
Go back now and
wait for your next mission.
Let's use a voice actor,
record it, and play it.
I wasn't able to film it.
Why don't we use captions?
That won't do.
The point of this preview is to make
people feel something for Jung Hye In.
A drama between the culprit
and Jung Hye In.
You said it, Writer Yeon. Did you forget?
- But, it's fake...
- Get it together.
If it's going to bother your conscience,
you shouldn't have started this.
Why are we doing this show?
I guess we have no choice
if we need people to
realize this show is about Hyun Woo.
Talk to Bo Yeon and get her on it.
Manipulate the voice and make it scary.
What?
It's nothing.
I thought I should ask you how you felt.
Why?
Jung Hye In, I know you never
cry in front of others.
But, now you have
to show yourself like this.
Plus we're going to use
a fake voice for the kidnapper.
We don't know how he will react.
What are your thoughts on this?
As a writer or a human being?
A writer.
Today's show. No...
Do you think it will be helpful
in all our future shows?
I'm sure it will be helpful in swaying
the people's opinions.
Then do it.
Make his voice sound scary and use music.
Do everything that you can.
Besides getting Hyun Woo back unharmed...
I have nothing left to protect.
Both you and Director Shin Dong Wook...
you are oddly alike.
I understand what you're saying.
Hello?
It's not a good time for me right now.
All right, I'll be there.
I need to go somewhere.
- If the mission arrives...
- I'll call you right away.
It would've been nice if you told me
before I saw it on TV.
I'm sorry about that.
Are you positive about it?
Was Tae Young's death not an accident?
I can't be positive,
but there is a good possibility.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
In order to save Hyun Woo,
I had to grab onto that possibility.
That possibility...
I want to look into, as well.
If Tae Young died that way,
I have to make it right.
Tae Young's son.
I have never even
been able to see his face.
The article today must have put
your show in a difficult position.
SG Group will be giving the show
its complete support.
Of course, I will look into it myself and
let you know if I find out anything.
If you need anything from me,
let me know right away, Sister-in-law.
I have my PR team and legal team
ready to go.
Thank you.
Senior.
The detective who investigated
Na Jae Hyun seven years ago
quit during the case.
What is he doing now?
He started up a private investigator
agency a year ago.
He had a bar before that
went out of business.
He did this and that.
- You found out where he is, right?
- Yes.
Let's go there now.
She's here!
How is the show's team doing?
How will you take responsibility
for hiding the murder?
Will you end the show now?
Do you think your actions are forgivable
because of Hyun Woo?
What is SG Group's role in this?
Please comment.
Please help me!
Jung Hye In, I found you.
Please, you have to save me.
I have to tell you something and
you have to put it on air.
Who are you?
Jung Hye In, I'm the fifth mission.
I investigated the case of a
missing person seven years ago.
Find Na Jae Hyun on Wanted today.
Get in.
Jung Hye In, just one comment please!
Shouldn't he go to a hospital first?
- Yeah.
- No, I'm all right.
Let's finish talking first.
Tell us what happened.
I never dreamed he would come
looking for me again.
He already ruined my life.
[Two Hours Ago]
Write it yourself.
Who made you stop investigating
my brother's case?
Who told you to quit being a detective?
[That never happened.]
Oh, you're hurt.
Here.
I'll wrap it for you.
You think you'll be able
to stop it again?
Write it.
[Ko Hyung Joon]
If you do what I tell you to do...
I will let you live.
But, if you run or call the police...
If you run or call the police,
you'll know the pain of losing family.
The fact that you didn't
know that is your crime.
Who did this to you and told
you to deliver the mission?
Na Soo Hyun, the younger brother of
Na Jae Hyun who's been missing.
Na Soo Hyun?
- Park Bo Yeon.
- Yes?
Call Lieutenant Cha, tell him everything,
and ask him for help.
We don't have much time
until the show starts.
Okay.
Why did Na Soo Hyun
do this to you, Detective Ko?
Because I didn't find his brother.
It's been seven years, so why now?
What was the situation regarding
Na Jae Hyun's case?
Well...
Seven years ago, Na Soo Hyun
reported Na Jae Hyun missing.
That was in mid-September.
Na Soo Hyun couldn't reach him
for two months
before he was discharged from army.
Seven years ago?
When did he last have contact
with someone?
July 12.
He had gone to work on that day.
July 12?
July 12, that day was...
That's right.
That's the day before my husband
died in the car accident.
[September 2009]
So, he stopped coming to work
after July 12 and didn't call?
Yes.
Nothing seemed strange
the last time you saw him?
He usually comes to work on his bicycle.
When he was going home that day,
he was getting into a foreign luxury car.
Someone seemed to be picking him up.
Did you see who was driving?
No, the car windows
were very darkly tinted.
What about the car model?
Do you know what kind?
It was a black Rolls Royce.
A black Rolls Royce.
That was Tae Young's car.
There wouldn't be many
of those in this country.
So, Na Jae Young
met Ham Tae Young that day.
Ham Tae Young died in
an accident the next day.
And Na Jae Young went missing after that?
We did have proof that
other owners of that car
were in other places at that time.
If you knew all of that,
why didn't the investigation continue?
Lieutenant Cha, I think
you need to come now.
Yes.
He was the detective in charge of
Na Jae Hyun's missings person case.
All right, we'll be right there.
We're in the area so it won't take long.
[Met with Detective Ko Hyung Joon.]
[Stopped investigating due
to orders from above.]
[He is hiding something.
What is the connection?]
What is that?
It's Na Soo Hyun.
What's your problem?
Why was Detective Kim Sang Shik
digging into my brother's case?
And what did he find out that
got him killed by Jo Nam Chul?
Find out before it's too late.
Did Detective Kim Sang Shik
meet with you?
Let go! Who's Kim Sang Shik?
The detective who came to you asking
about Na Jae Hyun seven years ago.
I don't know anyone like that.
No... you know him.
You definitely remember him.
Tell me. What did you say to him?
What did you tell him
that got him killed, you punk!
- Senior...
- Let me go!
Senior, Senior! You could get in trouble!
The show is starting soon.
Whether you kill him or not,
do it after the show.
I got an order from the higher-ups
to stop my investigation.
That's all I did wrong and...
I didn't have any evidence either.
Later, I got an call from Im Hyung Soon
that he had a tip for me.
I had already dropped the
case by that point.
That detective Kim Sang Shik...
He was asking a lot of questions.
I only told him the location where
he could meet Im Hyung Soon.
Don't drink so much.
- Stop lying.
- I'm choosing not to drink.
I'm really not.
Have some integrity.
It's not that I can't drink.
Where are you going now?
You're acting strange lately.
Are you meeting someone secretly?
I'm going to buy cigarettes.
I can't find a girlfriend
with you guys around.
What?
I didn't know he would
end up dying there.
Sang Shik.
I went looking for Im Hyung Soon,
but he had fled to The Philippines.
If I had pursued it any further
I thought something might happen to me,
so I quit my job too.
My life was ruined because
of that Na Jae Hyun case.
Let's focus on finding Na Jae Hyun.
About what happened to Detective Kim...
I know it's hard but Hyun Woo...
Hyun Woo.
I won't do anything to hurt him.
Then...
what should we do first?
Na Jae Hyun went missing
or went into hiding
after he met Ham Tae Young.
Ham Tae Young then died in an accident.
I don't think he's in hiding.
If he went into hiding on his own,
he would contact Na Soo Hyun somehow.
Na Soo Hyun put this entire thing into
motion in order to find Na Jae Hyun.
Detective Ko stopped looking for
Na Jae Hyun because of orders.
Jo Nam Chul said there
was someone backing him.
Hold on.
Something is off.
The storage unit in the first mission,
Jo Nam Chul, and even Im Hyung Soon.
All of these cases
are supposed to be connected.
And someone is behind it.
Why would Na Soo Hyun murder Jo Nam Chul?
Jo Nam Chul was going to
reveal who was behind it.
What if Jo Nam Chul did kill Na Soo Hyun?
And Na Soo Hyun killed Jo Nam Chul
to get revenge for his brother?
Na Soo Hyun already knows everything.
He didn't want Jo Nam Chul to
get away with it, unpunished.
Because he knew Jo Nam Chul
was the one who killed his brother.
Perhaps...
he wanted us to reveal
his brother's death
and the fact that it's still a cold case.
Then when he says to
put his brother on the show
he did not mean to
bring Na Jae Hyun in alive.
I had forgotten something.
The body that Park Gwang Hyung
had hidden for Jo Nam Chul.
We did go in together seven years ago.
He said he a favor to ask of me.
He wanted me to get rid
of a body for him.
A body?
It was hidden at a deserted
airport in Incheon.
He wasn't able to finish
the job before coming in.
He said the person who hired him
to do the job would throw a fit.
Was it Jo Nam Chul
who killed that person?
I don't know and I didn't ask.
That body Jo Nam Chul asked you to hide
where did you bury it?
Gosh, go.
My big mouth is a problem.
I trusted you and told you that.
I only told you because
you saved my life that one time.
This time I will owe you one
and I'll let you off next time.
Just tell me where.
Where is that body?
Stop airing the show!
Stop, stop!
Don't worry.
The body that the gangster boss buried
is probably just skeletal remains.
There is no way to tell if it's
Na Jae Hyun or not on today's show.
We have no other way anyhow.
You only need to think
about two things for today.
Make the public sympathetic
to Hyun Woo.
Also, make it as exciting
and suspenseful as a movie.
You just need to remember
one thing, Dong Wook.
Hyun Woo's safety.
Park Bo Yeon.
Yes.
The Executive Director has a cameraman
and is with the police.
Keep in touch with him constantly
and time it perfectly.
Uh... okay.
I'll send the video if
we find him in time
so you need to time it just right.
Don't forget that Hyun Woo's safety
and the mission's success
are the priorities.
Okay.
You have to film this, over here.
I took out the scene of the detectives
fighting from the script.
Confirm that.
The footage has changed too.
Okay.
Call me when you find something.
We're starting now.
Don't forget what we discussed.
Everything on this show is real.
We are doing this show at the request of
the person who has kidnapped my son.
Jung Hye In's Wanted is starting now.
Before today's show...
I am sure you all saw the preview.
Last night...
Hyun Woo attempted to escape
and we went to rescue him.
That is footage from the scene.
The moment I finally managed to hold him
I was tased by the kidnapper
and lost consciousness.
I...
I was unable to protect
my child two times now.
Hyun Woo is only seven years old.
He was taken again by a person
who kidnaps and murders
as if it is nothing.
Yes.
Yes, Commissioner.
I will do as I promised earlier.
The kidnapper was merely
a young man in his 20s.
Na Soo Hyun.
He is Hyun Woo's kidnapper.
Today, as reported in the news
regarding the murder of Professor Kim.
He is the only suspect in his murder
as well as the murder of Jo Nam Chul.
Na Soo Hyun lost his parents
at an early age.
He is said to have had a close bond
with his brother and young sister.
However, his sister died nine years ago.
Seven years ago,
his brother went missing.
Are these the incidents that
altered a young man's life?
While we investigated Na Soo Hyun,
we received the fifth mission.
Na Jae Hyun is Na Soo Hyun's brother
who went missing seven years ago.
Do you see the ring and bracelet we
retrieved from Jo Nam Chul's locker?
J, S, Y.
Na Young Hyun, his younger sister
who died nine years ago...
Na Jae Hyun, his brother who's been
missing for seven years...
And Na Soo Hyun.
We got a statement from the detective who
first investigated the Na Jae Hyun case.
Seven years ago...
Detective Kim was murdered
by Jo Nam Chul
who was working on an unofficial case.
We found out that he was looking
into Na Jae Hyun's disappearance.
What is this?
What happened to the footage of
Lieutenant Cha and Detective Ko fighting?
The script changed too.
I changed it.
What?
We sold out Lieutenant Cha
enough last time.
It has nothing to do
with Hyun Woo either.
It has nothing to do with it even if
you changed the entire feel of the show?
The continuity would've been better.
In my opinion...
it's not worth putting
someone through pain
without even getting his permission.
It's not that important.
Writer Yeon!
Right now, we are following our lead.
Our team is investigating
the whereabouts of Na Jae Hyun.
We have not found Na Jae Hyun yet.
For the sake of Hyun Woo's safety,
we must find him before this show ends.
I hope that Na Jae Hyun can safely
make an appearance on our show.
- Young Gwan!
- Yes!
Oh, Lieutenant Cha.
Closer, closer.
[Na Jae Hyun]
Okay, we found him.
Act excited like we just found him.
With ten minutes left to go,
they have found Na Jae Hyun.
Unfortunately...
Na Jae Hyun could not come to us alive
and speak to us on his behalf.
Na Jae Hyun was seen with my ex-husband,
who died in an accident on July 13, 2009.
He was last seen getting into his car.
Today...
his skeletal remains
were found in a mountain.
Jae Hyun.
We have completed the fifth mission.
In the beginning...
it seemed as if the culprit was
punishing people who wronged children.
Now, he is giving us
a complex question to solve.
Na Soo Hyun, Na Jae Hyun.
Detective Kim... and me.
Also, my former husband's accident.
What is behind all of this?
What are you doing?
Get me a mic.
I want to say something
before today's show ends.
As Hyun Woo's father and UCN's President,
I have something to say.
Camera on President Song.
Jung Hye In, act like you expected it.
Today will be the last episode
of Jung Hye In's Wanted.
Subtitles by DramaFever
If you want to talk, come inside.
Did you get something from
President Song's recording?
The broadcast team are all suspects now.
Should we start with the director?
We were told to use
this room starting today.
If you're not on this case,
then stay out.
Don't concern yourself with me.
Were you with Jo Nam Chul
when he got murdered?
Song Jung Ho!
Everything just falls right into place.