Subtitles by DramaFever
Come to my office if you want to talk...
[Episode 8]
Why did you do it?
I asked you why you did it.
I got an investment offer in return
for agreeing to cancel Wanted.
The capital funds are from China.
I was guaranteed management rights.
So, it was all about money?
You've been getting everything you want.
Yes, it's been good up until now.
However...
this show will be over in five days.
We're already starting to get
criticized over ethical issues.
We may have lots of legal
issues to deal with too.
Is this what you were planning
to do from the start?
This is the right time to pull out.
The police had been cooperating with us,
so we didn't have any big problems.
Tomorrow, the police will officially
announce they're not working with us.
We are all going to become
suspects in the investigation.
We'll have bigger issues to deal with.
Don't you care about Hyun Woo at all?
Can you even call yourself a human being?
You shouldn't say that.
This was an impossible show
to produce to begin with.
I was the one who made it possible.
It's impossible to air this on
another station by tomorrow.
What about doing an online broadcast?
Are you okay?
How did your talk go?
I can't get through to him at all.
He was only planning to get
what he wanted and leave.
I'm going to do this show
on UCN no matter what.
How will you do that?
I'll use his tactics.
I'll have to find his weakness.
I'll threaten him
or persuade him somehow.
Will that work?
He's all about profit and loss.
If I try to take away what he
doesn't want to lose the most
it will be possible.
The thing he doesn't want to lose...
That would be this station.
You should be responsible
for the lawsuit.
I had it set up with the legal team
from the very beginning.
I made it look like you set up
an external company and produced it.
The company has not
breached any contracts.
Therefore, you are responsible
for all the penalties.
You could be charged for embezzlement
and breach of contract.
Does he have a weakness like that?
He is willing to do anything
to make money.
I have to find something.
This customer is
unavailable at the moment.
Please try again.
This customer is
unavailable at the moment.
Kyung Hoon, where are you?
You saw the show last night, right?
I need your help.
It's something only you can do.
Contact me as soon as possible.
Hyun Woo!
Mom!
Let me take a look at you, Hyun Woo.
Are you hurt at all?
Are you in pain?
Shouldn't we try to make
a deal with the kidnapper?
We have no way of contacting him.
UCN would never let us do
a preview or a special episode.
I'm sure the kidnapper saw the episode.
I'm worried about Hyun Woo.
Who knows what he will do?
What's going on?
We were told to use
this room starting today.
Our team is using this room.
Wanted is over now.
You can't just come in here like this.
We're just doing what we were told.
I told them to do it.
We need time to prepare if
we're going to make a new show.
We need to work with new investors.
Now that they announced
the show is over
the culprit might make a move.
I know he's not his biological son,
but how could he make such a bold move?
It might be a good thing.
The kidnapper wouldn't be so rash
and kill Hyun Woo.
He has an end goal.
He planned things out in great detail.
How is that new team?
Are you joining them right away?
Yes, we are trying to find something
before the show's air time tomorrow.
But, it feels like they've
given up on the kid.
Chief, are you okay?
Huh? Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm not even suspended.
It's only a pay cut for three months.
They went easy on me.
I'm perfectly fine. It's no big deal.
They ought to find the kid though.
You really are heroic.
Chief, I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Keep Cha Seung In out of our way.
If you have something to say,
you can tell me directly.
If you're out of this case,
then stay out of it completely.
Sure. Don't worry about me.
I see you're not going to listen
to me whatsoever.
Where is Senior Mi Ock?
Oh Mi Ock?
I'll be keeping an eye on her
to make sure she's not around.
She could be punished
for abusing her position
when she's supposed to off.
Tell her to stay out of it too.
I'll take care of things here.
Don't concern yourself with it.
Hey, hey! That's enough.
Mi Ock's over there.
We'll wait outside.
What are you doing?
Empty out the room.
What is this? Who are you!
You weren't bad on the show earlier.
You wanted to apologize
for the disturbance
caused while searching for your son.
You will no longer acquiesce
to the demands of the kidnapper.
It was great.
A leader of the people.
Very cool, right?
Stop spouting nonsense and leave.
However, the truth is that
you got a large investment
and you're catering to them.
You put your son's life on the line
in exchange for that investment.
Was that possibly because
he's not really your son?
- What are you doing?
- You started this for money.
Now, the money might stop flowing.
It's the perfect time to end it.
You're the pathetic father
who doesn't care for his son.
You're the perfect character for people
to latch onto and rip to shreds.
Whether they're fans of the show or not,
there's something to criticize you about.
Get out.
I don't want to have
chased this story for nothing.
I better write this up
as a special report.
If you don't want that,
why don't you give them a chance?
They started this show to save a child.
Even if they have to give up,
shouldn't they fight until the end?
That would be a better story
for me to write too.
Wouldn't a better story
be if they kept fighting
when no one would give them a chance?
Empty this room by noon tomorrow.
I'm most worried about Hyun Woo
being with Na Soo Hyun.
Why?
Jo Nam Chul had Na Jae Hyun and
Ham Tae Young's belongings.
Jo Nam Chul asked Park Gwang Hyung
to bury the body for him.
That makes it very likely that
Jo Nam Chul killed Na Jae Hyun.
- But...
- But, what?
Na Soo Hyun's identity was revealed
with five episodes left to go.
Revenge for his brother
was not the final mission.
He may have taken part in this
to get revenge for his brother.
I think he's an accomplice.
If there is another culprit
this has been planned
out in great detail.
It wasn't a plan made
to punish Jo Nam Chul.
That's right.
But, Jo Nam Chul was not arrested
and managed to escape.
I think that's when
the plan started to go awry.
He came to the broadcast station
and killed Jo Nam Chul.
His face ended up being revealed.
Sing that song for your mom.
He no longer disguised his voice.
Losing Hyun Woo was a mistake.
To Jung Hye In, he acted as if he was
giving proof of Hyun Woo being alive.
He was able to scare her.
But, it was a real crisis
for Na Soo Hyun.
You're saying he made a mistake,
but pretended it was on purpose?
- What's your basis for this?
- The previous mission.
He wasn't telling her to expose
that her ex-husband's death
wasn't an accident.
The mission was to find out how he died.
Jung Hye In didn't complete her mission.
But, he wanted to make it seem like
he lost Hyun Woo on purpose.
He told her she succeeded
without any conditions or questions.
His plan keeps coming apart.
Just like how he put that note on my car,
he's risking being exposed.
Today, he confirmed
the body of his brother.
If the show can't continue,
we don't know what he'll do next.
- Let's go.
- Where?
He will contact Jung Hye In somehow.
He may do something impulsive
to get the show back on air.
Hello?
Hye In. It's me, Kyung Hoon.
Yes, Kyung Hoon.
Can you come home now?
I saw the hidden camera in the office.
I need the video file for that.
No, I won't go home.
What if the police are there?
Hye In, you tricked me
last time too.
Come to a place
that I choose by yourself.
That is, if you want the files.
It's me.
You have to be quiet.
Do you have it?
Hye In... you must not care
about how I've been doing.
I don't have the time for this.
You're just trying to use me.
You said you'd find Hyun Woo for me.
Hyun Woo is in so much danger.
If you keep asking questions like this,
how can I trust in you?
Here.
I put a camera in President Song's
office because...
You don't need to explain.
I'll call you again.
Wait.
Kwon Kyung Hoon!
[Sixth Mission]
[What is President Song's
relationship with to this woman?]
[Get him on the show
to explain it himself.]
Some man asked me to deliver it to you.
I thought it was for a special event.
Was it him?
He wearing a hat and mask,
so I can't be too certain.
I think that's him.
The eyes are similar.
He asked you to give an envelope to
Jung Hye In and you weren't suspicious?
Don't you watch TV?
Ah! I watch that show. It's really fun.
When I watch it on TV,
it's hard to realize that it's real.
Where did he go?
He went up those stairs.
It's been about 10 minutes.
There won't be any point
going out there now.
Wow, aren't you the detective
from the Jo Nam Chul mission?
It is you!
The action from the hostage thing
was really cool.
We should go.
Did you find anything in the files
for President Song?
There really isn't much.
It's just him talking in his study,
room, and company office.
He asks to meet in person
for important things.
They only have regular conversations.
I suppose you wouldn't understand
the nuance of their conversations.
Don't miss anything, report everything,
and bring it to me quickly.
Okay.
Will this really work?
Everything we've got so far is something
he can get out of with legal help.
I just need the station
to back off for five days.
Senior.
You know something, don't you?
Joon Gu, when we first started out...
I will be the producer.
I'm okay with that.
Will that be possible?
Find someone else for the lawsuit.
You're better at seizing
opportunities than I thought.
Okay.
What was that all about?
The thing is...
Paper company?
It will be difficult if they set
it up with the legal team.
It will be hard to start
investigating within five days too.
You know how the law works.
It often helps the powerful appear right
when they're doing wrong.
Still, let's start from there.
Okay.
I'll look into it.
Everything that the culprit is trying to
expose on air comes back to this day.
On the night of July 12, 2009,
Na Jae Hyun and Ham Tae Young meet.
Next day, 3:00 a.m. July 13.
Ham Tae Young dies in a car accident.
Na Jae Hyun goes missing after that.
His skeletal remains were
found yesterday night.
The kidnapper's motive was definitely
the Na Jae Hyun case.
Yes.
We were told to do the show
when Jo Nam Chul was paroled.
Na Jae Hyun and Ham Tae Young's items
were found in Jo Nam Chul's storage unit.
He had that in mind from the beginning.
If we organize these incidents
in a timeline...
Jo Nam Chul killed Ham Tae Young
and Na Jae Hyun.
He buried the body or made
it look like an accident.
Na Soo Hyun was discharged
from the army two months later.
He went to police and filed
a missing person's report.
Detective Ko Hyung Joon took the case.
Around the time that he found out
Ham Tae Young and Na Jae Hyun had met...
I got an order from the higher-ups
to stop my investigation.
That's all I did wrong and...
I didn't have any evidence either.
Later, I got an call from Im Hyung Soon
who Jo Nam Chul killed recently.
He said he had a tip for me.
I had already dropped the case
by that point.
That detective Kim Sang Shik...
He was asking a lot of questions.
I only told him the location where he
could meet Im Hyung Soon.
Jo Nam Chul was waiting at the location
that Im Hyun Soon was supposed to be.
That's where Senior Sang Shik...
Sang Shik!
After that, Im Hyun Soon
ran to The Philippines.
Three months ago, he returned to Korea.
You started meeting Park Sae Yong
one month before Hyun Woo was kidnapped.
Na Soo Hyun started working at the cafe
by UCN two months before the kidnapping.
When was this entire plan made?
And, three days before
Hyun Woo was kidnapped...
Park Sae Yong kidnapped Lee Ji Eun.
But...
There's Han Sol's father
from the first mission.
Also, the doctor Ha Dong Min
from the second mission.
They have no connection to the case
from seven years ago.
Accomplices Park Sae Yong and Lee Ji Eun.
Also, Han Sol's dad and Ha Dong Min.
We need to investigate how
these four are connected
to what happened seven years ago.
Is she his mistress?
She looks young.
If he's visiting her place,
it seems kind of...
Why is the kidnapper
suddenly targeting him?
He saw President Song announce
that the show is over.
The reason that he wants Song Jung Hon
on the show is...
There's a reason the kidnapper
initially wanted ten episodes.
You're right.
But, the show got canceled after five.
Isn't he trying to get it started again?
But, he didn't threaten or anything.
He just sent this mission.
He wanted us to find Han Sol.
That was in order for us to expose
his father who was abusing him.
If we look into their relationship...
we might be able to find a way
to start our show again.
Where are you going?
I think can find this woman.
I'll go alone for now.
Film it if it's important.
Yes, hello.
My husband left his keys
locked inside the car.
It's done.
Thank you.
Apartment...
Seven years ago?
Sae Yong was going through
a hard time back then.
Hard time?
His father passed away early.
I ran a restaurant alone
to raise Sae Yong.
I became so ill at that time.
Sae Yong was going to school and
working at the same time.
He was going through a lot.
Was he acting strange at all
before the incident?
It was a year ago.
Suddenly, he couldn't sleep at all.
He would stay in his room all the time
and he said he was making a bomb.
He ended up with a wound
on his wrist and gave up on it.
One year ago?
He didn't tell you why he was making it?
He said that it was the world's fault
that we were poor and suffering.
He was going to use it on bad people.
But, he was actually
a better son during all that.
He wasn't always a bad person.
He wanted to be a movie director
when he was younger.
I thought he was always watching movies.
He was so innocent.
Can we take a look inside his room?
I left it untouched.
I couldn't bear to go in.
Didn't the investigative team go through
everything when he committed suicide?
It's not because I don't
want to work or anything.
[Loadagun]
Senior.
This worked out well.
I thought the show ended,
but you're all still here.
It will make investigating easier.
What do you mean?
We're not here to help you today.
We're here to investigate
the Wanted team.
From now on, you are all included
as targets of the investigation.
Why would we be targets
of the investigation?
The motive is there.
You have lots to gain from the show.
All of you have a personal
relationship with Jung Hye In.
Some of you were
in a desperate situation.
We, the police...
want to announce that we will no longer
take part in efforts with UCN
in the kidnapping case of Song Hyun Woo
that has aired for the past five days.
This program has resulted in murder
and kidnapping.
These crimes continue to occur
as the culprit holds everyone hostage.
Also, the show is
being broadcast unfiltered.
It is adding to the anxiety
and fear of the people.
The kidnapper holds no respect for
punishment of crimes or justice.
We must fix this distorted view.
Before anyone imitates this crime,
we must correct this societal issue.
You won't be able to get out of this
with excuses about your show.
You'll have to cooperate
with our investigation.
Director Shin Dong Wook.
Should we start with you?
Sure.
Executive Director, you can come with me.
Executive Director.
What is it?
It's hidden camera footage that
Jung Hye In's manager took.
Did her manager give
this to Park Sae Yong?
The culprit used the footage
that the manager took.
I don't know if the manager
is an accomplice.
He might've shared it
or sold it to Park Sae Yong
not knowing what is was for.
I need to look into it.
Park Sae Yong was Jung Hye In's
stalker after all.
"Loadagun".
That's not her manager's ID.
If this is a user ID...
Park Sae Yong could have sent
the videos to this person too.
If we could find that,
it could be the kidnapper's user ID.
We want to find this user ID in
Park Sae Yong's hard drive.
What could this be? A user ID?
We're not positive. It could be.
There was a chat log
from a foreign country.
It's not easy to get the chat record
or who he was talking to.
It's a site that protects its
member's privacy.
The servers are in Central Europe.
If it isn't the account owner logging in,
the chat records will disappear.
It could take time.
The show from the day before yesterday,
there was a scene of Jo Nam Chul's death.
Who filmed that?
I did.
Aren't you close friends with
Executive Director Choi Joon Gu?
A friend of yours is passed out
at the scene of a murder.
And you start filming the murdered body.
I really don't understand it.
I called the ambulance right away.
There was nothing I could do
until they arrived.
We had to air the fact that
Jo Nam Chul had died.
We needed footage for that
and that's why I filmed it.
It wasn't that you killed him in order
to put it on your show?
You were with Jo Nam Chul when he got
murdered, right?
Yes.
I already heard on that day about how
you lost consciousness that day.
While he was attacking you,
wouldn't Jo Nam Chul have time to run?
Or he would have time to attack
Na Soo Hyun first.
I did not see the situation properly,
so I don't know.
What if you and Na Soo Hyun happened
to be co-accomplices?
Everything would make perfect sense.
You tell Na Soo Hyun where and when.
Then you help Na Soo Hyun get in.
Let's assume you attacked
Jo Nam Chul together.
I understand your situation, Detective.
I really don't know Na Soo Hyun.
I have no reason to
kill Jo Nam Chul, do I?
May I take a look at your phone?
Go ahead.
Director, they're taking our set apart!
What the hell.
What can I do for you?
Everything on this show is real.
We are doing this show at the request of
the person who has kidnapped my son.
Jung Hye In's Wanted is starting now.
- Put on President Song from last night.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
Get me a mic.
I want to say something
before today's show ends.
As Hyun Woo's father and UCN's
President, I have something to say.
Today will be the last episode
of Jung Hye In's Wanted.
That was UCN's President and my
husband speaking last night.
He is also Song Jung Ho,
Hyun Woo's father.
On live TV, he announced
that this was the last episode.
The entire broadcast team,
as well as myself...
had not expected it at all.
The kidnapper, Na Soo Hyun,
is currently with Hyun Woo.
If we do not continue with this show,
Hyun Woo will be in danger.
The day Hyun Woo was kidnapped...
President Song Jung Ho told you
that you'd have to take
the legal blame for the company.
That's what he said, right?
Yes.
But, I already said all of this
when Hyun Woo was kidnapped.
Why do I have to say it again?
I don't understand.
That was an investigation into your
motive and alibi for Hyun Woo.
Now, we're investigation this show.
It's not just you,
Executive Director Choi.
Your entire team will be investigated.
Let's take it slowly.
I think we'll be talking all night.
We received confirmation
from Song Jung Ho
that this show will not be canceled.
Many of you are probably thinking.
Because Hyun Woo..."
"Song Jung Ho isn't his biological son,
that's why he acted like this."
However, Song Jung Ho
has been a loving father
for the past seven years.
He has been like a strong fence for me.
Is President Song here yet?
Bo Yeon is going to call
when he arrives.
So, why?
This is a live show that
has Hyun Woo's life on the line.
So, why try to cancel it
without talking to me about it?
Unexpectedly, we found out through
the kidnapper's sixth mission.
We discovered why Song Jung Ho
had no other choice.
[What is is Song Jung Ho's
relationship with this woman?]
[Ten Hours Earlier]
What do you think you're doing?
Did you think you'd find
Song Jung Ho in here?
What is he to you?
A married man buys a woman
an apartment and drops by.
He gives her living expenses.
Isn't it obvious?
Didn't you know everything
before you came?
This woman, Ms. Kim, is the woman
in the picture sent by the kidnapper.
Is she truly my husband's mistress?
Is the mission solved?
However, while I was
meeting with Ms. Kim
the show's team was doing
their own research on her.
They discovered something odd.
[Nine Hours Earlier]
Jung Hye In?
There's another paper company
beside the one mentioned
by Executive Director Choi.
It's a movie or drama production company.
They've never produced anything and
I don't know what they actually do.
On the list of board members,
that woman is there.
Kim So Hyun is listed.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
There was a paper company created
by President Song Jung Ho.
This company had no
actual losses or profits.
Every month, a set amount of money
was deposited into Ms. Kim's account.
You should have filmed yourself
finding out that information.
No thanks.
I don't want to be in the show.
I'd rather not advertise the fact
I did an illegal act either.
Hello.
You shouldn't be in here
when we're on air.
Just come in for our meetings.
This is the real thing though.
You want to exclude me from this
and give me things I don't need?
This isn't what we promised.
I need to go to the restroom quickly.
- Hurry up.
- Sorry.
Seriously, you're being so stingy.
I'll leave, okay?
I have a favor to ask.
What?
Well, I'm not asking
you to do it for free.
What was this paper company used for?
We looked into a list of all the people
listed as employees of this company.
It was surprising.
Except for Ms. Kim,
they were all connected to one person.
That person was not
President Song Jung Ho.
I found it.
[Eight Hours and 30 Minutes Earlier]
Yes, Commissioner.
I will do as I promised earlier.
This was recorded
before yesterday's show.
So, the reason he ended the show
is connected to the commissioner.
No wonder the police were so helpful,
and then suddenly so unhelpful.
The Police Commissioner told him
to shut down the show.
This girl is connected too.
This mission is targeting
the Police Commissioner.
[Six Hours Earlier]
Everyone connected to the paper company
are all related to the commissioner,
except for Kim So Hyun.
His nephew, in-law, and cousin.
There's even a high school friend.
So, Kim So Hyun is not connected
to President Song.
Is she having an affair with
the Police Commissioner?
Isn't the pattern different this time?
Child abuse, illegal clinical tests,
and murder.
Those are very different
from a slush fund and an affair.
If the commissioner is the target
and not President Song...
The Police Commissioner must be connected
to what happened seven years ago too.
He asked President Song to stop the show
and even got him a new investor.
He must have something he needs to hide.
Let's look into the commissioner and
Kim So Hyun's connection seven years ago.
Okay.
You bastard!
How could you do this to me?
Watch what you're saying to me.
You said the show would end!
That paper company...
Why are they talking about it?
I'm sorry.
I have somewhere I need to be.
I'll be back soon.
Do you want to stay here and watch?
We should finish our talk.
This is the person connected to all the
board members of the paper company.
His nickname is Mister Clean.
He is an icon of integrity and honesty.
He is Police Commissioner Lee Tae Kyun.
UCN's President Song Jung Ho.
Police Commissioner Lee Tae Kyun.
This young lady, Kim So Hyun.
What is the connection
between these three people?
The kidnapper had put
one more demand on the mission.
Song Jung Ho must come on
the show and reveal it himself.
Song Jung Ho.
First, tell us what your relationship
with Kim So Hyun is.
First... I'd like to make
one thing clear.
I love my wife.
I have never betrayed my wife.
Earlier, we saw Kim So Hyun
say so herself.
She implied that you two were
in an illicit relationship.
She's young and still in her early 20s.
She has had many issues growing up,
so she has a rebellious personality.
I believe she reacts in that way when
people think the worst of her.
Then what about the apartment
and living expenses?
Can you please explain that?
As for Kim So Hyun...
A man that I respect...
No.
A man that I once respected needed
help in hiding a situation.
She is the child of
an extramarital affair.
Four years ago, he found out about a
daughter he didn't know existed.
Her mother contacted him
before she died of cancer.
The paper company was
made for that purpose.
It was a favor to him because he
couldn't go public with it.
I set it up for him to help
his daughter and her future.
Who is this person that you respected?
You may have guessed already.
It is Police Commissioner Lee Tae Kyun.
You have said that you respect him.
You set up an illegal paper company
and you helped take care his daughter.
Wouldn't you say your relationship
was of the business variety?
You're ready, right?
You know... you don't have to do this.
I'm fine.
I did respect him.
Kim So Hyun will be ready
in three minutes.
Get her lines ready.
I made it very clear.
I'm against putting Kim So Hyun
in front of the camera.
- She came in on her own.
- She'll regret it.
How long are you going to keep this up?
I wouldn't have asked you to work
if I knew you'd be this way.
I'm doing my job properly.
I'm just trying to make a good program.
Good program? And what is that?
It's okay for Song Jung Ho to go up there
and pretend to be a good guy.
We're revealing the commissioner's
hidden secrets.
Why can't she go on?
She lived a hard life because
of something she never asked for.
Now, she's going go up there and
people will point their fingers at her.
Does she have to stripped bare like that?
There are people waiting in lines
dying to do that.
Stop worrying about other's lives.
Worry about Hyun Woo's life,
which is depending on ratings.
Camera two.
When I announced the end
of this show yesterday...
it was at the order Commissioner Lee,
who was being pressured by the public.
I had no choice.
My son, Hyun Woo...
Yes.
We have now completed the sixth mission.
We have a guest here today to confirm
Song Jung Ho's statement.
Kim So Hyun.
Is everything Song Jung Ho
said today the truth?
Yes.
It's true.
Song Jung Ho!
What is that?
Who's calling during a live show?
We apologize to all our viewers.
Yes, Commissioner.
Tight close-up on Song Jung Ho.
Don't sit there getting angry.
Come here.
Speak to the citizens yourself.
If the commissioner is at the station,
I think we should go there.
We should.
I thought we weren't allowed
to investigate Hyun Woo's case.
He's the one who put a stop to
Na Jae Hyun's case seven years ago.
He's the only one who knows
what happened between
Na Jae Hyun and Ham Tae Young.
Let's go.
I came here today...
to tell all you the truth.
Everything that President Song Jung Ho
told you today
is not true.
As a policeman,
I have my honor to protect.
As a father, I have my family to protect.
I will fight back against
all of these vicious lies.
That is why I'm here today.
As for this young lady next to me...
she is not my daughter.
Yes.
You're not my father.
What kind of a father would do this?
You get me an apartment
and make me stay in there.
You tell me not to go anywhere because
you have to do your politics.
You made me live like a shadow!
And still...
I still trusted you
because you were my dad.
[Fours Hours Earlier]
What is it like living like this?
Like your father's shadow?
For his life?
You're in hiding.
And living in comfort with money
that you don't even want.
I can't ask you to come on the show.
If I can't get the ratings up...
my son will be in danger.
They announced that the show would end
and we didn't have a preview today.
We'll do what we can.
You should make the choice, So Hyun.
Choose how you want to live.
Choose what method you will use.
[Jung Hye In's Wanted - SG Group]
[Three Hours Earlier]
You must not have been very fond
of Hyun Woo while you raised him.
That's not it.
I... want to hold
my nephew just once.
[Five Hours Earlier]
I'll get straight to the point.
Help me get this show started again.
I did look into it actually.
A very aggressive investor
is already on it.
Yesterday, you promised
to give me your complete support.
Please acquire UCN by offering
more than the other investor.
That's the only way.
I was saying that I will do
whatever I can within my powers.
The group will need to look it over.
It's hard to promise anything right away.
I know you have the power to do this.
I also know that you
see the bigger picture
and see further ahead than anyone here.
Honestly, UCN is in need
of life support right now.
Wanted was that life support.
I gave them that.
I heard that you've been preparing
to buy a media company for a long time.
I know it took you longer because
your older brother opposed it.
I thought you were an actress,
but you have a knack for business.
From SG Group's standpoint...
they are helping to find the son
of their deceased youngest son.
It will look an unselfish good deed.
You are using that opportunity
to start a new business.
Awesome picture proof.
Yesterday, I saw the face
of Wanted's kidnapper.
I was doing my job.
Some guy in black gave me an envelope
and asked me to deliver it to a woman.
It turned out to be Jung Hye In.
I was dressed as a clown and I delivered
the mission to Jung Hye In.
The detectives who caught
Jo Nam Chul were there too.
Do you have anything more to say?
You...
Why did you do it?
Why did you ruin my life?
And that young child...
I didn't do that to your daughter.
That was your choice.
Subtitles by DramaFever