Everything that the culprit is trying to
expose on air comes back to this day.
On the night of July 12, 2009,
Na Jae Hyun and Ham Tae Young meet.
The next day, 3:00 a.m. July 13.
Ham Tae Young dies in a car accident.
Na Jae Hyun goes missing after that.
His skeletal remains were
found yesterday night.
The kidnapper's motive was
definitely the Na Jae Hyun case.
Jo Nam Chul killed Ham Tae Young
and Na Jae Hyun.
He buried the body,
or made it look like an accident.
Na Soo Hyun was discharged
from the army two months later.
He went to the police
and filed a missing person's report.
Detective Ko Hyung Joon took the case.
And around the time he found out
Ham Tae Young and Na Jae Hyun had met...
I got an order from the higher-ups
to stop my investigation.
That's all I did wrong.
And, three days before
Hyun Woo was kidnapped...
Park Sae Yong kidnapped Lee Ji Eun.
But...
There's Han Sol's father
from the first mission.
Also, the doctor Ha Dong Min
from the second mission.
They have no connection to
the case from seven years ago.
The commissioner tried to end this show.
And this woman is connected.
That means the commissioner
is the target of this mission.
You said you would end this show!
Why are you talking about
the paper company?
I'm sorry.
I have somewhere to be right now.
I'll be back soon.
Do you want to stay here
and watch the show?
We should finish our conversation.
He's the one who stopped
the investigation seven years ago.
He's the only one who knows what happened
with Na Jae Hyun and Ham Tae Young.
Everything President Song Jung Ho
said today is a lie.
This girl next to me is not my daughter.
Still, I trusted you as my father.
Do you still have more to say?
You...
Why did you do it?
Why did you ruin my life?
And that young child...
I didn't do that to your daughter.
That was a choice you made.
Put your hands up.
Yes, yes.
This is the President's office at UCN.
It wasn't me.
It was suicide... suicide.
I thought he was going to shoot me.
But he shot himself in the head.
[EPISODE 9]
The commissioner came into your room
about 30 minutes after
the show ended, right?
Yes.
What did he say to you?
He asked me if didn't
I pity his daughter.
He yelled at me about
why I ruined his life.
What next?
He came running at me.
He grabbed me by the throat.
I told him to stop.
I tried to talk to him and send him out.
It's all out in the open now anyway.
Why didn't you at least try
to appease your daughter?
I had it all prepared for you.
Prepared for me?
I said the slush fund was made
just for the sake of your daughter.
I said you did it because you
couldn't protect your daughter.
We made up that nice story.
Our writer is good at that kind of thing.
Why are you suddenly doing this to me?
That was my way of giving you an out.
People in our country, when they
see motherly or fatherly love
they will forgive anything
like corrupt politicians,
bad business deals, stealing.
You should have shown an emotional scene
with your daughter back then.
Who is it!
Who is it that has your back
and exposed me?
Look at you.
You really don't seem to understand.
No one has my back.
I'm the one deciding who to use
and making that choice.
Politics will be difficult
for you from now on.
Maybe there's a job for a president
at a public company.
I could find out for you.
Don't do this.
Let's just talk.
Give me a chance to fix this.
I...
To get to where I am...
I had to get a little dirty
here and there.
I may have lied and hidden things.
But, I have always been patriotic.
This country!
I believed that I could change
this country for the better.
I truly did.
Why are you doing this?
Saying all these things to me...
Why don't you go home for now?
Am I cleared of all charges now?
No, that's not it.
The police commissioner committed
suicide because of Wanted.
President Song was on the scene with him.
He will be investigated as a suspect
until there is clear evidence.
Then what about the show?
You will hear from us soon.
The broadcast team should
all be waiting on standby.
Make sure we can always find you.
Mom.
Sing that song for your mom.
The flower petals move my heart.
The flower petals bring
tears to my eyes.
Beautiful memories.
Blue skies.
I am taking it all in.
The flower petals move my heart.
The flower petals bring
tears to my eyes.
Beautiful memories.
Blue skies.
I am taking it all in.
Child, do not be weak.
What will you do now?
It's one thing after another.
Let's talk.
About the commissioner's suicide
write the article focusing
on the daughter.
Straighten out that slush fund story too.
Oh? You can't order me around
because we're on the same team.
Don't you see you're the only reporter?
I'm giving you an exclusive.
This isn't an exclusive.
I'm just observing.
If you want something,
I have to get something in return.
What do you want to know?
What was that SG logo after the show?
You must be thinking what this
is all about, so late at night.
It's not just any regular trouble.
He committed suicide after
his corruption was exposed.
Deputy Commissioner Sung. Wait, no...
Acting Police Commissioner Sung.
You'll be very busy for the next while.
Yes, the show.
That is what I am calling about.
My father always loved Tae Young so much.
He found out about his grandson.
Now, he is absolutely
determined to find him.
I know it is causing you
a lot of trouble.
Please give us just four more days
and we'll try to keep quiet.
Once we find the child,
you can do as you see fit.
Sung Jung Hoon will now take over
as Acting Police Commissioner.
Former Commissioner Lee Tae Kyun
tried to cover up his corruption.
Commissioner Lee Tae Kyun put pressure
on Wanted to shut down production.
From this point on, he will be...
Yeon Jung Eun.
She insisted on eating when you came.
She'll miss the school bus
if she eats now.
Oh, Jung Eun. Did you do that?
It's okay. We can eat together
and I'll drive her.
Jung Eun, let's take Mom's car
and go to school today.
We're supposed to have
your birthday party today.
Wow, this seaweed soup looks so good.
Grandma made such delicious soup.
Here. Open up, Jung Eun.
Come on.
Good girl.
Is it good?
It is good, isn't it?
Hi! You must be Jung Eun's friends.
Hello!
We're playing the Wanted game.
You should play too.
You can be Jung Hye In. I'm a detective.
You have to find the culprit.
[FIND OUT WHO MURDERED THIS PERSON.]
Stand up.
What is this?
The kidnapper has a fan club.
This is the fan club's symbol.
It's a "W" for Wanted.
People think Na Soo Hyun is good looking.
They like him and pity him
because of his brother and sister.
There is a very small group of them.
They go around trying punish
the wrongs of society.
They kill animals and destroy
local businesses.
They've started to leave behind this
symbol and take pictures.
Orson Welles.
This is the ID that Lee Ji Eun gave us
when she gave us Ha Dong Min's mission.
[PARK BO YEON]
Hello.
I'll head to the office now.
Yes, what is it?
Ill be there soon.
What in the world?
He's alive.
Is that the mission?
- That's...
- Isn't he...
That is Doctor Ha Dong Min's lawyer.
Ha Dong Min will be transparent
about everything.
It's a copycat.
We need to call the police.
This isn't something
we need to worry about.
We don't have the real mission yet.
But, how did they know?
How did they know Lee Ji Eun's
Coconut TV ID and password?
We never told the public.
Isn't it possible with hacking?
It is possible.
I don't think you can all ignore this.
If those people really kill that lawyer,
your information was hacked.
You provided a motive for a motive
for a crime like that too.
The public's sympathy for Hyun Woo
will be completely gone.
Apart from the public's sympathy
for Hyun Woo...
it is true that we bear some
responsibility for this.
Today's show will depend on
how fast we can resolve this.
It could completely change the show.
Tell the police first and let's think
about what to do next.
Anyone that was connected to
the incident seven years ago
the culprit has been observing them
and their crimes.
We can be sure of that now.
The Police Commissioner
committed suicide.
Why did Na Jae Hyun
and Ham Tae Young meet?
Why can't that reason
be known to the world?
Who is trying to hide it?
We've lost that chance now.
How is it going with
the investigation team?
They're putting all their resources
into catching Na Soo Hyun.
Detective Park and Yoo believe that
the real culprit is within
the broadcast team.
Let's continue looking at the motive.
Once we figure that out,
we can guess who the next target will be.
We can figure out who
has the most to gain in this.
Senior, meet with Lee Ji Eun once more.
She might cooperate if she hears
about this.
Things have gone out of control unlike
what they planned.
We'll look at Ha Dong Min.
And Professor Kim Woo Jin.
Let's seen what happened
to them seven years ago.
Okay.
Yes, Jung Hye In.
I got the IP.
Please let me live.
Why are you so bad at this?
What are you doing?
Hey.
I won it all! I won!
Let me live...
Please.
I'll give you anything you want.
Chief, we're going to
that location they found.
Gangnam-gu, Samseong-dong 741-1.
Please get us back-up.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Is anyone in there?
Yes, there is.
Your music is turned on so loud.
I can't take it anymore. Come out.
I'll turn it down. Just leave.
You have no manners. Just come out!
What the hell? You must be crazy.
People's reactions are not very...
Hyun Woo is no longer
of interest to people.
Now, the Police Commissioner
has committed suicide.
People are only focused on the
kidnapper's intent.
I'm sure you must
have expected this, Director.
I don't care why they watch
as long as we reach 20 percent.
Come on. Really?
From what I can tell,
you feel a moral duty to save Hyun Woo.
You're also testing to see how explosive
this show can become.
You can think whatever you want.
Let's get moving on
what we discussed yesterday.
Okay.
We'll do the slush fund later.
About the commissioner's suicide...
should I start writing
about him and his daughter?
SG Group has an official press release.
They have doubts about the death of
their youngest son, Ham Tae Young.
They would also like to find Hyun Woo,
who they did not know existed.
They are supporting the station.
They are even acquiring UCN,
which is in financial trouble.
Should I take this as fatherly love
from the billionaire family?
Police. Put your hands up.
Hye In.
Go home, or at least to the
break room and get some rest.
Perhaps, you should go to
the hospital and get an IV drip.
The mission is not here yet.
Sitting here like this
won't make it come.
It's okay. I prefer to be here.
Should I go buy some medicine?
No, it's okay.
Can you do that?
Yes.
You should eat something too.
Buy something easy to digest for Hye In
and something for yourself.
I'll be right back.
You waited on the jogging path
around 6:00 a.m. today.
When Lawyer Koo got out the car,
you kidnapped him.
How did you know where he jogged
and what time to be there?
He has it connected to his social media.
He puts up his jogging route and time.
That's where I saw it.
Your user ID is Magneto.
You're a special level member.
When did you join the Wanted
kidnapper's fan club?
It was after Ha Dong Min
was on the show.
He was using children for test subjects.
That bastard! It made me so angry.
Because of him,
all those poor kids were dying.
So, why didn't you go after Ha Dong Min?
Why did you kidnap Ha Dong Min's lawyer?
I thought that our master would
want to kill Ha Dong Min himself.
Just like when he killed
Professor Kim Woo Jin.
That's why I decided to complete it.
Master?
Hyun Woo's kidnapper.
That what we call him in our community.
Even that police commissioner yesterday.
They're all just rotten
and fill their pockets.
People like me who are born with nothing
we are no better than dogs or pigs
in this "Hell" Joseon.
This plan...
was it just the two of you?
Yes.
So, this is what
an interrogation room is like.
But, it's not like the movies at all.
It's quite lacking. It really is.
Be quiet.
Sit up straight.
Is Wanted not filming here?
We did all of this for our master.
We did fail.
It would be nice if the show aired
that we tried to do something.
Did Hyun Woo's kidnapper
ask you for help?
Oh, gosh, no.
It would've been great if he had.
I said to Magneto that we ought to
try using the potassium chloride.
He said that would ruin our futures.
He just wanted to scare the guy.
So, it wasn't the kidnapper.
Whose idea was it to do this?
The two of just thought
it would be fun, so we did it.
We didn't kill him, so it's fine.
Soon, my parents will be here
and I'll be released.
Before that happens,
can you help me get on the show?
Gosh, seriously!
You're a crazy punk.
Why isn't she picking up?
She should be back by now.
Please let me live.
Let me live, let me live, let me live!
Please let me live! Please!
Why are you doing this to me?
Please let me live!
Please, please!
Let me live!
Help me!
Please save me!
What is it?
"This girl dies or Ha Dong Min dies.
You choose."
Park Bo Yeon? What's going on?
Save me! Please save me.
What's wrong? Where are you?
I don't know.
I was buying medicine
and some man grabbed me.
I don't remember what happened next.
I'm buried underground right now.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
The last thing she saw was the frame
and ceiling of a deserted greenhouse.
All local stations are
looking at greenhouses.
Look through all the CCTVs
in the vicinity of UCN.
Look for any witnesses.
Find him no matter what.
Yes, sir.
Aren't you going to go?
Something is off.
About what?
They were caught too easily.
The kidnapping of the lawyer.
Who told you to do it?
I told you it was just our idea.
How many times do I have to tell you?
You guys are hackers,
yet you allowed your IP to be traced?
You managed to kidnap a person and
take him inside without getting caught.
You allow yourself to get arrested
as if you were waiting.
That was all a part of your plan, right?
Tell me now.
Where did you bury her?
You must be thinking
you'll be easily released.
If we can't catch the guy,
you'll take the fall.
If the victim dies...
Kidnapping, murder...
That's a life sentence.
Your friend Capco must be quick.
He already has a lawyer.
That lawyer is saying that you
threatened his client to do it all.
Will you be okay?
Tell us everything now.
You will be aiding the investigation,
so we could lighten your sentence.
I really don't know where she's buried.
He wasn't using one fixed ID.
I don't know his name either.
We were just chatting
and agreed to do it as a joke.
I really didn't know he was
going to bury anyone.
He's not talking at all.
They definitely planned
on getting caught.
Find out who owns
that place they were caught in.
Neither of them actually lives them.
Okay.
- Are you hurt at all?
- Please help me.
The phone is connected
to a virtual server.
We can't track her.
Mom.
Park Bo Yeon, stay calm.
We will come for you.
We are looking for you
and we'll find you soon.
Are you listening to me?
Are you watching?
Please save me quickly.
Detective!
Park Bo Yeon. It's me, Detective Park.
You know me, right?
The police are working hard to find you.
We will find you soon.
You need to hold on.
Don't hang up and talk to me.
We can't just do nothing.
Let the police handle it.
Let's talk about what we should do
about the kidnapper's demand.
The copycat kidnapper is demanding
that we punish Ha Dong Min.
Ha Dong Min is already in prison.
Ha Dong Min is the only mission
target who has yet to die.
They may not be looking for
a legal punishment here.
Ha Dong Min wouldn't even be getting
punished legally within today either.
This is a demand telling us to kill him.
Didn't you guys know?
That lawyer who was kidnapped
had requested a review
of the legality of his arrest.
Ha Dong Min was questioned yesterday
and the decision will be made today.
That means that the prosecution
hasn't charged him yet.
That's right.
Even if they charge him,
he will apply for bail.
That will just give him more time.
It's not as if he will go to
court today and get sentenced.
In order for him to get punished today
like the copycat demands...
death is the only way.
Let's get Ha Dong Min out of jail
and make a deal.
We should make a preview.
How will you do it?
We need to send a message
to the copycat kidnapper.
Let's trade Ha Dong Min for Bo Yeon.
We'll pretend to listen to his demands.
After that, the police
will have to take over.
I signed a two year lease
for my son to live here.
He had to leave the
country very suddenly.
I rented it out on the internet.
Did you check his identification?
Or did you get payment
through a bank account?
We met in person and
he paid six months' rent in cash.
I got two months rent as a deposit.
He looks very normal.
He sure decorated the place strangely.
He's not that young.
They tape over everything
every three days.
I don't think we have
anything from that spot.
I haven't seen that young man
for about a week either.
How long can Bo Yeon last?
She's in a box in the ground.
If she's not getting oxygen,
she'll have about an hour.
We still don't have a mission.
I don't know how he'll react
if he finds out about this situation.
We only have four more left.
If ten episodes is his goal,
today's show will be important to him.
He'll need to keep this show going.
I don't know if he'll change his plans
or just push things forward.
We'll send out the preview.
Whether it's Bo Yeon's kidnapper or
Hyun Woo's, we'll get a reaction.
Let's make a decision after.
Seeing as he hasn't sent a mission yet,
he might already know everything.
I'll do what I can do
to get Ha Dong Min out.
Do you have a way?
I'll be back.
Mom.
Dad! Please come save me.
Mom...
Come save me, please.
All right, we'll call you right away.
Thank you.
Lieutenant Cha Seung In called.
He thinks the people who kidnapped
Ha Dong Min's lawyers are conspirators.
Then this could be
those fan club members?
The police have a list of the members
that Bo Yeon found.
They've started investigating
the chat rooms and comments.
Isn't there anything that we can do?
We have to fool her kidnapper
and save Bo Yeon.
Hyun Woo's kidnapper knew everything
about Jung Hye In and the station.
The people who kidnapped Bo Yeon
are just copycats.
That's true.
They kidnapped Park Bo Yeon
to copy the Wanted kidnapper.
Burying someone alive has
been in a lot of movies.
Like that movie "Buried."
I'm sure the group
tried to plan it in detail.
If it was a fan club
that was doing this...
everything can't be controlled
and known by her kidnapper.
What if...
I made a preview with a corpse
that looked like Ha Dong Min?
Let's give it a try.
We have to a proper job.
It could put Bo Yeon in more danger.
We have to discuss this with the police
and even let Ha Dong Min's people know.
Young Gwan.
I've never seen this fish before.
Do you think this can
lead us to something?
I think it's some kind of ancient fish,
though I don't know exactly which one.
An ancient type of fish?
I was kind of interested in
rare creatures when I was in school.
It won't be hard to find
which stores sell this.
There are a few internet stores
that sell them too.
Let's get a list of businesses
that sell this fish.
Then find out if they
delivered to this address.
Okay.
Yes, this was one of ours.
We had them two months ago.
Did you deliver it to this address?
Hold on.
Yes, that's right. I sent it here.
Is he a registered member?
Yes, he's a regular customer.
Can we have his information?
Is this Moon Sung Hyuk?
I'm getting tired.
My parents...
Have they heard the news?
Do they know?
Of course, we contacted
your mother and father.
They're at the police station.
They're getting all the updates.
I want to hear my mom's voice.
- My mom.
- Bo Yeon!
We will save you.
- Mom...
- We'll do whatever it takes to save you.
You have to hold on, okay?
Park Bo Yeon, stay strong!
Mom.
Stay focused!
Mom...
All right. I'll get your mom.
I'll go get your mom.
[WE HAVEN'T RECEIVED
THE SEVENTH MISSION YET!]
[DOCTOR HA DONG MIN WHO DID ILLEGAL HUMAN
TESTS WILL RE-APPEAR TODAY ON WANTED.]
[WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HA DONG MIN,
WHO JUST ARRIVED AT THE UNC STATION?]
Yes.
I understand.
The preview will air
during every commercial.
The copycat has to see it and contact us.
We have an actor ready to go.
Bo Yeon...
We have to save Bo Yeon soon.
If he doesn't contact us within a hour...
let's put up the preview
of Ha Dong Min's corpse.
Park Bo Yeon is still talking
to Executive Director Choi
so she has oxygen.
You have to be very careful.
If the media reveals that
Ha Dong Min is still in prison
we may end up provoking
her kidnapper by lying.
The higher-ups have taken measures,
so let's just wait for contact.
By the way...
why isn't Hyun Woo's kidnapper
sending today's mission?
He seems to know what's going on here.
Maybe he doesn't want Park Bo Yeon
to get injured.
I suppose that could be true.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
This is Shin Dong Wook of UCN.
If you try to fool me,
Park Bo Yeon will die immediately.
I'll call again if you actually show me
Ha Dong Min on the air.
I've heard a lot about you,
but I've never been able to meet you.
Why would we have any reason to meet?
Still, you were a senior that
my late husband respected.
He said you were a classmate
he was very close to.
He told me a great deal about you.
He respected me? I don't know about that.
We just drank together and played poker.
That was all.
What brings you here today?
Ah, I saw the preview.
Why did you lie and say that Ha Dong Min
is at the station when he's in prison?
Have you made a decision on his lawyer's
request on the legality of his arrest?
I am going to dismiss it.
Please release Ha Dong Min.
Why should I do that?
Our show's assistant director has been
kidnapped by copycat culprits.
She's buried somewhere
with nothing but a phone.
Her kidnapper is threatening to kill her
unless Ha Dong Min is punished today.
What do you mean punished today?
Do you mean he must be killed like
your son's kidnapper has been doing?
Of course, we would protect
Ha Dong Min once we have him.
What if I trusted you?
And I released a person when
I had made the decision not to.
What if he ends up really dying?
I heard that you're retiring soon.
And you're planning on
setting up your own law practice.
You've never had any corruption issues.
Your wife is ill,
so you want to start over.
What of it?
SG Group's lead counsel position
is vacant at the moment.
They need a wise legal mind to give
their legal department a new image.
I...
Is anyone out there?
What is this about?
This morning from 9:00 to noon,
where were you?
Did you go to work?
No, I wasn't feeling very good.
I took half the day off
and came into work during lunch.
Can anyone verify that
you were home this morning?
I was alone.
My family members left
for work around 8:00 a.m.
This apartment is
a place you rent, right?
Yes, but what is this about?
I left in the middle of a meeting.
Park Bo Yeon... where is she?
Park Bo Yeon?
Who... who is that?
The person you conspired to kidnap
in the Wanted fan club.
Where did you bury her?
What are you saying?
You just show up like this and
start asking me this nonsense.
Are you even really police?
If you really want to investigate,
come back with a warrant.
I came out in the middle of a meeting,
so I have to head back in.
Seriously, why are you doing this?
If he has a navigation app,
look for recent places he went to.
Give me your pin.
Seriously, this is crazy.
You have to tell me what this
is about for me to deny it.
Do you even have proof of anything?
You live in Seoul.
Where did you get so much dirt
on your shoes on the way to work?
I had a few drinks in a park with my
friends in the park a few days ago.
Is that a crime?
We'll let you go if there's nothing here,
so just tell me.
One, six, zero, six, two, three.
Tell me now. Where is Park Bo Yeon?
Senior!
Wait.
It could break so put your shovels
down and use your hands.
Hurry up and dig.
Bo Yeon.
Be... be careful!
Please save me.
She's alive. She's alive!
Please save me...
Hurry up!
Bo Yeon, you did good.
You're okay now.
Park Bo Yeon, are you okay?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
How is she?
She just fell asleep.
Thankfully, there are no other issues
besides shock and exhaustion.
What a relief.
What kind of person was her kidnapper?
He was just an average guy.
Someone you could see anywhere.
He graduated from a college in Seoul
and had a pretty good job.
He wasn't struggling to make a living.
But, he had to give up the things
he really wanted.
An average person like that.
Why would he have done
something like this?
He saw the show.
He said he wanted to become special too.
I'm determined to find Hyun Woo.
I'm determined to
catch his kidnapper too.
We'll do ten episodes of this crazy show.
Before it ends the way
the kidnapper wants...
Before more people
get hurt or destroyed...
I'm going to get ahead of
it all and catch him.
Why are you staring at someone eating?
You can have some
if you didn't eat lunch.
Did you hear about today's show?
I heard.
I heard that Jung Hye In went to the
judge and asked for your release.
So...
is he going to release me?
SG Group's lead counsel position
is vacant at the moment.
They need a wise legal mind to give
their legal department a new image.
I, no...
SG Group and Hyun Woo's uncle would
like to have a meeting with you.
Jung Hye In.
I truly hope you find your son,
Song Hyun Woo.
I mean that.
Thank you.
I hope that the assistant director
ends up safe, as well.
However... I cannot release Ha Dong Min.
Judge!
I have never made judgments based
on my emotions or for any cause.
I only look at the law to see whether
Ha Dong Min should be in prison or not.
I look only to the basic fundamentals
and principles of law.
Using those reasons,
I believe he should be in prison.
- But...
- Good luck finding Hyun Woo.
I hope his kidnapper ends up receiving
severe punishment under the law.
This is the seventh mission.
Get Lee Ji Eun to appear on Wanted.
Last time, you told me that your dad
was the only person who believes you.
You said that it was the world that
made him a depressed alcoholic.
Then before that happened.
So...
Seven years ago...
Tell me what happened
to your dad seven years ago.
Can we talk about that?
I have nothing to say.
People saw Wanted today.
They committed a copycat kidnapping.
They kidnapped a member
of the broadcast team
and demanded we kill Ha Dong Min.
They buried her in the ground.
This isn't what you wanted.
If you want to tell me something...
If something bad happened to you,
tell me about it.
Would your dad still believe you
if he saw you like this?
Are you okay if he wouldn't?
- My dad is dead.
- Is that why it doesn't matter?
So, what happened?
Did you kill Ha Dong Min?
No.
We caught the copycat kidnapper.
What about the broadcast team member?
We saved her right before she died.
Ha Dong Min.
Ha Dong Min can't die.
Why is that?
If he dies now...
Let me use your phone.
Who are you going to call?
You'll know once I call.
Yes. It's me, Ha Dong Min.
I think it's safer for me
in here for now.
Don't you think you should make it easy
for me to get out once this show is done?
Look...
The whole world already knows my face
and I'm just a monster now.
I was already arrested
and I'm in prison.
I can expose that and
it won't destroy me any further.
I'm keeping my mouth shut for
the person who needs to be careful.
Jung Hye In went to see
the judge to get me released.
If she keeps that up,
I might as well tell Jung Hye In.
Wouldn't it be better to help
her find the kidnapper quickly?
I'm the one in danger of dying.
Lieutenant Cha, I received the mission.
I need to meet Lee Ji Eun now.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Someone just jumped off the roof.
I'm certain the culprit
is in the broadcast team.
You took pictures when we
saved Bo Yeon, didn't you?
Are you sure it was suicide?
What do you mean it's not suicide?
- The note was strange.
- Na Soo Hyun?
The only person who would know anything
about this is Ha Dong Min.
This is our chance to figure out
what the kidnapper will do next.
We don't have much time.
I have the mission.
- Don't go alone.
- Let me go!
I can't appear on the show.
Then tell me now who the kidnapper
is and where Hyun Woo is.